<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE version SYSTEM "../rt-version.dtd">

<!--
  * Economics.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2005 The Public Knowledge Project
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  *
  * Reading Tools version: Economics (es_ES)
  *
  * $Id$
  -->

<version id="Economics" locale="es_ES">
	<version_title>Economics</version_title>
	<version_description>The Reading Tools can help readers of this study consult a wide range of related resources that can provide a context for interpreting, situating and evaluating the study.</version_description>

	<context>
		<context_title>Author's work</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Other Works</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Identify other works by the article's author(s) by using OAI engines.</context_description>
		<author_terms />
		<search>
			<search_title>Google Scholar</search_title>
			<search_description>Google Scholar enables specific searches of scholarly literature, including peer-reviewed papers, theses, books, pre-prints, abstracts, and technical reports. Content includes a range of publishers and aggregators with whom Google already has standing arrangements, e.g., the Association for Computing Machinery, IEEE, OCLC's Open WorldCat library locator service, etc. Result displays will show different version clusters, citation analysis, and library location (currently books only).</search_description>
			<url>http://scholar.google.com</url>
			<search_url>http://scholar.google.com/scholar?ie=UTF-8&amp;oe=UTF-8&amp;hl=eng&amp;as_sauthors={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>OAIster (Open Archives Initiative research databases)</search_title>
			<search_description>OAIster is a project of the University of Michigan Digital Library Production Services, and provides searching a wide variety of collections from a wide variety of institutions. These institutions have made the records of their digital resources available to access, and the project team has gathered and aggregated them into the OAIster service.</search_description>
			<url>http://oaister.umdl.umich.edu/</url>
			<search_url>http://oaister.umdl.umich.edu/cgi/b/bib/bib-idx?type=boolean&amp;size=10&amp;c=oaister&amp;q1=&amp;rgn1=entire+record&amp;op2=and&amp;q2=&amp;rgn2=entire+record&amp;op3=And&amp;q3=&amp;rgn3=title&amp;op4=And&amp;rgn4=author&amp;op5=And&amp;q5=&amp;rgn5=subject&amp;op6=And&amp;rgn6=norm&amp;q6=all+types&amp;sort=author%2Fcreator&amp;submit2=search&amp;q4={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Public Knowledge Project Open Archives Harvester</search_title>
			<search_description>The PKP Open Archives Harvester is a free metadata indexing system developed by the Public Knowledge Project through its federally funded efforts to expand and improve access to research. The PKP OAI Harvester allows you to create a searchable index of the metadata from Open Archives Initiative-compliant archives, such as sites using Open Journal Systems or Open Conference Systems.</search_description>
			<url>http://pkp.sfu.ca/harvester/</url>
			<search_url>http://pkp.sfu.ca/harvester/search.php?limit=author&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>IDEAc</search_title>
			<search_description>IDEA: the complete RePEc database at your disposal. Working papers, journal articles, software components, author information, directory of institutions.</search_description>
			<url>http://ideas.repec.org/</url>
			<search_url>http://ideas.repec.org/cgi-bin/htsearch?restrict=http://ideas.repec.org/p/&amp;config=htdig&amp;restrict=&amp;exclude=&amp;sort=score&amp;format=long&amp;method=and&amp;search_algorithm=exact:1&amp;words={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>World Bank Group Documents &amp; Reports</search_title>
			<search_description>The World Bank Group makes more than 14,000 documents available through the Documents &amp; Reports website. Documents include Project appraisal reports, Economic and Sector Works, Evaluation reports and studies and working papers.</search_description>
			<url>http://www-wds.worldbank.org/</url>
			<search_url>http://www-wds.worldbank.org/servlet/WDS_IBank_Servlet?all=&amp;stype=AllWords&amp;dname=&amp;rc=&amp;ss=&amp;dt=&amp;dr=range&amp;bdt=&amp;edt=&amp;rno=&amp;lno=&amp;cno=&amp;pid=&amp;tno=&amp;sortby=D&amp;sortcat=D&amp;psz=20&amp;x=34&amp;y=8&amp;ptype=advSrch&amp;pcont=results&amp;auth={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>NBER</search_title>
			<search_description>NBER (The National Bureau of Economic Research, Inc) is a private, nonprofit, nonpartisan research organization dedicated to promoting a greater understanding of how the economy works. Nearly 500 NBER Working papers are published each year, and many subsequently appear in scholarly journals.</search_description>
			<url>http://papers.nber.org/</url>
			<search_url>http://papers.nber.org/papers?module=search&amp;action=query&amp;default_conjunction=and&amp;keywords={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Definitions</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Definitions</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Double click on any word in the text and it will appear in the &quot;Definition of terms&quot; box.  You can also type or paste a word into the box.  Then use the search function to find a definition for the word.  These resources have been selected because of their relevance and their open (free) access to all or part of their contents.</context_description>
		<define_terms />
		<search>
			<search_title>Google</search_title>
			<search_description>Search for definitions using the popular Google search engine.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.google.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=define%3A{$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Online Glossary of Research Economics</search_title>
			<search_description>An online glossary of terms in research economics.</search_description>
			<url>http://econterms.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://econterms.com/glossary.cgi?query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Merriam-Webster Online</search_title>
			<search_description>A dictionary based on the Webster 10th Collegiate edition, 1993, with updates added annually. More than 160,000 entries. Each word is accompanied by definition, pronunciation, usage, grammatical function, and a brief etymology. Includes a thesaurus. Misspellings return suggested spellings. The dictionary's search system supports internal wildcards and right hand truncation searching. Includes an extensive pronunciation guide and sound files for the pronunciation of many terms.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.merriam-webster.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.merriam-webster.com/cgi-bin/dictionary?book=Dictionary&amp;va={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>OneLook Dictionaries</search_title>
			<search_description>OneLook is a meta-dictionary. Enter an English language word or acronym, and OneLook will search its index of 5,292,362 words in 934 dictionaries indexed in general and special interest dictionaries for the definition.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.onelook.com/index.html</url>
			<search_url>http://www.onelook.com/?ls=a&amp;w={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>AmosWeb GLOSS*arama</search_title>
			<search_description>The AmosWEB GLOSS*arama, a glossary for principles students, is a searchable database of 1800 economic terms and concepts.</search_description>
			<url>http://amosweb.com/gls/</url>
			<search_url>http://amosweb.com/cgi-bin/gls.pl?fcd=dsp&amp;key={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Concise Encyclopedia of Economics (CEE)</search_title>
			<search_description>Concise Encyclopedia of Economics (CEE) - tutorials on various economic topics</search_description>
			<url>http://www.econlib.org/library/CEE.html</url>
			<search_url>http://www.econlib.org/cgi-bin/search.pl?results=0&amp;book=Encyclopedia&amp;andor=and&amp;sensitive=no&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>EH.Net Encyclopedia of Economic and Business History</search_title>
			<search_description>Directed by a distinguished board, articles in this encyclopedia on both business and economic history &quot;are written by experts, screened by a group of authorities, and carefully edited.&quot;</search_description>
			<url>http://eh.net/encyclopedia/</url>
			<search_url>http://eh.net/encyclopedia/search/?Search.x=37&amp;Search.y=10&amp; q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Wikipedia: The Free Encyclopedia</search_title>
			<search_description>&quot;Wikipedia is a free content encyclopedia that is being written collaboratively by contributors from all around the world. The site is a WikiWiki, meaning that anyone ... can edit any article. ...&quot; Without editorial oversight, the quality of the content on this site varies dramatically, but it is worth exploring. The English version has hundreds of thousands of entries. Spanish, French, and Esperanto are among the several other languages offered.</search_description>
			<url>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Main_Page</url>
			<search_url>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Special:Search?go=Go&amp;fulltext=Search&amp;search={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Infoplease.com</search_title>
			<search_description>This site includes contents of the Information Please Almanacs, a biography database, a dictionary, an atlas, and articles from the Columbia Encyclopedia. You can search these ready reference works together or separately or browse the Almanacs. There are feature stories each week covering topics in the news, with links to pertinent Almanac content and other Web resources.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.infoplease.com</url>
			<search_url>http://www.infoplease.com/search?fr=iptn&amp;in=all&amp;x=0&amp;y=0&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Financial Dictionary</search_title>
			<search_description>This dictionary of financial terms is sponsored by specialinvestor.com, which aims to be &quot;the first complete portal in the world aimed at business students.&quot;</search_description>
			<url>http://www.specialinvestor.com/dictionary/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.specialinvestor.com/dictionary/</search_url>
			<search_post>q={$formKeywords}</search_post>			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Book</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Book</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Book-related Resources</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Google Print</search_title>
			<search_description>Google is working with libraries at the University of Michigan, Harvard University, Stanford University, Oxford University and the New York Public Library to digitize books in their collections and make them accessible via Google Print, a massive scanning project that will bring millions of volumes of printed books into the Google Print database.  Click a book title and you'll see the page of the book that has your search terms, your can search for more information within that specific book, find reviews, find related information, learn about the publisher, buy this book, and find nearby libraries that have it.</search_description>
			<url>http://print.google.com</url>
			<search_url>http://print.google.com/print?q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Online books Page</search_title>
			<search_description>Online books Page, edited by John Mark Ockerbloom, at the University of Pennsylvania.  This is an excellent starting point in the search for full-text books on the Internet. Over 20,000 English works in various formats available online at different sites. Entries may be searched by author or title. An interesting feature allows browsing by Library of Congress call number categories. New listings are added regularly and are listed on a separate web page at &lt;a href=&quot;http://onlinebooks.library.upenn.edu/new.html&quot;&gt;http://onlinebooks.library.upenn.edu/new.html&lt;/a&gt;.</search_description>
			<url>http://digital.library.upenn.edu/books/</url>
			<search_url>http://onlinebooks.library.upenn.edu/webbin/book/search?tmode=words&amp;title={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Books-On-Line</search_title>
			<search_description>A collection of over 32935 titles, although some are only excerpts. Browse by subject or search by author or title. Not all items are free.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.books-on-line.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.books-on-line.com/bol/KeyWordSearch.cfm?RowCount=50&amp;Searchquery={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Universal Library</search_title>
			<search_description>The Universal Library is considerably more involved, and more ambitious -- it has amassed a collection of 100,000 e-books (some of them from Project Gutenberg), and is aiming for 1 million e-books by the end of 2006.</search_description>
			<url>http://tera-3.ul.cs.cmu.edu/</url>
			<search_url>http://tera-3.ul.cs.cmu.edu/cgi-bin/DBscripts/advsearch_db.cgi?perPage=25&amp;listStart=0&amp;author1=&amp;subject1=Any&amp;year1=&amp;year2=&amp;language1=Any&amp;scentre=Any&amp;search=Search&amp;title1={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Working papers</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Working papers</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Search the largest online, free research paper collections in economics.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>NBER</search_title>
			<search_description>NBER (The National Bureau of Economic Research, Inc) is a private, nonprofit, nonpartisan research organization dedicated to promoting a greater understanding of how the economy works. Nearly 500 NBER Working papers are published each year, and many subsequently appear in scholarly journals.</search_description>
			<url>http://papers.nber.org/</url>
			<search_url>http://papers.nber.org/papers?module=search&amp;action=query&amp;default_conjunction=and&amp;keywords={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Related studies</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Related studies</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Access to related studies by establishing a working link with an open-access (free) database, with abstracts and/or full texts related to your topic.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>EDIRC</search_title>
			<search_description>EDIRC: Economics Departments, Institutes and Research Centers in the World currently contains 6,321 institutions in 207 countries and territories.</search_description>
			<url>http://edirc.repec.org/</url>
			<search_url>http://edirc.repec.org/cgi-bin/search.cgi?boolean=AND&amp;keyword1={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>World Bank Group Documents &amp; Reports</search_title>
			<search_description>The World Bank Group makes more than 14,000 documents available through the Documents &amp; Reports website. Documents include Project appraisal reports, Economic and Sector Works, Evaluation reports and studies and working papers.</search_description>
			<url>http://www-wds.worldbank.org/</url>
			<search_url>http://www-wds.worldbank.org/servlet/WDS_IBank_Servlet?stype=AllWords&amp;ptype=sSrch&amp;pcont=results&amp;sortby=D&amp;sortcat=D&amp;x=17&amp;y=3&amp;all={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Portals</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Portals</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Offer an entry point to other websites.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>WebEC: World Wide Web Resources in Economics</search_title>
			<search_description>WebEC provides links to a variety of resources on economics. Topics include: economics and teaching; methodology and history; mathematical and quantitative methods; economics and computing; economics data; microeconomics; macroeconomics; international economics; financial economics; public economics; health, education and welfare; labor and demographics; law and economics; industrial organization; business economics; economic history; development, technological change and growth; economic systems; agriculture and natural resources; regional economics; and economics of networks.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.helsinki.fi/WebEc/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;lr=&amp;q=site%3Awww.helsinki.fi%2F WebEc%2F+{$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Nat'l statistics</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Nat'l statistics</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Provides access to statistics in economic studies.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Office for National Statistics (UK)</search_title>
			<search_description>National Statistics is the official UK statistics site. You can view and download a wealth of economic and social data free.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.statistics.gov.uk/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.statistics.gov.uk/CCI/SearchRes.asp?term={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Statistics Canada</search_title>
			<search_description>Statistics Canada is the official source for Canadian social and economic statistics and products.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.statcan.ca/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.statcan.ca:8081/english/clf/query.html?GO%21=GO%21&amp;ht=0&amp;qp=&amp;qs=&amp;qc=0&amp;pw=100%25&amp;la=en&amp;qm=1&amp;st=1&amp;oq=&amp;rq=0&amp;si=0&amp;rf=0&amp;col=alle&amp;qt={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Pay-per-view</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Pay-per-view</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>A pay-per-view service is for those who do not have direct access to electronic journal articles via subscriptions. The service allows customers to gain direct access to an article by paying by credit card using the RSC's secure payment mechanism. Immediately the payment details have been validated, the customer can gain access to the required article file for a period of 30 days.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Ingenta</search_title>
			<search_description>Ingenta restricts access to full text articles. Although access to the full text costs money, the site can be used as a free index.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.ingenta.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.ingenta.com/isis/searching/Search/ingenta?database=1&amp;title={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>ebrary</search_title>
			<search_description>Independent researchers who do not have access to ebrary_ databases through their library may now set up an individual account for as little as $5. ebrary Discover spans multiple academic disciplines and provides anytime, anywhere access to over 20,000 authoritative titles including books in full-text, sheet music, reports and other authoritative documents from more than 175 leading publishers such as Cambridge University Press, Random House, Inc., and The McGraw-Hill Companies.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.ebrary.com/company/</url>
			<search_url>http://shop.ebrary.com/Top?layout=search&amp;f00=text&amp;p01=&amp;f01=subject&amp;d=journal&amp;l=en&amp;sch=%A0%A0%A0%A0%A0Search%A0%A0%A0%A0%A0&amp;frm=adv.x&amp;p00={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Questia</search_title>
			<search_description>Questia provides access to over 47,000 books and 375,000 journal, magazine, and newspaper articles. All books and articles are available in their entirety - search every page.  The subscription rate is ranging from 19.05 per month to 119.95 per year.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.questia.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.questia.com/SM.qst?act=search&amp;keywordsSearchType=1000&amp;mediaType=book&amp;mediaType=journal&amp;mediaType=magazine&amp;mediaType=newspaper&amp;mediaType=encyclopedia&amp;mediaType=startpage&amp;keywords={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Wiley InterScience Pay-per-view Service</search_title>
			<search_description>Wiley InterScience Pay-per-view affords instant, full-text access to an extensive collection of journal articles or book chapters available on Wiley InterScience without the need for a subscription. This service allows anyone to purchase access to individual journal articles or book chapters directly by using a credit card. Access is instant and available for 24 hours.</search_description>
			<url>http://www3.interscience.wiley.com/aboutus/ppv-articleselect.html</url>
			<search_url>http://www3.interscience.wiley.com/search/allsearch</search_url>
			<search_post>allContentSearchForm=&amp;mode=quicksearch&amp;WISindexid1=WISall&amp;WISsearch1={$formKeywords}</search_post>			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Online forums</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Online forums</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Choose online, open-access online forums that would enrich the context of the research studies on your site.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>H-Net</search_title>
			<search_description>H-Net Humanities and Social Sciences Online provides information and resources for all those interested in the Humanities and Social Sciences.</search_description>
			<url>http://www2.h-net.msu.edu/lists/</url>
			<search_url>http://www2.h-net.msu.edu/logsearch/index.cgi?type=keyword&amp;list=All+lists&amp;hitlimit=100&amp;field=&amp;nojg=on&amp;smonth=00&amp;syear=1989&amp;emonth=11&amp;eyear=2004&amp;order=relevance&amp;phrase={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>INOMICS</search_title>
			<search_description>INOMICS provides searches in indexes of other Web pages related to Economics.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.conference-board.org/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.conference-board.org/cgi-bin/MsmFind.exe?AND_ON=N&amp;ALLCATS=X&amp;AGE_WGT=0&amp;EN=X&amp;ES=X&amp;NO_DL=X&amp;x=57&amp;y=11&amp;QUERY={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Teaching files</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Instructional</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Immediately initiates a search based on the subject of the article or paper that connects users to free current and archival articles in the field from leading newspapers around the world.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Tutor 2U Economics</search_title>
			<search_description>Tutor 2U Economics includes study resources, revision guides, relevant links, an updated dataroom, and a discussion forum.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.tutor2u.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.tutor2u.net/search.asp?func=search&amp;tree=0&amp;submit=Search+Tutor2u&amp;myquery={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>biz/ed</search_title>
			<search_description>biz/ed is a series of economics and business simulations on various topics.</search_description>
			<url>http://bized.ac.uk/</url>
			<search_url>http://bized.ac.uk/cgi-bin/htsearch?words={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>EcEdWeb</search_title>
			<search_description>Economic Education Website: The purpose of the Economic Education Website is to provide support for economic education in all forms and at all levels.</search_description>
			<url>http://ecedweb.unomaha.edu/search.cfm</url>
			<search_url>http://www.google.com/u/ecedweb?q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Government policy</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Gov Policy</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Immediately initiates a search based on the subject of the article or paper that connects users to free current and archival articles in the field from leading newspapers around the world.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Access to Australian Government Information and Services</search_title>
			<search_description>The Australian Government Entry Point offers comprehensive and integrated access to Australian Government information and services.  You will find a concentrated body of Australian Government information through this site. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.australia.gov.au&quot;&gt;www.australia.gov.au&lt;/a&gt; currently signposts over 700 Australian Government web sites, indexes more than 5,000,000 pages and uses both metadata and full text indexing to ensure it is a comprehensive government portal.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.fed.gov.au</url>
			<search_url>http://govsearch.australia.gov.au/search/search.cgi?collection=gov&amp;form=au&amp;query=&amp;query_phrase=&amp;query_or=&amp;query_not=&amp;meta_f_sand=&amp;scope=&amp;fscope=512&amp;num_ranks=20&amp;chksummary=chksummary&amp;query_and={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Canadian Government Information</search_title>
			<search_description>Includes links to Canadian government libraries, federal documents and news releases, publications catalogues, and provincial governments. Most information is in English, but some of the linked material is in French, or a combination of French and English.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.nlc-bnc.ca/8/4/index-e.html</url>
			<search_url>http://www.collectionscanada.ca/search/006001-110.01-e.php?q%5B1%5D=pagelevel%3A1&amp;q%5B2%5D=&amp;x=15&amp;y=13&amp;q%5B0%5D={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Directgov</search_title>
			<search_description>Directgov is a government service giving people access to the latest and widest range of public service information in one place on the Web and on Digital TV. Directgov uses the specifications formulated and consulted on through UK GovTalk.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.direct.gov.uk</url>
			<search_url>http://www.direct.gov.uk/AdvancedSearch/SearchResults/fs/en?NP=1&amp;PO1=C&amp;PI1=W&amp;PF1=A&amp;PG=1&amp;RP=20&amp;SC=__dgov_site&amp;Z=1&amp;PT1={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Info4local.gov.uk</search_title>
			<search_description>Information for local government from central government.  This site gives local authorities a quick and easy way to find relevant information on the web sites of central government departments, agencies and public bodies. It includes extensive information on implementing electronic government.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.info4local.gov.uk</url>
			<search_url>http://www.info4local.gov.uk/searchresults.asp?formname=frmAdvanced&amp;keywordstype=1&amp;month=&amp;year=&amp;pub=1&amp;news=1&amp;links=1&amp;allsubjects=1&amp;alldepts=1&amp;alldoctypes=1&amp;keywords={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>The New Zealand government portal</search_title>
			<search_description>The New Zealand government portal is a website providing search capability for, and links into the online and offline information and services of most government agencies.  This site is managed and maintained by the State Services Commission, a New Zealand government department.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.govt.nz</url>
			<search_url>http://www.govt.nz/search?type=spider&amp;t=spider&amp;q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Europa</search_title>
			<search_description>Current information on the member countries of the European Union, including statistical data, policies, news, official documents, legal texts, and other publications.</search_description>
			<url>http://europa.eu.int/index_en.htm</url>
			<search_url>http://europa.eu.int/geninfo/query/engine/search/query.pl?action=FilterSearch&amp;filter=europaflt.hts&amp;Collection=fullEUROPA&amp;ResultTemplate=europarslt_ascii.hts&amp;ResultCount=25&amp;ResultMaxDocs=200&amp;DefaultLG=en&amp;ViewTemplate=europaview.hts&amp;QueryText={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>The Global Legal Information Network (GLIN)</search_title>
			<search_description>The Global Legal Information Network (GLIN) is a database of laws, regulations, judicial decisions, and other complementary legal sources contributed by governmental agencies and international organizations. These GLIN members contribute the official full texts of published documents to the database in their original language. Each document is accompanied by a summary in English and subject terms selected from the multilingual index to GLIN.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.glin.gov</url>
			<search_url>http://www.glin.gov/search.do?refineQuery=&amp;offset=0&amp;refineQueryType=&amp;fromSearch=true&amp;queryType=ALL&amp;searchBtn=Search&amp;includeAllFields=on&amp;searchAll=on&amp;sumLanguage=any&amp;pubLanguage=any&amp;pubJurisdiction=any&amp;publicationJurisdictionExclude=false&amp;searchPublicationDate=true&amp;dateFromDay=01&amp;dateFromMonth=01&amp;dateFromYear=&amp;dateToDay=01&amp;dateToMonth=01&amp;dateToYear=&amp;subjTerm=&amp;subjTermConjunction%5B0%5D=AND&amp;subjTerm=&amp;subjTermConjunction%5B1%5D=AND&amp;subjTerm=&amp;subjTermConjunction%5B2%5D=AND&amp;subjTerm=&amp;subjTermConjunction%5B3%5D=AND&amp;subjTerm=&amp;searchOrder=default&amp;hitsPerPage=10&amp;showSummary=on&amp;queryString={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>The OECD (Organisation for Economic Co-operation and Development)</search_title>
			<search_description>The OECD groups 30 member countries sharing a commitment to democratic government and the market economy. With active relationships with some 70 other countries, NGOs and civil society, it has a global reach. Best known for its publications and its statistics, its work covers economic and social issues from macroeconomics, to trade, education, development and science and innovation.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.oecd.org/home/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.oecd.org/searchResult/0,2665,en_2649_201185_1_1_1_1_1,00.html?fpSearchExact=3&amp;fpSearchText={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>FirstGov</search_title>
			<search_description>FirstGov (U.S. federal and state) is a public-private partnership, led by a cross-agency board.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.firstgov.gov/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.firstgov.gov/fgsearch/index.jsp?db=www&amp;st=AS&amp;ms0=should&amp;mt0=all&amp;rn=2&amp;parsed=true&amp;x=2&amp;y=8&amp;mw0={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Canada Sites</search_title>
			<search_description>Canada Sites provides an information and services gateway run by the Government of Canada and each of the provinces.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.canada.gc.ca/main_e.html</url>
			<search_url>http://search-recherche.gc.ca/cgi-bin/query?mss=canada%2Fen%2Fsimple.html&amp;enc=iso88591&amp;pg=q&amp;kl=en&amp;site=main&amp;browser=IE&amp;mss=canada%2Fen%2Fsimple.html&amp;q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Media reports</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Media reports</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Immediately initiates a search based on the subject of the article or paper that connects users to free current and archival articles in the field from leading newspapers around the world.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Google News</search_title>
			<search_description>Search news reports using the popular search engine Google's news feature.</search_description>
			<url>http://news.google.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://news.google.com/news?hl=en&amp;q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>The Economist</search_title>
			<search_description>The Economist is the online version of the famous magazine with articles and a searchable archive.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.economist.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.economist.com/search/search.cfm?cb=46&amp;area=1&amp;page=index&amp;keywords=1&amp;frommonth=01&amp;fromyear=1997&amp;tomonth=02&amp;toyear=2002&amp;rv=2&amp;qr={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>People's Daily</search_title>
			<search_description>People's Daily, China (January 1999-)</search_description>
			<url>http://english.peopledaily.com.cn/</url>
			<search_url>http://english.peopledaily.com.cn/cgi-bin/htsearch?method=boolean&amp;format=builtin-long&amp;sort=score&amp;config=english&amp;exclude=&amp;words={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Globe and Mail</search_title>
			<search_description>Globe and Mail, Toronto (last seven days)</search_description>
			<url>http://www.globeandmail.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.globeandmail.com/servlet/HTMLTemplate/search?tf=tgam/search/tgam/SearchResults.html&amp;cf=tgam/search/tgam/SearchResults.cfg&amp;current_row=1&amp;start_row=1&amp;num_rows=10&amp;keywords={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Mail &amp; Guardian Newspaper</search_title>
			<search_description>Mail &amp; Guardian Newspaper, South Africa (1994-)</search_description>
			<url>http://www.mg.co.za/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.mg.co.za/mg_search_results.aspx?PrintEdition=PrintEdition&amp;DailyNews=DailyNews&amp;SearchSection=&amp;StartDay=&amp;StartMonth=&amp;StartYear=&amp;EndDay=&amp;EndMonth=&amp;EndYear=&amp;keywords={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>National Public Radio</search_title>
			<search_description>National Public Radio, United States (unlimited)</search_description>
			<url>http://www.npr.org/archives/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.npr.org/search.php?text={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>New York Times</search_title>
			<search_description>New York Times, New York (last seven days)</search_description>
			<url>http://www.nytimes.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://query.nytimes.com/search/query?date=site1week&amp;submit.x=1&amp;submit.y=9&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>The Japan Times Online</search_title>
			<search_description>The Japan Times Online, Japan (January 1999-)</search_description>
			<url>http://www.japantimes.co.jp/search.htm</url>
			<search_url>http://search.japantimes.co.jp/cgi-bin/JTsearch4.pl5?term1={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>The Moscow Times</search_title>
			<search_description>The Moscow Times, Russia (1994-)</search_description>
			<url>http://www.moscowtimes.ru/doc/Search.html</url>
			<search_url>http://www.moscowtimes.ru/cgi-bin/search?config=&amp;exclude=&amp;method=and&amp;format=long&amp;sort=score&amp;matchesperpage=10&amp;words={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Washington Post</search_title>
			<search_description>Washington Post, Washington, DC (last two weeks)</search_description>
			<url>http://www.washingtonpost.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.washingtonpost.com/cgi-bin/search99.pl?searchsection=news&amp;searchdatabase=news&amp;x=11&amp;y=8&amp;searchtext={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Newsdirectory</search_title>
			<search_description>Newsdirectory is a comprehensive and searchable guide to the world's English-language online media. Currently over 8,000 newspapers and magazines are listed, as well as more than 1,000 U.S. television broadcasters.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.newsdirectory.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://ask.elibrary.com/search.asp?refid=NEWSD&amp;datetype=all&amp;srcmags=checked&amp;srcnews=checked&amp;srcbooks=checked&amp;srctvrad=checked&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Web search</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Web search</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Enter a search term for Internet resources through various search engines.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Google</search_title>
			<search_description>Search using the popular Google search engine.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.google.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.google.com/search?q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Google Scholar</search_title>
			<search_description>Google Scholar enables specific searches of scholarly literature, including peer-reviewed papers, theses, books, pre-prints, abstracts, and technical reports. Content includes a range of publishers and aggregators with whom Google already has standing arrangements, e.g., the Association for Computing Machinery, IEEE, OCLC's Open WorldCat library locator service, etc. Result displays will show different version clusters, citation analysis, and library location (currently books only).</search_description>
			<url>http://scholar.google.com</url>
			<search_url>http://scholar.google.com/scholar?ie=UTF-8&amp;oe=UTF-8&amp;hl=en&amp;q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Clusty the Clustering Engine</search_title>
			<search_description>This search tool from Vivismo offers clustered results for a selection of searches.  Metasearch the whole web, or use tabs to search for news, gossip, images, orproducts via Bizrate or eBay.</search_description>
			<url>http://clusty.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://clusty.com/search?query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Vivisimo</search_title>
			<search_description>The award-winning Vivisimo clustering technology, developed by Carnegie Mellon research scientists, is unlocking the value of stored information at Fortune 500 companies, top websites, prestigious publishers and government agencies by categorizing research results on the fly into meaningful orders, thus achieving breakthrough improvement in access to relevant information.</search_description>
			<url>http://vivisimo.com</url>
			<search_url>http://vivisimo.com/search?tb=homepage&amp;v%3Asources=Web&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
</version>
