<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic SYSTEM "../../../../lib/pkp/dtd/helpTopic.dtd">

<!--
  * 000001.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2013-2015 Simon Fraser University Library
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2015 John Willinsky
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  *
  * User Interface - Home
  *
  -->

<topic id="user/topic/000001" locale="en_US" title="Home" toc="user/toc/000000" key="user.home">
	<section>
		<![CDATA[<p>There are two main "Home" pages: one for the Open Journal System as a whole, or Main Site Home Page; and a journal-level Home Page. Both home pages contain much of the same information, but differ in certain respects.</p>]]>	
	</section>

	<section title="Main Site Home Page">
		<![CDATA[<p>Upon accessing the Main Site Home Page you will be provided with a description of the site as a whole, and a list of journals residing on the site. From here you can access a journal's Home Page, access any available current issues, and also register with the journal. The Main Site navigation features break down as follows:</p><p><strong>Top Navigation Bar</strong></p><p><em>Home</em> and <em>About</em> provide information about the site (as opposed to an individual journal).</p><p><em>Log In</em> allows you to create a user profile if you have not already done so. See {help_topic key="user.registerAndProfile" text="Register and Profile"}. The Log In link will be replaced with a User Home link once you register and log in. See {help_topic key="user.userHome" text="User Home"}.</p><p><em>Register</em> allows you to add a journal to your User Home Page.</p><p><em>Search</em> allows you to search the entire site or just an individual journal.  See {help_topic key="user.searchAndBrowse" text="Search and Browse"}.</p><p><strong>Right Navigation Bar</strong></p><p>The <em>Open Journal Systems</em> link will take you to the Public Knowledge Project website, which provides resources for Open Journals Systems and other related software.</p><p>The <em>Journal Help</em> link provides context sensitive help.</p><p>The form under the <em>User</em> heading allows you to log in if you have a username and password.  After logging in you will be taken to your User Home page. Once logged in, there will be links under <em>User</em> to a list of journals you have registered to; to your profile; and to log out.</p><p><em>Language</em> allows you to choose a language supported by OJS.</p><p>The search field under <em>Journal Content</em> allows you to search the site in a basic variety of ways. For a more comprehensive search, click the Search link on the top navigation bar.</p>	<p><em>Font Size</em> allows you to make the site font size smaller or bigger.</p>]]>
</section>

<section title="Journal Home Page">
		<![CDATA[<p>The home page for a journal is the one which is seen when <em>View Journal</em> or <em>Current Issue</em> under the journal's name on the site home page is clicked, or when a journal's name is clicked from <em>User Home</em>.The Journal Home Page breaks down as follows:</p><p><strong>Top Navigation Bar</strong></p><p><em>Home</em> and <em>About</em> provide information about the specific journal.</p><p><em>Log In</em> and <em>Register</em> act as above, but redirect to the journal's home page rather than the site home page.</p><p><em>User Home</em> appears once you have logged in, and displays the user home page. This page provides links to manage your journal roles, and to manage your account.</p>	<p><em>Search</em> provides extensive search options, but is used to search only the journal currently being viewed.</p>	<p><em>Current</em> displays the table of contents of the current issue of the journal, if available.</p>	<p><em>Archives</em> displays the names of previously published issues, if available.  Clicking on the name of a previously published issue will display its table of contents.</p><p>An <em>Announcements</em> link appears on the top navigation bar if the Journal Manager has enabled announcements. Clicking on this link will access the announcements page.</p><p><strong>Right Navigation Bar</strong></p><p>The <em>Open Journal Systems</em> link will take you to the Public Knowledge Project website, which provides resources for Open Journals Systems and other related software.</p><p>The <em>Journal Help</em> link provides context sensitive help.</p><p>The form under <em>User</em> will allow you to log in if you have a username and password.  After logging in you will be taken to your User Home page. Once logged in, there will be links under <em>User</em> to a list of journals you have registered to; to your profile; and to log out.</p><p><em>Language</em> allows you to choose a language supported by OJS.</p><p>The search field under <em>Journal Content</em> allows you to search the journal's content in a basic variety of ways. For a more comprehensive search, click the Search link on the top navigation bar.</p><p><em>Font Size</em> allows you to make the site font size smaller or bigger.</p><p>There is also information for Authors, Readers and Librarians listed in the right navigation bar.</p>]]>

</section>
</topic>
