<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic SYSTEM "../../../../lib/pkp/dtd/helpTopic.dtd">

<!--
  * 000031.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2013-2014 Simon Fraser University Library
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2014 John Willinsky
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  *
  * Management Pages - Import/Export
  *
  -->

<topic id="journal/topic/000031" locale="de_DE" title="Import/Export Data" toc="journal/toc/000001" key="journal.managementPages.importExport">
	<section>
		<![CDATA[<p>The Import/Export Data feature, available from Journal Management, allows the Journal Manager to inject data into and extract data from OJS.</p><p>Data import/export is implemented using plugins, with each format or type of data being provided by a different plugin. For more information, refer to each plugin's documentation, found within OJS' plugin directory.</p><p>Five Import/Export plugins ship with OJS, and are documented below.</p><p>Import/export functionality is also available as a command-line tool; see tools/importExport.php for more information.</p>]]>
	</section>
	<section title="Users XML Plugin">
			<![CDATA[<p>The Users XML Plugin can be used to import and export users and their roles. See the XML DTD in "plugins/importexport/users/users.dtd" for more information.</p>]]>
	</section>
	<section title="Erudit Article Export Plugin">
			<![CDATA[<p>The Erudit Article Export Plugin implements single-article export for full-text indexing using Erudit's XML DTD. See <a href="http://www.erudit.org">http://www.erudit.org</a> for more information.</p>]]>
	</section>
	<section title="Articles &amp; Issues XML Plugin">
			<![CDATA[<p>The Articles &amp; Issues XML Plugin is the primary method for batch import and export. It can be used to import and export single articles, multiple articles, single issues, and multiple issues, including comprehensive metadata. For information on this plugin, see the XML DTD in "plugins/importexport/native/native.dtd".</p>]]>
	</section>
	<section title="PubMed XML Export Plugin">
			<![CDATA[<p>The PubMed XML Export Plugin provides an import/export plugin to generate bibliographic information for articles in the current issue in PubMed standard publisher data format XML for indexing in NLM PubMed/MEDLINE.  Details on the XML format and data requirements is available at: <a href="http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/entrez/query/static/spec.html">http://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/entrez/query/static/spec.html</a>. More information on this plugin can be found in "plugins/importexport/pubmed".</p>]]>
	</section>
	<section title="Crossref XML Export Plugin">
			<![CDATA[<p>The Crossref XML Export Plugin provides an import/export plugin to generate metadata information for articles and issues for indexing in CrossRef.  Details on the XML format and data requirements is available at: <a href="http://www.crossref.org/schema">http://www.crossref.org/schema</a>. More information on this plugin can be found in "plugins/importexport/crossref".</p>]]>
	</section>
</topic>
