<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic SYSTEM "../../../topic.dtd">

<!--
  * 000034.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2006 John Willinsky
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  *
  * Author's Role Review Index - Peer Review
  *
  * $Id$
  -->

<topic id="editorial/topic/000034" locale="en_US" title="Editor Decision" toc="editorial/toc/000010" key="editorial.authorsRole.review.editorDecision">
	<section>
		<![CDATA[<p>With the Editor Decision, the Author will be emailed by the Section Editor with a decision, based on the reviews and the Section Editor's judgment. The decision is also recorded in the Editor/Author Correspondence on the Author's Review page. If the Editor requests revisions before arriving at a final decision, the Author is able to upload a revised version of the submission on this page, as well as revised or additional Supplementary Files as well (reflecting data sets, research instruments, source documents, etc.). The Editor is also able to upload and present versions of the submission or other documents for the Author to consult. (To consult uploaded files, the Author clicks on the file name, and opens the file or saves the file to the computer and then opens it.) If and when the submission is accepted, it will then proceed to the {help_topic key="editorial.editorsRole.submissions.inEditing" text="Editing"} stage of the editorial process.</p><p><i>Resubmit for Review</i>. If the Section Editor's decision is that the submission should be revised and then resubmitted for peer review, the Author should first indicate their willingness to undertake the revisions, using the Editor/Author Correspondence. Then, when the revisions have been completed, the Author uploads the version for a second round of reviews. The Section Editor will submit it to the same Reviewers or to one or more new Reviewers, and notify the Author when a decision has been reached in a similar manner to the initial review.</p>]]>	
	</section>
</topic>
