<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic SYSTEM "../../topic.dtd">

<!--
  * 000040.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2005 The Public Knowledge Project
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  *
  * Layout Editor's Role - Layout
  *
  * $Id$
  -->

<topic id="editorial/topic/000040" locale="en_US" title="Layout" toc="editorial/toc/000013" key="editorial.layoutEditorsRole.layout">
	<section>
		<![CDATA[<p>The Layout Version of the submission has been prepared by the copyeditor to the journal's standards. The Layout Editor will layout the submission in the appropriate file formats and layout style for the journal. The Layout Editor will need to use third party-software to prepare the HTML, PDF, Postscript, etc. files (e.g., Dreamweaver, Front Page, Acrobat, etc.).  As well, the journal is able to make a set of Layout Instructions available to Layout Editors to assist them in properly formatting the files for publication.</p><p><i>Uploading galleys</i>. When the Layout Editor uploads a file to Galley Format, the system will typically identify the file type based on its suffix (e.g., PDF, HTML), as well as provide information on the file size and its original name. This label, which will appear on the journal's Table of Contents in association with the item published, will tell readers what kind of file format the published item is available in. The Layout Editor also has the option of manually labelling the file. The Layout Editor can upload more than one Galley Format file, delete files that have been uploaded, and edit information such as the file name. In uploading HTML files, the images and style sheet must also be uploaded with the .htm or .html file.</p><p><i>Supplementary files</i>. If the Author has uploaded any Supplementary Files, they  will already be in place. They are to be published in the journal in their original file format, unless the journal has a special policy with regard to their preparation (as with Figures or illustrations). Even if the policy is to publish them in their original format, the Layout Editor may still wish to consult the files to ensure that they are legible and to see whether they can be readily made to further conform to journal style and standards. Supplementary Files can be deleted, worked on, and uploaded again by the Layout Editor (as well as by the Author, if required because of aspects of the file format).</p>]]>	
	</section>
</topic>
