<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic SYSTEM "../../../topic.dtd">

<!--
  * 000038.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2006 John Willinsky
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  *
  * Copyeditor's Role - Copyediting
  *
  * $Id$
  -->

<topic id="editorial/topic/000038" locale="en_US" title="Copyediting" toc="editorial/toc/000012" key="editorial.copyeditorsRole.copyediting">
	<section>
		<![CDATA[<p>On the submission's Copyediting page, the copyediting is divided into three steps. The copyediting is done directly on the submission file, with suggestions to improve the flow of language and communication of meaning, and with changes to ensure the submission adheres to the journal's style and format. The file is then saved on the Copyeditor's or Author's computer and uploaded to the appropriate Step. This makes the copyedited file available for the next step, or in the case of Step 3, for the Layout stage.</p><p><i>Step 1</i><br />In the first step, the Copyeditor clicks on the file name to download the file and open it. After opening the submission in Step 1, the Copyeditor then copyedits the text, following the agreed upon copyediting standards for the journal. (These can be customized by the Journal Manager in Setup.) The Copyeditor records all suggested changes and corrections, as well as Author Queries (e.g., missing page numbers) and/or Editor Queries (e.g., matters of journal style and standards).  When finished the initial copyedit, Copyeditor saves the file to the computer and uploads it for the next step, which is the Author copyedit.</p><p><i>Completion of Step 1</i>. Once the copyedited file is uploaded and the metadata reviewed, the Copyeditor clicks the email icon under Complete for Step 1. This leads to an email to the Author and the Editor, informing them that Step 1 is complete. The Copyeditor should note in the email if there are any Editor Queries for the Section Editor to consider.</p><p><i>Step 2</i><br />The Author downloads and opens the copyedited version from Step 1 and reviews the copyediting, responding to any Author Queries directly on the file. The Author saves the file and uploads it in Step 2, which makes the file available to the Copyeditor for the final copyedit. The Editor will respond to any Editor Queries by email to ensure that Author and Editor do not upload versions of the file on top of one another. The Author sends a completed email to the Copyeditor and Editor, initiating, in effect, the third step.</p><p><i>Step 3</i><br />The Copyeditor downloads and opens the copyedited file in Step 2 and creates a clean version (with all traces of the copyediting process removed) based on the responses of the Author and Editor, which is ready for the Layout Editor to turn into the published version of the submission. The Copyeditor uploads the clean copy in Step 3, which also becomes the Layout Version for the Editing page. The Copyeditor then uses the email icon under Complete to notify the Layout Editor and Section Editor that copyediting for the submission is now complete.</p>]]>	
	</section>
</topic>
