<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic SYSTEM "../../topic.dtd">

<!--
  * 000027.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2005 The Public Knowledge Project
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  *
  * Section Editor's Role Index - Editing - Copyediting
  *
  * $Id$
  -->

<topic id="editorial/topic/000027" locale="en_US" title="Copyediting" toc="editorial/toc/000007" key="editorial.sectionEditorsRole.editing.copyediting">
	<section title="">
		<![CDATA[<p>Once the Copyeditor has  been selected and an email sent requesting the process begin, the Copyeditor will work directly on the submission marking up the proposed changes according to the journal's Copyediting Instructions [Copyediting Instructions]. The Copyeditor will upload the initial copyedit version as part of Step 1, and this file will be sent to Step 2, when the Copyeditor completes the initial step and sends the "Complete" email to the Author, with a cc to the Section Editor, requesting Step 2 to begin. The Copyeditor creates a clean and final copyedited version in Step 3, with this version serving as the Layout Version in Layout, when the Copyeditor completes Step 3. The Section Editor may wish to look this version over to ensure that it means the standards and guidelines of the journal, before the Layout Editor begins work on it.</p><p><i>Editor Queries in copyediting</i>. In the initial copyedit, there may be Editor Queries (with regard to journal style, for example), which the Copyeditor will reference in their email that is sent to the Author and Section Editor on the completion of Step 1. The Section Editor should review the Editor Queries by clicking on the file name in Step 2, and emailing a response to the queries directly to the Copyeditor (by clicking on the email icon under Request) to avoid uploading a version of the file on top of the Author's responses to the initial copyediting of the Submission.</p><p><i>Copyediting Options</i>. Should the need arise (if, say, the Section Editor is acting as the Copyeditor), the Section Editor is able to upload a version of the submission to each of the Copyediting stages, although care must be taken not to over-write a version that was uploaded by the Copyeditor or Author after the Section downloads and makes changes to the submission.</p>]]>	
	</section>
</topic>
