<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE locale SYSTEM "../../../../../lib/pkp/dtd/locale.dtd">

<!--
  * plugins/generic/oas/locale/en_US/locale.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2012 John Willinsky
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  *
  * Localization strings.
  -->
 
<locale name="en_US" full_name="U.S. English">
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.displayName">Open Access Statistics (OA-S)</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.description"><![CDATA[The OA-S plugin transforms OJS into a data provider for the <a href="http://www.dini.de/projekte/oa-statistik" target="_new">Open Access Statistics (OA-S) project</a>.]]></message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.report.displayName">OA-S Reporting</message>
	<message key="plugins.reports.oas.report.description">This plugin implements reports based on OA-S metrics.</message>
	
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.optout">Opt Out</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.optout.done">You successfully opted out from usage statistics collection. While you see this message no statistics will be collected from your usage of this site.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.optout.title">Privacy Information</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.optout.link">Read more...</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.optout.shortDesc"><![CDATA[We log anonymous usage statistics. Please read the <a href="{$privacyInfo}">privacy information</a> for details.]]></message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.optout.cookie">
		If you click the opt-out button below then your browser will receive an "opt-out cookie" and no statistics information will be collected at all as long as
		this cookie is present in your browser. The opt-out information will be stored for one year and will be renewed for another year whenever you access OJS. The
		cookie contains no information that may be used to identify you. Please note that if you are using a different browser or if you delete cookies from your
		browser then you'll have to opt-out again as we'll not keep any personal information about you on our side to protect your privacy.
	</message>

	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings">Settings</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.description"><![CDATA[
		The OA-S plugin requires access to a SALT server to pseudonimize IP addresses. After registering your OJS installation with the OA-S project you'll
		receive a username and password from University Library Saarbrücken (SULB). Please enter these login credentials here so that you are able to use the
		plug-in.
	]]></message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.oasSettings">OA-S Plugin: Settings</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.saltApiPassword">Password</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.saltApiPasswordInstructions">Please enter the corresponding SALT server password.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.saltApiPasswordRequired">Please enter a valid password to authenticate to the SALT server.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.saltServerSettings">SALT server settings</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.saltApiUsername">Username</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.saltApiUsernameInstructions">Please enter the OA-S SALT server username you received from University Saarbrücken.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.oas.settings.saltApiUsernameRequired">Please enter a valid username to authenticate to the SALT server (colons are disallowed).</message>
</locale>
