<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic SYSTEM "../../topic.dtd">

<!--
  * 000000.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2004 The Public Knowledge Project
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  *
  * Author Submission Process Index 
  *
  * $Id$
  -->

<topic id="submission/topic/000000" locale="en_US" title="Submission Process" toc="submission/toc/000000" key="HELP_TOPIC_INDEX">
	<section title="">
		<![CDATA[<p>The journal provides Authors with the ability to upload their submission directly to the journal Web site. Author wishing to submit an item to the journal needs to first register with the journal Web site. On doing so, the Author will have the option of also registering as a Reviewer and a Reader.  On completing the registration process, the Author is taken directly to User Home, listing the various roles under which the Author is enrolled. Clicking on the role of Author, takes the Author to the submissions page, where a list of current and past submissions are listed, and where a new submission can be initiated. The Submission process is broken down into five steps, with guidance provided at each step. Authors do not need to complete the five steps at one go, but can return to what will be listed as an "Incomplete".</p>]]>	
	</section>
	<section title="Author Guidelines">
		<![CDATA[<p>The journal provides a set of Author Guidelines in About the Journal that cover the bibliographic and other formatting standards employed by the journal. For aspects not covered in the examples provided by the Guidelines, Authors may also wish to browse through published articles in the journal to see how the journal handles other sorts of material.</p>]]>	
	</section>
	<section title="Submission Requirements">
		<![CDATA[<p>In order to ensure that submissions to the journal have been properly prepared and are in a suitable format for processing, the Journal Manager and Editor have developed a set of Submission Requirements which the Author must check off as having been complied with, before being allowed to proceed to Step Two of the Author Submission process. If the Author is unable to comply with one of the Requirements for some reason, the Author can check the Requirement and provided an explanation in the Comments to the Editor.</p>]]>	
	</section>
	<section title="Indexing and Metadata">
		<![CDATA[<p>This journal system has the Authors participate in the indexing of submissions to the journal. The system itself also generates some of the indexing or metadata elements (such as journal title, date, URL, etc.). Metadata, or data about data, amounts to a series of terms that describe the document or data at issue, thus the comparable use of indexing terms which do the same thing. The journal uses a metadata protocol for indexing submissions that has been developed and is maintained by the Open Archives Initiative (OAI) which draws, in turn, on the Dublin Core Metadata Initiative. The OAI Metadata Harvesting Protocol is the emerging standard for research, enabling OAI compliant search engines to create research indexes based on the resources from around the world. However, the journal's contents are also available through Google and other standard, Web-wide search engines.</p><p><i>Metadata elements</i>. The Dublin Core consists of 15 metadata elements that are used to identify and describe documents. The elements include traditional indexing terms for identifying documents, such as Author, Title, Description (Abstract), Subject, allowing for more detailed or granular indexing by also including elements such as Type, Coverage, and Sponsor. The Journal Manager and Editor of the journal have selected which metadata elements are appropriate for this journal and have provided examples of each - based on the journal's scope and focus - to guide Authors.</p><p><i>Advantages of indexing</i>. Authors are encouraged to complete the indexing of their submission in Step 2 of the Submission process, and will have the opportunity to review and revise the metadata as part of the editorial process. The metadata will also be reviewed as part of the Copyediting step. The metadata for this journal will be "harvested" by a number of research-dedicated search engines that create, in effect, a research index or guide. Work that is well indexed will be that much more easily found by those who need it and are more likely to cite it. While there are limits to the number of terms by which a work is indexed, Authors are encouraged to think about how their work is positioned and found by virtue of this detailed indexing.</p>]]>	
	</section>
	<section title="Supplementary Files">
		<![CDATA[<p>The Author is able to upload the Supplementary Files in Step 4 of the Submission Process. The Supplementary Files are intended to include research data sets, research instruments, source texts or other materials that might otherwise form an appendix to the submission but warrant being treated as separate documents as they may have value on their own merits. In addition, the Supplementary Files will be indexed by the Author, independently of the submission, enabling the Files to be part of a larger index and found by those looking for these particular type of items.</p><p><i>Supplementary File formats</i>. Supplementary Files are also uploaded in their original file format - and on which they are no restrictions - and remain in that format, as opposed to the rest of the submission which must be in a standard manuscript format and will be transposed into a standard publication format. This means that data sets in spread sheets or flash demonstrations can be uploaded and preserved in that format. This may pose challenges to readers, which Authors need to take into account, perhaps by providing in the description of the file, where the requisite "reader" to open and view this File can be found.</p>]]>	
	</section>
</topic>
