<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE locale SYSTEM "../../../../../lib/pkp/dtd/locale.dtd">

<!--
  * plugins/generic/usageStats/locale/en_US/locale.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2013-2019 Simon Fraser University
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2019 John Willinsky
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  *
  * Localization strings
  -->

<locale name="en_US" full_name="U.S. English">
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.settings.logging">Access log options</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.settings.createLogFiles">Create log files</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.settings.createLogFiles.description">Activating this option will make the plugin create access log files inside the files directory. Those files should be used to extract the usage statistics data. If you don't want to create more access log files you can leave this option disabled and use your own server log access files.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.settings.logParseRegex">Parse log files regex</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.settings.logParseRegex.description">The default regex used can parse apache access log files in combined format and also the plugin's log files. If your access log files are in a different format you will have to insert a regex capable of parsing them and giving the expected values. See UsageStatsLoader::_getDataFromLogEntry() for more information.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.settings.saved">Usage statistics plugin settings saved</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.settings.dataPrivacyOption">Data privacy option</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.settings.dataPrivacyOption.saltFilepath">File path for the anonymizing salt</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.settings.dataPrivacyOption.saltFilepath.invalid">The salt file is not writable.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.settings.dataPrivacyOption.requirements">To ensure data privacy, you must specify a file readable and writable by the web user to contain a randomly generated salt value.  This file must NOT be backed up to ensure privacy protection. The salt is randomly generated either using: the function mcrypt_create_iv, which requires the PHP mcrypt; the function openssl_random_pseudo_bytes, which requires the PHP openssl; the file /dev/urandom, which works only on *nix systems; or the function mt_rand, which is not cryptographically safe. Thus, if you are using a Windows server, please ensure that you install either the PHP mcrypt or openssl enabled in order to have the cryptographically safe generated salt.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.settings.dataPrivacyOption.description">Activate this option to use a plugin version that respects privacy legislations, i.e. that is logging hashed IP addresses, informs the users about the tracking and provides an opt-out option for users. Note: when using this option you will not be able to use the geo features of the plugin.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.settings.dataPrivacyOption.requiresSalt">Enabling data privacy requires a salt file.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.settings.dataPrivacyOption.excludesCity">Enabling data privacy excludes City as an optional statistic.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.settings.dataPrivacyOption.excludesRegion">Enabling data privacy excludes Region as an optional statistic.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.settings.dataPrivacyCheckbox">Respect data privacy</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.settings.optionalColumns">Optional statistic information</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.settings.archives">Archives</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.settings.compressArchives.description">Activate this option to compress archived log files using gzip tool (you will have to configure the gzip setting inside config.inc.php). If you have a high traffic site it's a good idea to enable this, so you can save some extra disk space.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.settings.compressArchives">Compress archives</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.settings.optionalColumns.description">Enable or disable the collection of the following optional information. This will influence on the possible statistics reports you can retrieve, and also will have an impact on the database size. DO NOT CHANGE unless you fully understand what you're doing.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.settings.optionalColumns.cityRequiresRegion">The optional column "City" requires the optional column "Region".</message>

	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.usageStatsLoaderName">Usage statistics file loader task</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.openFileFailed">The file {$file} could not be opened and was rejected.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.invalidLogEntry">The line number {$lineNumber} from the file {$file} is not a valid log entry and the file was rejected.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.removeUrlError">The line number {$lineNumber} from the file {$file} contains an url that the system can't remove the base url from.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.loadDataError">Couldn't load data extracted from file {$file}. The error was: {$error}. The file was moved to stage again.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.displayName">Usage Statistics</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.description">Present data objects usage statistics. Can use server access log files to extract statistics.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.pluginDisabled">Usage statistics plugin is disabled. No log files processed.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.processingPathNotEmpty">The directory {$directory} is not empty. This could indicate a previously failed process, or a concurrently running process.  This file will be automatically reprocessed if you are also using scheduledTasksAutoStage.xml, otherwise you will need to manually move any orphaned files in the processing directory back into the stage directory.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.noCounterBotList">The COUNTER bot list could not be found, or more than one list is present. The file {$file} could not be processed.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.failedCounterBotList">The COUNTER bot list {$botlist} could not be opened. The file {$file} could not be processed.</message>
	
	<message key="plugins.reports.usageStats.report.displayName">OJS usage statistics report</message>
	<message key="plugins.reports.usageStats.report.description">OJS default usage statistics report (COUNTER ready)</message>

	<message key="plugins.reports.usageStats.optout.displayName">Usage Statistics Privacy Information</message>
	<message key="plugins.reports.usageStats.optout.description">Usage Statistics Privacy Information</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.optout.title">Usage Statistics Information</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.optout.shortDesc"><![CDATA[We log anonymous usage statistics. Please read the <a href="{$privacyInfo}">privacy information</a> for details.]]></message>	
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.optout.description"><![CDATA[
		<h3>General Privacy Information</h3>
		<p>Please refer to our general <a href="{$privacyStatementUrl}">privacy statement</a>.</p>
		<h3>Usage Statistics</h3>
		<p>In order to be able to analyse usage and impact of our journal and the published articles, we collect and log access to the journal’s homepage, issues, articles, galleys and supplementary files. In the process all data is anonymised. No personal information is logged. IP addresses are anonymised by being hashed (using <em>SHA 256</em>) in combination with a <em>secure 64 characters long salt</em> that is automatically <em>randomly generated and overridden on a daily basis</em>. Therefore IP addresses cannot be reconstructed.</p>
		<p>The following information is collected next to the anonymised IP addresses:</p>
		<ul>
		<li>Access type (i.e. administrative)</li>
		<li>Request time</li>
		<li>Requested URL</li>
		<li>HTTP status code</li>
		<li>Browser</li>
		</ul>
		<p>The collected data is only used for evaluation purposes. No IP addresses are mapped to user IDs. It is technically impossible to trace a specific set of data to a specific IP address.</p>]]></message> 
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.optout.done"><![CDATA[
		<p>You successfully opted out of usage statistics collection. While you see this message no statictics will be collected from your usage of this site. Click the button below to revert your decision.</p>]]></message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.optin">Opt In</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.optout">Opt Out</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.usageStats.optout.cookie"><![CDATA[
		<p>If you wish you can opt-out of the data collection process. By clicking the opt-out button below, you can actively decide against participating in the statistical analysis. When clicking the opt-out button a <em>cookie</em> is being created on your system to store your decision. If the privacy settings of your browser lead to cookies being automatically deleted you will have to opt-out again the next time you access this journal. The cookie is only valid for one browser. If you use a different browser, you will have to opt out again. No individual information is stored within this cookie. This cookie lease is valid for one year after your last access.</p>
		<p>Please bear in mind that general server logs are not affected by your decision to opt-out of the detailed evaluation process. Please refer to our general <a href="{$privacyStatementUrl}">privacy statement</a>.</p>]]></message>
	<message key="plugins.reports.usageStats.metricType">OJS/COUNTER</message>
	<message key="plugins.reports.usageStats.metricType.full">Open Journal Systems statistics (COUNTER ready)</message>
</locale>
