<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE locale SYSTEM "../../../../../lib/pkp/dtd/locale.dtd">

<!--
  * plugins/generic/dataverse/locale/tr_TR/locale.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2013-2015 Simon Fraser University Library
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2015 John Willinsky
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  *
  * Dataverse plugin localization strings
  -->

<locale name="tr_TR" full_name="Türkiye Türkçesi">

	<!-- Dataverse Plugin -->
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.displayName">Veri Dizisi Eklentisi</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.description">Veri setleri ve/veya diğer ek dosyaların bir Veri Dizisi'nde depolanması</message>

	<!-- Set up Dataverse: DVN URL and authentication details -->
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.connect">Bağlantı</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.dvnUri">Veri Dizisi Ağ URL'si</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.dvnUriDescription">URL of Dataverse Network to which the journal's Dataverse belongs</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.usernameDescription">Username of account to be used to deposit files in Dataverse</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.passwordDescription">Yukarıda verilen kullanıcı adı için şifre</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.dvnUriRequired">Veri Dizisi ağı URL'si gerekli.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.dvnUriNotValid">Veri Dizisi ağı URL'si geçerli değil.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.usernameRequired">Belirli Veri Dizisi ağı için lütfen geçerli bir kullanıcı adı giriniz.</message>
	<!-- Set up Dataverse: select Dataverse -->
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.selectDataverse">Veri Dizisi Seç</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.dataverse">Veri Dizisi</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.dataverseDescription">Bu derginin veri dosyalarını depolamak için Veri Dizisi seçiniz.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.dataverseRequired">Lütfen bir Veri Dizisi seçiniz.</message>

	<!-- Plugin configuration: Settings -->
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings">Ayarlar</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.dataPolicies">Veri Politikaları</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.dataPoliciesDescription">Veri politikaları konfigürasyonu</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.dataAvailabilityPolicy">Veri Kullanılabilirliği Politikası</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.dataAvailabilityPolicyDescription">Dergi için genel veri kullanılabilirliği politikası. Bu derginin hakkında kısmında görünür.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.dataAvailabilityRequired">Lütfen veri kullanılabilirliği politikası giriniz.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.sectionPoliciesDescription">Belirli dergi bölümler için veri politikaları ekleyiniz.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.authorGuidelinesDescription"><![CDATA[Veri gönderisi ve atıf rehberleri için <a href="{$authorGuidelinesUrl}" target="_blank">Yazar Rehberleri</a>ni düzenle.]]></message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.checklistDescription"><![CDATA[Edit <a href="{$checklistUrl}" target="_blank">Submission Preparation Checklist</a> to help authors comply with data submission and citation guidelines.]]></message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.reviewPolicyDescription"><![CDATA[Edit <a href="{$reviewPolicyUrl}" target="_blank">Review Policy</a> to address datasets.]]></message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.reviewGuidelinesUrl"><![CDATA[Edit <a href="{$reviewGuidelinesUrl}" target="_blank">Review Guidelines</a> to include instructions for reviewing datasets.]]></message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.copyeditInstructionsUrl"><![CDATA[Edit <a href="{$copyeditInstructionsUrl}" target="_blank">Copyedit Instructions</a> to include instructions for datasets.]]></message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.termsOfUse">Terms of Use</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.termsOfUseRequired">Provide terms of use or choose to fetch terms of use from Dataverse.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.termsOfUseDescription">Provide the terms of use to which users must agree before depositing data files.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.fetchTermsOfUse">Fetch terms of use from the Dataverse set up for this journal.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.defineTermsOfUse">Enter custom terms of use in the field below.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.dataverseTermsOfUseError">Could not retrieve terms of use for the configured Dataverse. Please check connection settings.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.metadata">Üst veri ayarları</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.citationFormat">Atıf biçimi</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.citationFormatDescription">Choose format of publication citation displayed in study cataloguing information.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.citationFormat.apa">APA Atıf Biçimi</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.pubIdType">Genel belirleyici türü</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.pubIdTypeDescription"><![CDATA[Choose type of public identifier to link to article from publication citation. If no <a href="{$pubIdsUrl}">public identifier plugins</a> are enabled, citations for published articles will use OJS URLs.]]></message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.workflow">İş akışı ayarları</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.requireData">Gerekli veri dosyaları</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.requireDataDescription">Require submissions to include data files deposited in Dataverse.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.requireDataError">Authors are required to deposit submission data files in Dataverse. Upload a supplementary file to continue.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.studyRelease">Yayın taslak çalışmaları</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.studyReleaseSubmissionAccepted">editör kabulleri gönderisi</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.studyReleaseArticlePublished">Makale yayınlandı</message>

	<!-- Settings: default values -->
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.default.dataAvailabilityPolicy"><![CDATA[{$journal} requires, as a condition for publication, that data supporting the results in the paper should be archived in an appropriate public archive. {$journal} recommends the <a href="http://thedata.harvard.edu/">Harvard Dataverse</a>, which is free and open to all researchers worldwide to share, cite, reuse and archive research data. Data are important products of the scientific enterprise, and they should be preserved and usable for decades in the future. Authors may elect to have the data publicly available at time of publication. Exceptions may be granted at the discretion of the editor, especially for sensitive information such as human subject data or the location of endangered species. Any exceptions should be documented in a statement in the public article. (Adapted from <a href="http://datadryad.org/pages/jdap">Joint Data Archiving Policy</a> (JDAP)).]]></message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.default.authorGuidelines.extras">Örnek yazar rehberleri</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.default.authorGuidelines.extras.label">Show example data submission and citation guidelines</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.default.authorGuidelines"><![CDATA[<ol>
     <li>
       <p>Definition of data that must be shared</p>
       <p>A "minimal dataset" can be defined to consist of the dataset used to reach the conclusions drawn in the manuscript with related metadata and methods, and any additional data required to replicate the reported study findings in their entirety. Include sufficient information for a researcher to understand data, and any citations to data from which the replication set is derived. Core descriptive data, methods, and study results should be included within the main paper, regardless of data deposition. Authors who have datasets too large for sharing via repositories or uploaded files should contact {$journal} for advice. (Adapted from <a href="http://www.plos.org/data-access-for-the-open-access-literature-ploss-data-policy/">PLOS' Data Policy</a>)</p>
     </li>
     <li>
       <p>Guidance on sharing datasets that derive from work involving human participants</p>
       <p>{$journal} recognizes that there are cases where for reasons of privacy, national security and commercial confidentiality the full data cannot be made openly available. In such cases researchers should share their data analysis under the least restrictive terms consistent with legal requirements, and abiding by the research ethics and guidelines of their community. This should include opening up non-sensitive data, summary data, metadata and code; and facilitating access if the owner of the original data grants other researchers permission to use the data. (Adapted from OKF's <a href="http://openeconomics.net/principles/#sthash.MdxVXZlC.dpuf">Open Economics Priciples</a>)</p>
     </li>
     <li>
       <p>Guidance on Data Citation</p>
       <p>If your research data is deposited at the same time as your manuscript using OJS' article submission form then a Data Citation will automatically be generated by the Harvard Dataverse. However, if your research data is already in a repository then here is the suggested Data Citation format to include when you submit your manuscript:</p>
       <p>Author(s), Year, Dataset Title, Global Persistent Identifier, Data Repository or Archive, version and subset.</p>
       <p>For more information on Data Citation best practices please review <a href="http://www.force11.org/datacitation">Force11's Data Citation Priciples</a>.</p>
     </li>
   </ol>]]></message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.default.checklist.extras">Submission preparation checklist examples</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.default.checklist.extras.label">Show example checklist items for submissions with datasets</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.default.checklist"><![CDATA[<ol>
   <li><p>If intending to share datasets that derive from work involving human participants please review "Guidance on sharing datasets that derive from work involving human participants" above.</p></li>
   <li><p>Prepare dataset for deposit by reviewing replication guidelines: <a href="http://thedata.org/book/replication-guidelines">http://thedata.org/book/replication-guidelines</a></p></li>
   <li><p>If depositing into the Harvard Dataverse, you may submit your dataset in OJS at the same time as your manuscript in {$journal}. This will be automatically deposited in the Harvard Dataverse and will generate a Data Citation with a persistent URL (DOI) which you can then refer others to cite your data when your article is published.</p></li>
   <li><p>If your dataset is already in a recommended public archive please include a Data Citation with a persistent URL. For guidelines on Data Citation please review the author guidelines.</p></li>
   </ol>]]></message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.default.reviewPolicy.extras">Review policy examples</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.default.reviewPolicy.extras.label">Show examples of review policies for datasets</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.default.reviewPolicy"><![CDATA[<ul>
   <li><p>Deposited datasets should be treated as part of the article for the purpose of peer review; OR</p></li>
   <li><p>At acceptance, and prior to the final version of the manuscript, underlying data must be submitted along with a description of how the dataset was created (including any differences from prior versions, and the name of any software packages that were used).</p></li>
   </ul>
   <p>A review policy should include a statement on datasets derived from work involving human participants:</p>
   <ul>
   <li><p>Datasets that derive from work involving human participants should demonstrate that the study participants' privacy was preserved as indicated in the Data Availability Policy. They should also preferably meet the "minimal dataset" requirement described in the Data Availability Policy.</p></li>
   </ul>]]></message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.default.reviewGuidelines.extras">Example review guidelines</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.default.reviewGuidelines.extras.label">Show example guidelines for reviewing datasets</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.default.reviewGuidelines"><![CDATA[<p>As regards an article's accompanying data, reviewers should verify that the article and dataset comply with the journal's data submission policy, that the data appear consistent with the article, and the article and supplementary documentation are sufficient to understand the data provided, as well as its origins and the way in which it was used.</p>]]></message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.default.copyeditInstructions.extras">Example copyedit instructions</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.default.copyeditInstructions.extras.label">Show examples of copyediting instructions for datasets</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.settings.default.copyeditInstructions"><![CDATA[<ul>
			<li><p>Copyeditors have verified that data citation policy is followed; OR</p></li>
			<li><p>Copyeditors have verified that empirical claims are accompanied by appropriate citations to data.</p></li>
		</ul>]]></message>

	<!-- Notifications -->
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.notification.studyCreated">Submission data has been deposited in Dataverse.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.notification.studyUpdated">Submission data has been updated in Dataverse.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.notification.fileAdded">Supplementary file has been deposited in Dataverse.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.notification.fileDeleted">Supplementary file has been removed from Dataverse.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.notification.studyDeleted">Submission data has been removed from Dataverse.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.notification.releaseDataverse">Data published in this journal's Dataverse is not accessible until the Dataverse is released. Please log in to the journal's Dataverse and release it.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.notification.studyReleased"><![CDATA[<p>Submission data has been published in Dataverse:</p><p>{$dataCitation}</p>]]></message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.notification.error">An error occured updating this submission's data in Dataverse.</message>

	<!-- Article metadata for completed submissions: form errors -->
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.metadataForm.studyLocked">This submission's Dataverse study is locked for processing. Submission metadata can't be updated until processing has completed.</message>

	<!-- Additional metadata: suppfile form -->
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.suppFile.title">Dataverse Plugin: Publish Data</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.suppFile.description">Research data can be submitted for publication by depositing supplementary files in the journal's Dataverse or by supplying a citation to data already in a repository.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.suppFile.publishDataNone"><![CDATA[Treat uploaded file as supplementary file. File <strong>will not</strong> be deposited in Dataverse.]]></message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.suppFile.publishDataDataverse"><![CDATA[Deposit file in Dataverse. Author accepts and agrees to Dataverse <a href="javascript:openWindow('{$dataverseTermsOfUseUrl}');">terms of use</a>.]]></message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.suppFile.publishData.error">Please upload a file to deposit in Dataverse.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.suppFile.dataCitationDescription">The file will be added to the Dataverse study created for this submission:</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.suppFile.studyLocked">This study is locked for processing. No changes can be made to submission data until processing has completed.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.suppFile.externalDataCitation">External Data Citation</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.suppFile.externalDataCitation.description">If the data to be published with this submission is already in a different repository, please provide a data citation.</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.suppFile.externalDataCitation.error">Please upload files to deposit in Dataverse OR provide an external data citation.</message>

	<!-- Terms of use -->
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.termsOfUse.title">Terms Of Use</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.termsOfUse.dataverse">Dataverse</message>

	<!-- Data availality policy -->
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.dataAvailabilityPolicy.title">Data Availability Policy</message>

	<!-- Block plugin -->
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.block.displayName">Dataverse Block Plugin</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.block.title">Veri Atıfı</message>

	<!-- Reading tools: suppfiles -->
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.suppFiles.view">Veri Dizisi Görüntüle</message>

	<!-- Field labels -->
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.dataCitation">Veri atıfı</message>

	<!-- Citation "in press" info -->
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.citationAPA.inPress">(baskıda).</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.suppFile.studyDescription">Çalışma Açıklaması</message>
	<message key="plugins.generic.dataverse.suppFile.studyDescription.description">Çalışma verilerin kapsamı, amacı ve özgünlüğü konusunda özet girin.</message>
</locale>
