<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic SYSTEM "../../../topic.dtd">

<!--
  * 000001.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2007 John Willinsky
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  *
  * Site Administration - Installation 
  *
  * $Id$
  -->

<topic id="site/topic/000001" locale="en_US" title="Installation" toc="site/toc/000000" key="site.installation">
	<section>
		<![CDATA[<p>Open Journal Systems is an open source application that can be freely downloaded and installed on nearly any desktop or server computer.</p>]]>	
	</section>
	
	<section title="License">
		<![CDATA[<p>OJS is distributed under the terms of the <a href="http://www.gnu.org/copyleft/gpl.html" target="_blank">GNU General Public License</a>. A copy of the license terms for redistributing OJS code in original or modified form is included with the OJS download.</p>]]>
	</section>
	
	<section title="System Requirements">
		<![CDATA[<p>A server environment meeting the following requirements is recommended:</p>
		<ul>
			<li><a href="http://www.php.net/" target="_blank">PHP</a> >= 4.2.x</li>
			<li><a href="http://www.mysql.com/" target="_blank">MySQL</a> >= 3.23.23 (including 4.x) or <a href="http://www.postgresql.org/" target="_blank">PostgreSQL</a> >= 7.1 (including
	  PostgreSQL 8.x)</li>
			<li><a href="http://httpd.apache.org/" target="_blank">Apache</a> >= 1.3.2x or >= 2.0.4x or Microsoft IIS 6+</li>
			<li>Operating system: Any OS that supports the above software, including <a href="http://www.linux.org/" target="_blank">Linux</a>, <a href="http://www.bsd.org/" target="_blank">BSD</a>, <a href="http://www.sun.com/" target="_blank">Solaris</a>, <a href="http://www.apple.com/" target="_blank">Mac OS X</a>, and <a href="http://www.microsoft.com/">Windows</a></li>
		</ul>
		<p>OJS has currently only been tested on MySQL and PostgreSQL, although other database management systems supported by <a href="http://adodb.sourceforge.net/" target="_blank">ADOdb</a> may work (in full or partially). Compatibility reports and/or code patches for alternative DBMSs are welcome.</p>
		]]>
	</section>
	
	<section title="Download">
		<![CDATA[<p>OJS can be downloaded from the Public Knowledge Project <a href="http://pkp.sfu.ca/ojs/" target="_blank">web site</a>.</p>]]>
	</section>
	
	<section title="Installation">
		<![CDATA[<p>OJS comes with a web-based installation script that guides the system administrator through the installation process. Alternately, a command-line installation tool is available.</p>
		<ol>
			<li>
				Download the OJS archive.
			</li>
			<li>
				Decompress the OJS archive on your web server and place it in the desired location in your web documents tree:<br />
				<tt>$ tar -zxf ojs-2.*.tar.gz<br />
				$ mv ojs-* /var/www/myjournal</tt>
			</li>
			<li>
				Make the following files and directories writable (i.e., using chown or chmod):<br />
				- config.inc.php (optional)<br />
				- public<br />
				- cache<br />
				- cache/t_cache<br />
				- cache/t_config<br />
				- cache/t_compile<br />
				- cache/_db
			</li>
			<li>
				Open a web browser to the location of your OJS installation (e.g., http://www.mydomain.com/myjournal/) and follow the on-screen instructions to complete the install. See docs/README for more information on the installation process.
			</li>
		</ol>
		]]>
	</section>
</topic>
