<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic SYSTEM "../../../../lib/pkp/dtd/helpTopic.dtd">

<!--
  * 000006.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2011 John Willinsky
  * Distribuido por GNU GPL v2. Para términos completos vea el archivo docs/COPYING.
  *
  * Administarción de páginas - Correos preparados 
  *
  * Translated by Juan Arias, Corporación Parque Tecnológico de Mérida: juanarias@ula.ve.
  *
  * $Id$
  -->

<topic id="journal/topic/000006" locale="es_ES" title="Correos preparados" toc="journal/toc/000001" key="journal.managementPages.emails">
	<section>
		<![CDATA[<p>La revista utiliza una variedad de correos electrónicos preparados para dirigir los procesos de editorial y publicación. Todos los correos están dirigidos a los recipiente(s) adecuado(s) de antemano (por ejemplo, el editor de la sección notifica al editor de correción de textos que que la correción de textos de una entrega puede comenzar). El adiminitrador de la revista puede editar versiones defectuosas de estos correos(disponibles bajo correos electrónicos en la página de administración de la revista). De igual manera, los correos pueden editarse por el usuario antes de ser enviados. Automaticamente, el sistema inserta cualquier información relevante y especifica dentro de la prioridad del correo antes de presentárlo al usuario para enviar (por ejemplo, el título y el resúmen del envío en cuestión o la fecha de entrega de la revisión). El correo también le informa al recipiente sobre las instrucciones para encontrar la página Web pertinente, para que pueda hacer la tarea que se le solicita realizar.</p>]]>	
	</section>
	
	<section title="Sending Emails">
		<![CDATA[<p>OJS uses email to coordinate the functioning of the editorial and publishing process. All of the prepared emails have default versions, which come up each time the relevant email icon is clicked. The default emails can edited by the Journal Manager at any point. As well, an email can be edited by the sender prior to mailing it. When an email icon is clicked, it will have the intended recipient automatically filled in, along with all of the pertinent information needed for the editorial or publishing function. The sender can add comments or further direction, as needed. The sender can alter the recipient's email address and additional recipients, except in those cases that involve the sending of passwords (for security reasons). Note that correcting a recipient's address does not alter the email address listed on their Profile page in this system. Correcting the recipient's email address on a permanent basis for this system requires notifying the Journal Manager, who has the authority to make such changes to users' profiles.</p>]]>
	</section>
</topic>
