<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE version SYSTEM "../rt-version.dtd">

<!--
  * Business.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2005 The Public Knowledge Project
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  *
  * Reading Tools version: Business (en_US)
  *
  * $Id$
  -->

<version id="Business" locale="en_US">
	<version_title>Business</version_title>
	<version_description>The Reading Tools can help readers of this study consult a wide range of related resources that can provide a context for interpreting, situating and evaluating the study.</version_description>

	<context>
		<context_title>Author's work</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Other Works</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Identify other works by the article's author(s) by using OAI engines.</context_description>
		<author_terms />
		<search>
			<search_title>Google Scholar</search_title>
			<search_description>Google Scholar enables specific searches of scholarly literature, including peer-reviewed papers, theses, books, pre-prints, abstracts, and technical reports. Content includes a range of publishers and aggregators with whom Google already has standing arrangements, e.g., the Association for Computing Machinery, IEEE, OCLC's Open WorldCat library locator service, etc. Result displays will show different version clusters, citation analysis, and library location (currently books only).</search_description>
			<url>http://scholar.google.com</url>
			<search_url>http://scholar.google.com/scholar?ie=UTF-8&amp;oe=UTF-8&amp;hl=eng&amp;as_sauthors={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>OAIster (Open Archives Initiative research databases)</search_title>
			<search_description>OAIster is a project of the University of Michigan Digital Library Production Services, and provides searching a wide variety of collections from a wide variety of institutions. These institutions have made the records of their digital resources available to access, and the project team has gathered and aggregated them into the OAIster service.</search_description>
			<url>http://oaister.umdl.umich.edu/</url>
			<search_url>http://oaister.umdl.umich.edu/cgi/b/bib/bib-idx?type=boolean&amp;size=10&amp;c=oaister&amp;q1=&amp;rgn1=entire+record&amp;op2=and&amp;q2=&amp;rgn2=entire+record&amp;op3=And&amp;q3=&amp;rgn3=title&amp;op4=And&amp;rgn4=author&amp;op5=And&amp;q5=&amp;rgn5=subject&amp;op6=And&amp;rgn6=norm&amp;q6=all+types&amp;sort=author%2Fcreator&amp;submit2=search&amp;q4={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Public Knowledge Project Open Archives Harvester</search_title>
			<search_description>The PKP Open Archives Harvester is a free metadata indexing system developed by the Public Knowledge Project through its federally funded efforts to expand and improve access to research. The PKP OAI Harvester allows you to create a searchable index of the metadata from Open Archives Initiative-compliant archives, such as sites using Open Journal Systems or Open Conference Systems.</search_description>
			<url>http://pkp.sfu.ca/harvester/</url>
			<search_url>http://pkp.sfu.ca/harvester/search.php?limit=author&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>The Corporate Library</search_title>
			<search_description>The Corporate Library is intended to serve as a central repository for research, study and critical thinking about the nature of the modern global corporation, with a special focus on corporate governance and the relationship between company management, their boards and their shareowners. Use this site to retrieve biographies for the companies in the S&amp;P 1500 Supercomposite Index. Screen on a variety of features to identify matching directors (e.g. company name, age, attendance problems, # shares held, etc.) The site also contains research reports on trends in corporate governance.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.thecorporatelibrary.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://thecorporatelibrary.master.com/texis/master/search/?s=SS&amp;q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Find articles</search_title>
			<search_description>Provides citations, abstracts and fulltext articles for over 300 magazines and journals on topics such as business, health, society, entertainment and sports.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.findarticles.com/PI/index.jhtml</url>
			<search_url>http://www.findarticles.com/cf_0/PI/search.jhtml?magR=all+magazines&amp;key={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Social Science Information Gateway</search_title>
			<search_description>Social Science Information Gateway provides selected Internet information in the social sciences, business, and law.</search_description>
			<url>http://sosig.ac.uk/</url>
			<search_url>http://sosig.ac.uk/roads/cgi-bin/search.pl?attrib1=Author-Name&amp;boolean=and&amp;ranking=on&amp;referrals=on&amp;stemming=on&amp;maxserver=8&amp;method=any&amp;view=batched&amp;bsize=10&amp;categories=on&amp;templatetype=all&amp;highlight=on&amp;database=SOSIG+ZPlugin&amp;x=11&amp;y=13&amp;term1={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Brint.com</search_title>
			<search_description>Extensive information portal with news, analysis and links related to business, commerce, economics, information technology, and information resources.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.brint.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://portal.brint.com/cgi-bin/search.cgi?PA={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Book</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Book</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Book-related Resources</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Google Print</search_title>
			<search_description>Google is working with libraries at the University of Michigan, Harvard University, Stanford University, Oxford University and the New York Public Library to digitize books in their collections and make them accessible via Google Print, a massive scanning project that will bring millions of volumes of printed books into the Google Print database.  Click a book title and you'll see the page of the book that has your search terms, your can search for more information within that specific book, find reviews, find related information, learn about the publisher, buy this book, and find nearby libraries that have it.</search_description>
			<url>http://print.google.com</url>
			<search_url>http://print.google.com/print?q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Online books Page</search_title>
			<search_description>Online books Page, edited by John Mark Ockerbloom, at the University of Pennsylvania.  This is an excellent starting point in the search for full-text books on the Internet. Over 20,000 English works in various formats available online at different sites. Entries may be searched by author or title. An interesting feature allows browsing by Library of Congress call number categories. New listings are added regularly and are listed on a separate web page at &lt;a href=&quot;http://onlinebooks.library.upenn.edu/new.html&quot;&gt;http://onlinebooks.library.upenn.edu/new.html&lt;/a&gt;.</search_description>
			<url>http://digital.library.upenn.edu/books/</url>
			<search_url>http://onlinebooks.library.upenn.edu/webbin/book/search?tmode=words&amp;title={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Books-On-Line</search_title>
			<search_description>A collection of over 32935 titles, although some are only excerpts. Browse by subject or search by author or title. Not all items are free.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.books-on-line.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.books-on-line.com/bol/KeyWordSearch.cfm?RowCount=50&amp;Searchquery={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Universal Library</search_title>
			<search_description>The Universal Library is considerably more involved, and more ambitious -- it has amassed a collection of 100,000 e-books (some of them from Project Gutenberg), and is aiming for 1 million e-books by the end of 2006.</search_description>
			<url>http://tera-3.ul.cs.cmu.edu/</url>
			<search_url>http://tera-3.ul.cs.cmu.edu/cgi-bin/DBscripts/advsearch_db.cgi?perPage=25&amp;listStart=0&amp;author1=&amp;subject1=Any&amp;year1=&amp;year2=&amp;language1=Any&amp;scentre=Any&amp;search=Search&amp;title1={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Definitions</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Definitions</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Double click on any word in the text and it will appear in the &quot;Definition of terms&quot; box.  You can also type or paste a word into the box.  Then use the search function to find a definition for the word.  These resources have been selected because of their relevance and their open (free) access to all or part of their contents.</context_description>
		<define_terms />
		<search>
			<search_title>Google</search_title>
			<search_description>Search for definitions using the popular Google search engine.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.google.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=define%3A{$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Online Dictionary of the Social Sciences</search_title>
			<search_description>Online Dictionary of the Social Sciences is a searchable dictionary of terms commonly used in the social sciences. Both phrase and keyword searches are facilitated.</search_description>
			<url>http://bitbucket.icaap.org/</url>
			<search_url>http://bitbucket.icaap.org/dict.pl?definition={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Merriam-Webster Online</search_title>
			<search_description>A dictionary based on the Webster 10th Collegiate edition, 1993, with updates added annually. More than 160,000 entries. Each word is accompanied by definition, pronunciation, usage, grammatical function, and a brief etymology. Includes a thesaurus. Misspellings return suggested spellings. The dictionary's search system supports internal wildcards and right hand truncation searching. Includes an extensive pronunciation guide and sound files for the pronunciation of many terms.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.merriam-webster.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.merriam-webster.com/cgi-bin/dictionary?book=Dictionary&amp;va={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>OneLook Dictionaries</search_title>
			<search_description>OneLook is a meta-dictionary. Enter an English language 
word or acronym, and OneLook will search its index of 5,292,362 words in 934 
dictionaries indexed in general and special interest dictionaries for the 
definition.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.onelook.com/index.html</url>
			<search_url>http://www.onelook.com/?ls=a&amp;w={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Wikipedia: The Free Encyclopedia</search_title>
			<search_description>&quot;Wikipedia is a free content encyclopedia that is being written collaboratively by contributors from all around the world. The site is a WikiWiki, meaning that anyone ... can edit any article. ...&quot; Without editorial oversight, the quality of the content on this site varies dramatically, but it is worth exploring. The English version has hundreds of thousands of entries. Spanish, French, and Esperanto are among the several other languages offered.</search_description>
			<url>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Main_Page</url>
			<search_url>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Special:Search?go=Go&amp;fulltext=Search&amp;search={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Infoplease.com</search_title>
			<search_description>This site includes contents of the Information Please Almanacs, a biography database, a dictionary, an atlas, and articles from the Columbia Encyclopedia. You can search these ready reference works together or separately or browse the Almanacs. There are feature stories each week covering topics in the news, with links to pertinent Almanac content and other Web resources.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.infoplease.com</url>
			<search_url>http://www.infoplease.com/search?fr=iptn&amp;in=all&amp;x=0&amp;y=0&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Find places</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Find places</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Search for locations relating to the article.</context_description>
		<geo_terms />
		<search>
			<search_title>Google Maps</search_title>
			<search_description>Search for locations using the popular Google search engine's mapping features.</search_description>
			<url>http://maps.google.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://maps.google.com/maps?hl=en&amp;q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Related studies</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Related studies</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Access to related studies by establishing a working link with an open-access (free) database, with abstracts and/or full texts related to your topic.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>The Corporate Library</search_title>
			<search_description>The Corporate Library is intended to serve as a central repository for research, study and critical thinking about the nature of the modern global corporation, with a special focus on corporate governance and the relationship between company management, their boards and their shareowners. Use this site to retrieve biographies for the companies in the S&amp;P 1500 Supercomposite Index. Screen on a variety of features to identify matching directors (e.g. company name, age, attendance problems, # shares held, etc.) The site also contains research reports on trends in corporate governance.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.thecorporatelibrary.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://thecorporatelibrary.master.com/texis/master/search/?s=SS&amp;q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Find articles</search_title>
			<search_description>Provides citations, abstracts and fulltext articles for over 300 magazines and journals on topics such as business, health, society, entertainment and sports.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.findarticles.com/PI/index.jhtml</url>
			<search_url>http://www.findarticles.com/cf_0/PI/search.jhtml?magR=all+magazines&amp;key={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Social Science Information Gateway</search_title>
			<search_description>Social Science Information Gateway provides selected Internet information in the social sciences, business, and law.</search_description>
			<url>http://sosig.ac.uk/</url>
			<search_url>http://sosig.ac.uk/roads/cgi-bin/search.pl?attrib1=ANY&amp;boolean=and&amp;ranking=on&amp;referrals=on&amp;stemming=on&amp;maxserver=8&amp;method=any&amp;view=batched&amp;bsize=10&amp;categories=on&amp;templatetype=all&amp;highlight=on&amp;database=SOSIG+ZPlugin&amp;x=11&amp;y=13&amp;term1={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Portals</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Portals</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Offer an entry point to other websites.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Brint.com</search_title>
			<search_description>Extensive information portal with news, analysis and links related to business, commerce, economics, information technology, and information resources.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.brint.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://portal.brint.com/cgi-bin/search.cgi?PA={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>SMEALSearch</search_title>
			<search_description>SMEALSearch is a publicly available vertical digital library and search engine hosted at Penn State's Smeal College of Business that focuses on academic business documents. SmealSearch crawls the web and harvests, catalogs, and indexes academic business documents. It is based on the computer and information science engine, CiteSeer, initially developed at NEC Research Institute by Kurt Bollacker, Lee Giles and Steve Lawrence. The search engine crawls websites of academia, commerce, research institutes, government agencies, etc. for academic business documents, including published articles, working papers, white papers, consulting reports, etc. For certain documents, SmealSearch only indexes and stores the hyperlinks to those documents. SMEALSearch generates a citation analysis for all the academic articles harvested and ranks them in order of their citation rates (the most cited articles are listed first) similar to the ranking of CiteSeer and the Google Scholar.</search_description>
			<url>http://gunther.smeal.psu.edu/SMEALSearchAbout.html</url>
			<search_url>http://gunther.smeal.psu.edu/cs?submit=Search+Documents&amp;q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Roubini Global Economics (RGE) Montor</search_title>
			<search_description>Includes daily economic analysis for individual countries, and information on emerging markets, financial markets, banking, and other topics. Contains original content and links to government and news sources. Searchable.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.rgemonitor.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.rgemonitor.com/?option=com_content&amp;task=search&amp;kwd={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Pay-per-view</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Pay-per-view</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>A pay-per-view service is for those who do not have direct access to electronic journal articles via subscriptions. The service allows customers to gain direct access to an article by paying by credit card using the RSC's secure payment mechanism. Immediately the payment details have been validated, the customer can gain access to the required article file for a period of 30 days.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Ingenta</search_title>
			<search_description>Ingenta restricts access to full text articles. Although access to the full text costs money, the site can be used as a free index.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.ingenta.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.ingenta.com/isis/searching/Search/ingenta?database=1&amp;title={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>ebrary</search_title>
			<search_description>Independent researchers who do not have access to ebrary_ databases through their library may now set up an individual account for as little as $5. ebrary Discover spans multiple academic disciplines and provides anytime, anywhere access to over 20,000 authoritative titles including books in full-text, sheet music, reports and other authoritative documents from more than 175 leading publishers such as Cambridge University Press, Random House, Inc., and The McGraw-Hill Companies.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.ebrary.com/company/</url>
			<search_url>http://shop.ebrary.com/Top?layout=search&amp;f00=text&amp;p01=&amp;f01=subject&amp;d=journal&amp;l=en&amp;sch=%A0%A0%A0%A0%A0Search%A0%A0%A0%A0%A0&amp;frm=adv.x&amp;p00={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Questia</search_title>
			<search_description>Questia provides access to over 47,000 books and 375,000 journal, magazine, and newspaper articles. All books and articles are available in their entirety - search every page.  The subscription rate is ranging from 19.05 per month to 119.95 per year.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.questia.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.questia.com/SM.qst?act=search&amp;keywordsSearchType=1000&amp;mediaType=book&amp;mediaType=journal&amp;mediaType=magazine&amp;mediaType=newspaper&amp;mediaType=encyclopedia&amp;mediaType=startpage&amp;keywords={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Wiley InterScience Pay-per-view Service</search_title>
			<search_description>Wiley InterScience Pay-per-view affords instant, full-text access to an extensive collection of journal articles or book chapters available on Wiley InterScience without the need for a subscription. This service allows anyone to purchase access to individual journal articles or book chapters directly by using a credit card. Access is instant and available for 24 hours.</search_description>
			<url>http://www3.interscience.wiley.com/aboutus/ppv-articleselect.html</url>
			<search_url>http://www3.interscience.wiley.com/search/allsearch</search_url>
			<search_post>allContentSearchForm=&amp;mode=quicksearch&amp;WISindexid1=WISall&amp;WISsearch1={$formKeywords}</search_post>			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>e-Journals</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>e-Journals</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Provide pop-up window for entering open-access and full-text e-Journals relevant to your field.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Business Week</search_title>
			<search_description>Business Week's Web site provides the full text of the current issue, plus selected articles from earlier editions. There is also a searchable archive covering three years of articles from the print magazine, although charges apply for retrieving the full articles. Other features include updated news in the Daily Briefing section and BW Plus!, offering archive articles and other content on such topics as the computer industry, women in business, and business book reviews.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.businessweek.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://search.businessweek.com/search97cgi/s97_cgi?action=FilterSearch&amp;ServerKey=Primary&amp;filter=bwfilt.hts&amp;command=GetMenu&amp;ResultMaxDocs=500&amp;ResultCount=25&amp;resulttemplate=bwarchiv.hts&amp;querytext={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>businesswire.com</search_title>
			<search_description>Offers company press releases, searchable by company name, industry, region, or keyword/concept. Each company's releases are broken down by topic, i.e., earnings, management changes, mergers/acquisitions, products, etc.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.businesswire.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://home.businesswire.com/portal/site/home/?epi_menuItemID=e23d7f2be635f4725e0fa455c6908a0c&amp;epi_menuID=887566059a3aedb6efaaa9e27a808a0c&amp;epi_baseMenuID=384979e8cc48c441ef0130f5c6908a0c&amp;searchHereRadio=false&amp;ndmHsc=v2*A0*J2*L1*N-1002313*Z{$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Fortune</search_title>
			<search_description>Fortune magazine's Web site offers the full text of the print publication back to September 1995, plus links to special features like the Fortune 500, Best Cities for Business, Investor's Guide, and others.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.fortune.com/fortune/</url>
			<search_url>http://search.money.cnn.com/pages/search.jsp?Coll=moneymag_xml&amp;QuerySubmit=true&amp;Page=1&amp;LastQuery=&amp;magazine=fort&amp;QueryText={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>The McKinsey Quarterly</search_title>
			<search_description>The McKinsey Quarterly, a unique print and online publication published by McKinsey &amp; Company, the leading global management consultancy, has long been a trusted source of strategic thinking, industry scenarios, and real-world market analysis.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.mckinseyquarterly.com/home.aspx</url>
			<search_url>http://www.mckinseyquarterly.com/search_result.aspx?search_query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Inc.com</search_title>
			<search_description>Inc.com, the website for Inc. magazine, delivers advice, tools, and services, to help business owners and CEOs start, run, and grow their businesses more successfully.  Inc. magazine archives date back to 1988 and are fully searchable. Site also features products, services, and online tools for virtually every business or management task.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.inc.com/home/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.inc.com/cgi-bin/finder.cgi?query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Business Finance Magazine</search_title>
			<search_description>Trade magazine for finance executives. Subject areas include Budgeting &amp; Reporting; Cost Management; Performance Management; Risk Management; E-Business; Technology &amp; Software; more. Also includes full article archives; Webcasts; Salary Central; an events &amp; vendor directory; Web links; Research Reports; e-Newsletters. Visitors can participate in a regularly updated slate of research projects.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.businessfinancemag.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.businessfinancemag.com/site/search/search.cfm?site=BF&amp;qs={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Databases</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Databases</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Provide access to open-access abstract and/or full-text databases.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Free EDGAR database of corporate information</search_title>
			<search_description>EDGAR, the Electronic Data Gathering, Analysis, and Retrieval system, performs automated collection, validation, indexing, acceptance, and forwarding of submissions by companies and others who are required by law to file forms with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC).</search_description>
			<url>http://sec.freeedgar.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://sec.freeedgar.com/resultsCompanies.asp?searchfrom=new&amp;searchtype=name&amp;x=27&amp;y=3&amp;searchvalue={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>ThomasRegister</search_title>
			<search_description>&quot;Free access to: over 168,000 companies; 68,000 product and service categories; thousands of online suppliers catalogs and web site links; over 2 million line items available for secvure online ordering; and, over 1 million downloadable CAD drawings.&quot;</search_description>
			<url>http://www.thomasregister.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.thomasnet.com/prodsearch.html?cov=NA&amp;which=prod&amp;navsec=search&amp;what={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Microsoft Investor</search_title>
			<search_description>Microsoft's investor information page -- free. Has links to information on all of the companies that it covers.</search_description>
			<url>http://moneycentral.msn.com/investor/home.asp</url>
			<search_url>http://moneycentral.msn.com/money.search?q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>BPubs.com</search_title>
			<search_description>Business Publications Search Engine</search_description>
			<url>http://www.bpubs.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.bpubs.com/cgi/search.cgi?bool=or&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Global Edge</search_title>
			<search_description>International business information include Country Insights' information on all countries, along with extensive links to research resources.</search_description>
			<url>http://globaledge.msu.edu/ibrd/ibrd.asp</url>
			<search_url>http://globaledge.msu.edu/ibrd/busresmain.asp?search=1&amp;SearchTerms={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Bond Markets Online</search_title>
			<search_description>Bond Market Association, association for bond market professionals, provides information and education resources for bond market professionals that underwrite, trade and sell debt securities. Includes policy issues, advocacy, news, research and statistics for bond professionals and investors.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.bondmarkets.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.bondmarkets.com/search/search.pl?nocpp=1&amp;Match=1&amp;Realm=bondmarkets&amp;sort-method=1&amp;Terms={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>TaxLinks</search_title>
			<search_description>A link and data aggregator focusing on tax payers and tax professionals. Its strength lies in its free databases of IRS Revenue Rulings since 1960 and Revenue Procedures since 1995. TaxLinks links up with tax sites above. Again, the content of the databases may not be totally complete, but they're free and easily accessible from the home page.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.taxlinks.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.taxlinks.com/_vti_bin/shtml.dll/search.htm</search_url>
			<search_post>VTI-GROUP=0&amp;search={$formKeywords}</search_post>			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Hoover's Online! Company Info</search_title>
			<search_description>Databases of information on tens of thousands of the largest or fastest-growing public and private U.S. companies. Information provided includes company address, number of employees, key people, financial data, news items and selected Web links to company Web site, SEC filings, and current stock prices. Some information is fee-based, but quite a bit of content is still freely available.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.hoovers.com/free/?abforward=true</url>
			<search_url>http://www.hoovers.com/free/search/simple/xmillion/index.xhtml?page=1&amp;which=company&amp;query_string={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Online forums</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Online forums</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Choose online, open-access online forums that would enrich the context of the research studies on your site.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>H-Net Humanities and Social Sciences Online</search_title>
			<search_description>H-Net Humanities and Social Sciences Online provides information and resources for all those interested in the Humanities and Social Sciences.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.h-net.msu.edu/</url>
			<search_url>http://www2.h-net.msu.edu/cgi-bin/htsearch?config=&amp;restrict=&amp;exclude=&amp;method=and&amp;format=builtin-long&amp;sort=score&amp;words={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Liszt</search_title>
			<search_description>Liszt, hosted by Topica, is a free service that allows you to find, manage and participate in email lists and discussion groups in business.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.liszt.com/dir/?cid=2</url>
			<search_url>http://www.liszt.com/search/?search_type=cat&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>MInd: the Meetings Index</search_title>
			<search_description>Use this service to identify and locate the organizers and sponsors for future conferences, congresses, meetings and symposia, as well as conference proceedings (for future and past conferences).</search_description>
			<url>http://www.interdok.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.google.com/search?q=site%3Ainterdok.com+mind+{$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>TechCalendar</search_title>
			<search_description>TechCalendar is a searchable/browseable event directory, with categories such as: Internet/Online, Communications, Software &amp; Services, Vertical Markets, Computing Platforms, and Computing Industry.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.techweb.com/calendar/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.tsnn.com/partner/results/results_techweb.cfm?city=&amp;select=-1&amp;country=-1&amp;classid=0&amp;Month=-1&amp;subject={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Government policy</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Gov Policy</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Access to Information and services gateway run by the Government of the United States and Canada.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Access to Australian Government Information and Services</search_title>
			<search_description>The Australian Government Entry Point offers comprehensive and integrated access to Australian Government information and services.  You will find a concentrated body of Australian Government information through this site. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.australia.gov.au&quot;&gt;www.australia.gov.au&lt;/a&gt; currently signposts over 700 Australian Government web sites, indexes more than 5,000,000 pages and uses both metadata and full text indexing to ensure it is a comprehensive government portal.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.fed.gov.au</url>
			<search_url>http://govsearch.australia.gov.au/search/search.cgi?collection=gov&amp;form=au&amp;query=&amp;query_phrase=&amp;query_or=&amp;query_not=&amp;meta_f_sand=&amp;scope=&amp;fscope=512&amp;num_ranks=20&amp;chksummary=chksummary&amp;query_and={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Canadian Government Information</search_title>
			<search_description>Includes links to Canadian government libraries, federal documents and news releases, publications catalogues, and provincial governments. Most information is in English, but some of the linked material is in French, or a combination of French and English.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.nlc-bnc.ca/8/4/index-e.html</url>
			<search_url>http://www.collectionscanada.ca/search/006001-110.01-e.php?q%5B1%5D=pagelevel%3A1&amp;q%5B2%5D=&amp;x=15&amp;y=13&amp;q%5B0%5D={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Directgov</search_title>
			<search_description>Directgov is a government service giving people access to the latest and widest range of public service information in one place on the Web and on Digital TV. Directgov uses the specifications formulated and consulted on through UK GovTalk.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.direct.gov.uk</url>
			<search_url>http://www.direct.gov.uk/AdvancedSearch/SearchResults/fs/en?NP=1&amp;PO1=C&amp;PI1=W&amp;PF1=A&amp;PG=1&amp;RP=20&amp;SC=__dgov_site&amp;Z=1&amp;PT1={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Info4local.gov.uk</search_title>
			<search_description>Information for local government from central government.  This site gives local authorities a quick and easy way to find relevant information on the web sites of central government departments, agencies and public bodies. It includes extensive information on implementing electronic government.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.info4local.gov.uk</url>
			<search_url>http://www.info4local.gov.uk/searchresults.asp?formname=frmAdvanced&amp;keywordstype=1&amp;month=&amp;year=&amp;pub=1&amp;news=1&amp;links=1&amp;allsubjects=1&amp;alldepts=1&amp;alldoctypes=1&amp;keywords={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>The New Zealand government portal</search_title>
			<search_description>The New Zealand government portal is a website providing search capability for, and links into the online and offline information and services of most government agencies.  This site is managed and maintained by the State Services Commission, a New Zealand government department.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.govt.nz</url>
			<search_url>http://www.govt.nz/search?type=spider&amp;t=spider&amp;q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Europa</search_title>
			<search_description>Current information on the member countries of the European Union, including statistical data, policies, news, official documents, legal texts, and other publications.</search_description>
			<url>http://europa.eu.int/index_en.htm</url>
			<search_url>http://europa.eu.int/geninfo/query/engine/search/query.pl?action=FilterSearch&amp;filter=europaflt.hts&amp;Collection=fullEUROPA&amp;ResultTemplate=europarslt_ascii.hts&amp;ResultCount=25&amp;ResultMaxDocs=200&amp;DefaultLG=en&amp;ViewTemplate=europaview.hts&amp;QueryText={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>The Global Legal Information Network (GLIN)</search_title>
			<search_description>The Global Legal Information Network (GLIN) is a database of laws, regulations, judicial decisions, and other complementary legal sources contributed by governmental agencies and international organizations. These GLIN members contribute the official full texts of published documents to the database in their original language. Each document is accompanied by a summary in English and subject terms selected from the multilingual index to GLIN.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.glin.gov</url>
			<search_url>http://www.glin.gov/search.do?refineQuery=&amp;offset=0&amp;refineQueryType=&amp;fromSearch=true&amp;queryType=ALL&amp;searchBtn=Search&amp;includeAllFields=on&amp;searchAll=on&amp;sumLanguage=any&amp;pubLanguage=any&amp;pubJurisdiction=any&amp;publicationJurisdictionExclude=false&amp;searchPublicationDate=true&amp;dateFromDay=01&amp;dateFromMonth=01&amp;dateFromYear=&amp;dateToDay=01&amp;dateToMonth=01&amp;dateToYear=&amp;subjTerm=&amp;subjTermConjunction%5B0%5D=AND&amp;subjTerm=&amp;subjTermConjunction%5B1%5D=AND&amp;subjTerm=&amp;subjTermConjunction%5B2%5D=AND&amp;subjTerm=&amp;subjTermConjunction%5B3%5D=AND&amp;subjTerm=&amp;searchOrder=default&amp;hitsPerPage=10&amp;showSummary=on&amp;queryString={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Business.gov</search_title>
			<search_description>Business.gov is  an online resource guide designed to provide legal and regulatory information to America's small businesses. Entrepreneurs can use this gateway to federal, state and local information in order to quickly define their problems and find solutions on topics ranging from federal advertising laws to local zoning codes. In addition to self-help articles, interactive guides, and the ability to complete transactions on line such as applying for a Federal EIN, the site also connects users with sources of in-person help from government officials, attorneys and business counselors in their local area.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.business.gov/</url>
			<search_url>http://search.business.gov/query.html?qt={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Organization for Economic Co-operation and Development</search_title>
			<search_description>The OECD groups 30 member countries sharing a commitment to democratic government and the market economy. With active relationships with some 70 other countries, NGOs and civil society, it has a global reach. Best known for its publications and its statistics, its work covers economic and social issues from macroeconomics, to trade, education, development and science and innovation.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.oecd.org/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.oecd.org/searchResult/0,2665,en_2649_201185_1_1_1_1_1,00.html?fpSearchExact=3&amp;fpSearchText={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>E-Commerce Information from the European Union</search_title>
			<search_description>Statistics, research, and discussion lists.</search_description>
			<url>http://europa.eu.int/information_society/ecowor/ebusiness/index_en.htm</url>
			<search_url>http://europa.eu.int/geninfo/query/engine/search/query.pl?action=FilterSearch&amp;filter=europaflt.hts&amp;collection=fullEUROPA&amp;ResultTemplate=europarslt_ascii.hts&amp;ResultCount=25&amp;ResultMaxDocs=200&amp;DefaultLG=en&amp;ViewTemplate=europaview.hts&amp;QueryText={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Country Studies: Area Handbook Series</search_title>
			<search_description>From the Library of Congress, this site provides extensive information on foreign countries.  The Country Studies Series presents a description and analysis of the historical setting and the social, economic, political, and national security systems and institutions of countries throughout the world.</search_description>
			<url>http://lcweb2.loc.gov/frd/cs/cshome.html</url>
			<search_url>http://search.loc.gov:8765/query.html?col=loc&amp;qp=url%3A%2Frr%2Ffrd%2F&amp;submit.x=11&amp;submit.y=9&amp;qt={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Strategis</search_title>
			<search_description>This site was developed by Industry Canada and provides a searchable database of Canadian companies, business information for each sector, a list of business support services, and a guide to business laws and regulations.  Trade Data Online provides Canadian and US trade data.</search_description>
			<url>http://strategis.ic.gc.ca/engdoc/main.html</url>
			<search_url>http://strategis.ic.gc.ca/cio/search-recherche/search.do?language=eng&amp;V_SEARCH.command=search&amp;searchCriteriaArray%28V_SEARCH__returnedField%29=dc.date.modified&amp;searchCriteriaArray%28V_SEARCH__returnedField%29=site_product_code&amp;searchCriteriaArray%28V_SEARCH__returnedField%29=dc.description&amp;searchCriteriaArray%28V_SEARCH__returnedField%29=description&amp;searchCriteriaArray%28V_SEARCH__returnedField%29=dc.type&amp;searchCriteriaArray%28V_SEARCH__returnedField%29=dc.creator&amp;searchCriteriaArray%28V_SEARCH__returnedField%29=vdksummary&amp;searchCriteria%28V_SEARCH__charMap%29=8859&amp;searchCriteria%28V_SEARCH__resultsJSP%29=%2FsiteResults.do&amp;searchCriteria%28V_SEARCH__customSearchJSP%29=%2FcustomSearch.do&amp;searchCriteria%28V_SEARCH__documentJSP%29=%2Fdocument.do&amp;searchCriteria%28V_SEARCH__locale%29=en_CA&amp;searchCriteria%28V_SEARCH__baseURL%29=search.do&amp;searchCriteria%28V_CUSTOM__searchWithin%29=false&amp;searchCriteria%28V_CUSTOM__collection%29=industry&amp;searchCriteria%28V_CUSTOM__details%29=show&amp;searchCriteria%28V_SEARCH__sortSpec%29=score+desc&amp;searchCriteria%28V_CUSTOM__operator%29=AND&amp;searchCriteria%28V_CUSTOM__column%29=FULLTEXT&amp;searchCriteria%28V_CUSTOM__userInput%29={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>FirstGov</search_title>
			<search_description>FirstGov (U.S. federal and state) is a public-private partnership, led by a cross-agency board.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.firstgov.gov/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.firstgov.gov/fgsearch/index.jsp?db=www-fed-all&amp;st=AS&amp;ms0=should&amp;mt0=all&amp;rn=2&amp;parsed=true&amp;x=5&amp;y=16&amp;mw0={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Canada Sites</search_title>
			<search_description>Canada Sites provides an information and services gateway run by the Government of Canada and each of the provinces.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.canada.gc.ca/main_e.html</url>
			<search_url>http://search-recherche.gc.ca/cgi-bin/query?mss=canada%2Fen%2Fsimple.html&amp;enc=iso88591&amp;pg=q&amp;kl=en&amp;site=main&amp;q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>THOMAS: Legislative Information on the Internet</search_title>
			<search_description>Through Thomas, the Library of Congress offers the text of bills in the United States Congress, the full text of the Congressional Record, House and Senate committee reports, and historical documents.</search_description>
			<url>http://thomas.loc.gov/</url>
			<search_url>http://thomas.loc.gov/cgi-bin/thomas</search_url>
			<search_post>congress=109&amp;database=text&amp;MaxDocs=1000&amp;querytype=phrase&amp;Search=SEARCH&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_post>			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Media reports</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Media reports</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Immediately initiates a search based on the subject of the article or paper that connects users to free current and archival articles in the field from leading newspapers around the world.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Google News</search_title>
			<search_description>Search news reports using the popular search engine Google's news feature.</search_description>
			<url>http://news.google.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://news.google.com/news?hl=en&amp;q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Businesswire</search_title>
			<search_description>Offers company press releases, searchable by company name, industry, region, or keyword/concept. Each company's releases are broken down by topic, i.e., earnings, management changes, mergers/acquisitions, products, etc.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.businesswire.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://home.businesswire.com/portal/site/home/?epi_menuItemID=e23d7f2be635f4725e0fa455c6908a0c&amp;epi_menuID=887566059a3aedb6efaaa9e27a808a0c&amp;epi_baseMenuID=384979e8cc48c441ef0130f5c6908a0c&amp;searchHereRadio=false&amp;ndmHsc=v2*A0*J2*L1*N-1002313*Z{$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Globe and Mail</search_title>
			<search_description>Globe and Mail, Toronto (last seven days)</search_description>
			<url>http://www.globeandmail.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.globeandmail.com/servlet/HTMLTemplate/search?tf=tgam/search/tgam/SearchResults.html&amp;cf=tgam/search/tgam/SearchResults.cfg&amp;current_row=1&amp;start_row=1&amp;num_rows=10&amp;keywords={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Mail &amp; Guardian Newspaper</search_title>
			<search_description>Mail &amp; Guardian Newspaper, South Africa (1994-)</search_description>
			<url>http://www.mg.co.za/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.mg.co.za/mg_search_results.aspx?PrintEdition=PrintEdition&amp;DailyNews=DailyNews&amp;SearchSection=&amp;StartDay=&amp;StartMonth=&amp;StartYear=&amp;EndDay=&amp;EndMonth=&amp;EndYear=&amp;keywords={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>People's Daily</search_title>
			<search_description>People's Daily, China (January 1999-)</search_description>
			<url>http://english.peopledaily.com.cn/</url>
			<search_url>http://english.peopledaily.com.cn/cgi-bin/htsearch?method=boolean&amp;format=builtin-long&amp;sort=score&amp;config=english&amp;exclude=&amp;words={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>National Public Radio</search_title>
			<search_description>National Public Radio, United States (unlimited)</search_description>
			<url>http://www.npr.org/archives/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.npr.org/search.php?text={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>New York Times</search_title>
			<search_description>New York Times, New York (last seven days)</search_description>
			<url>http://www.nytimes.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://query.nytimes.com/search/query?date=site1week&amp;submit.x=1&amp;submit.y=9&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>The Japan Times Online</search_title>
			<search_description>The Japan Times Online, Japan (January 1999-)</search_description>
			<url>http://www.japantimes.co.jp/search.htm</url>
			<search_url>http://search.japantimes.co.jp/cgi-bin/JTsearch4.pl5?term1={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>The Moscow Times</search_title>
			<search_description>The Moscow Times, Russia (1994-)</search_description>
			<url>http://www.moscowtimes.ru/doc/Search.html</url>
			<search_url>http://www.moscowtimes.ru/cgi-bin/search?config=&amp;exclude=&amp;method=and&amp;format=long&amp;sort=score&amp;matchesperpage=10&amp;words={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Washington Post</search_title>
			<search_description>Washington Post, Washington, DC (last two weeks)</search_description>
			<url>http://www.washingtonpost.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.washingtonpost.com/cgi-bin/search99.pl?searchsection=news&amp;searchdatabase=news&amp;x=11&amp;y=8&amp;searchtext={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Newsdirectory</search_title>
			<search_description>Newsdirectory is a comprehensive and searchable guide to the world's English-language online media. Currently over 8,000 newspapers and magazines are listed, as well as more than 1,000 U.S. television broadcasters.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.newsdirectory.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://ask.elibrary.com/search.asp?refid=NEWSD&amp;datetype=all&amp;srcmags=checked&amp;srcnews=checked&amp;srcbooks=checked&amp;srctvrad=checked&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>CNN Finance</search_title>
			<search_description>Headline financial news and markets: keep up with what's going on in the world of finance.</search_description>
			<url>http://cnnfn.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://search.money.cnn.com/pages/search.jsp?QueryText={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Nikkei Business Publications Asia</search_title>
			<search_description>Japan BizTech is a source for technology and business news from Japan and Asia developed by Nikkei Business Publications. It covers the latest news and research breakthroughs in the communications, electronics and computer industries in Japan and other Asian countries. An online directory for technology and business contacts throughout Asia in banking, communications, transport equipment and wholesale is available at the site.</search_description>
			<url>http://neasia.nikkeibp.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://neasia.nikkeibp.com/cgi-bin/search.pl?stype=&amp;lang=eng&amp;b=1&amp;t=1&amp;u=0&amp;alt=1&amp;l=0&amp;default=1&amp;d=0&amp;k=0&amp;au=0&amp;terms={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Web search</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Web search</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Enter a search term for Internet resources through various search engines.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Google</search_title>
			<search_description>Search using the popular Google search engine.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.google.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.google.com/search?q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Google Scholar</search_title>
			<search_description>Google Scholar enables specific searches of scholarly literature, including peer-reviewed papers, theses, books, pre-prints, abstracts, and technical reports. Content includes a range of publishers and aggregators with whom Google already has standing arrangements, e.g., the Association for Computing Machinery, IEEE, OCLC's Open WorldCat library locator service, etc. Result displays will show different version clusters, citation analysis, and library location (currently books only).</search_description>
			<url>http://scholar.google.com</url>
			<search_url>http://scholar.google.com/scholar?ie=UTF-8&amp;oe=UTF-8&amp;hl=en&amp;q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Clusty the Clustering Engine</search_title>
			<search_description>This search tool from Vivismo offers clustered results for a selection of searches.  Metasearch the whole web, or use tabs to search for news, gossip, images, orproducts via Bizrate or eBay.</search_description>
			<url>http://clusty.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://clusty.com/search?query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Vivisimo</search_title>
			<search_description>The award-winning Vivisimo clustering technology, developed by Carnegie Mellon research scientists, is unlocking the value of stored information at Fortune 500 companies, top websites, prestigious publishers and government agencies by categorizing research results on the fly into meaningful orders, thus achieving breakthrough improvement in access to relevant information.</search_description>
			<url>http://vivisimo.com</url>
			<search_url>http://vivisimo.com/search?tb=homepage&amp;v%3Asources=Web&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
</version>
