<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE version SYSTEM "../rt-version.dtd">

<!--
  * Humanities.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2008 John Willinsky
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  *
  * Reading Tools version: Humanities (en_US)
  *
  * $Id$
  -->

<version id="Humanities" locale="en_US">
	<version_title>Humanities</version_title>
	<version_description>The Reading Tools can help readers of this study consult a wide range of related resources that can provide a context for interpreting, situating and evaluating the study.</version_description>

	<context>
		<context_title>Author's work</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Other Works</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Identify other works by the article's author(s) by using OAI engines.</context_description>
		<author_terms />
		<search>
			<search_title>Google Scholar</search_title>
			<search_description>Google Scholar enables specific searches of scholarly literature, including peer-reviewed papers, theses, books, pre-prints, abstracts, and technical reports. Content includes a range of publishers and aggregators with whom Google already has standing arrangements, e.g., the Association for Computing Machinery, IEEE, OCLC's Open WorldCat library locator service, etc. Result displays will show different version clusters, citation analysis, and library location (currently books only).</search_description>
			<url>http://scholar.google.com</url>
			<search_url>http://scholar.google.com/scholar?ie=UTF-8&amp;oe=UTF-8&amp;hl=eng&amp;as_sauthors={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Intute: Arts &amp; Humanities</search_title>
			<search_description>Intute: Arts &amp; Humanities is a free online service providing you with access to the best Web resources for education and research, selected and evaluated by a network of subject specialists. There are over 18,000 Web resources listed here that are freely available by keyword searching and browsing.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.intute.ac.uk/artsandhumanities/ejournals.html</url>
			<search_url>http://www.intute.ac.uk/artsandhumanities/cgi-bin/search.pl?submit.x=0&amp;submit.y=0&amp;submit=Go&amp;limit=0&amp;subject=artsandhumanities&amp;term1={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>OAIster (Open Archives Initiative research databases)</search_title>
			<search_description>OAIster is a project of the University of Michigan Digital Library Production Services, and provides searching a wide variety of collections from a wide variety of institutions. These institutions have made the records of their digital resources available to access, and the project team has gathered and aggregated them into the OAIster service.</search_description>
			<url>http://oaister.umdl.umich.edu/</url>
			<search_url>http://oaister.umdl.umich.edu/cgi/b/bib/bib-idx?type=boolean&amp;size=10&amp;c=oaister&amp;q1=&amp;rgn1=entire+record&amp;op2=and&amp;q2=&amp;rgn2=entire+record&amp;op3=And&amp;q3=&amp;rgn3=title&amp;op4=And&amp;rgn4=author&amp;op5=And&amp;q5=&amp;rgn5=subject&amp;op6=And&amp;rgn6=norm&amp;q6=all+types&amp;sort=author%2Fcreator&amp;submit2=search&amp;q4={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Public Knowledge Project Open Archives Harvester</search_title>
			<search_description>The PKP Open Archives Harvester is a free metadata indexing system developed by the Public Knowledge Project through its federally funded efforts to expand and improve access to research. The PKP OAI Harvester allows you to create a searchable index of the metadata from Open Archives Initiative-compliant archives, such as sites using Open Journal Systems or Open Conference Systems.</search_description>
			<url>http://pkp.sfu.ca/harvester/</url>
			<search_url>http://pkp.sfu.ca/harvester/search.php?limit=author&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Anthropological index</search_title>
			<search_description>The Anthropological Index is a regionally arranged subject and author index to periodical articles in all areas of anthropology. It is produced by the Museum of Mankind Library.</search_description>
			<url>http://aio.anthropology.org.uk/cgi-bin/uncgi/search_bib_ai/anthind_short</url>
			<search_url>http://aio.anthropology.org.uk/cgi-bin/uncgi/search_bib_ai/anthind_short</search_url>
			<search_post>Default_Years=#1957#1958#1959#1960#1961#1962#1963#1964#1965#1966#1967#1968#1969#1970#1971#1972#1973#1974#1975#1976#1977#1978#1979#1980#1981#1982#1983#1984#1985#1986#1987#1988#1989#1990#1991#1992#1993#1994#1995#1996#1997#1998#1999#2000#2001#2002#2003#2004#2005#Recent&amp;Year=Recent&amp;Text_w=&amp;Text=&amp;Author_w=&amp;Subject1=&amp;Subject2=&amp;Subject3=&amp;Email=You@whereever.edu&amp;Refer=on&amp;Author={$formKeywords}</search_post>			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>The English Server</search_title>
			<search_description>The English Server contains humanities texts online with over 18,000 works, covering history, race, art &amp; architecture, government and other topics.</search_description>
			<url>http://eserver.org/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.google.com/u/EServer?q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>IATH: Institute for Advanced Technology in the Humanities</search_title>
			<search_description>IATH: Institute for Advanced Technology in the Humanities, from the University of Virginia at Charlottesville, provides access to web-based humanities research archives and reports, essays, and the current issue of Postmodern Culture, the Internet's oldest peer-reviewed electronic journal in the humanities.</search_description>
			<url>http://jefferson.village.virginia.edu/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.google.com/u/iath?sa=Google+Search+of+IATH&amp;domains=village.virginia.edu&amp;sitesearch=village.virginia.edu&amp;q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>The Online books Page</search_title>
			<search_description>The Online books Page is the most comprehensive website that facilitates access to books that are freely readable over the Internet.</search_description>
			<url>http://digital.library.upenn.edu/books/</url>
			<search_url>http://onlinebooks.library.upenn.edu/webbin/book/search?amode=words&amp;tmode=words&amp;title=&amp;author={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Perseus Digital Library</search_title>
			<search_description>Perseus Digital library is designed to be resources for the study of the ancient world. Originally begun with coverage of the Archaic and Classical Greek world, has now expanded to Latin text and tools, Renaissance materials, and Papyri. Contains hundreds of texts by the major ancient authors and lexica and morphological databases and catalog entries for over 2,800 vases, sculptures, coins, buildings, and sites, including over 13,000 photographs of such objects.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.perseus.tufts.edu/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.perseus.tufts.edu/cgi-bin/vor?x=22&amp;y=15&amp;lookup={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Voice of the Shuttle</search_title>
			<search_description>Voice of the Shuttle emphasizes both primary and secondary (or theoretical) resources of American literature, including links of syllabi, electronic journals and newsgroups.</search_description>
			<url>http://vos.ucsb.edu/</url>
			<search_url>http://vos.ucsb.edu/search-results.asp?Submit=Go&amp;search={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Look up terms</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Look up terms</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Double click on any word in the text and it will appear in the &quot;Definition of terms&quot; box. You can also type or paste a word into the box. Then use the search function to find a definition for the word. These resources have been selected because of their relevance and their open (free) access to all or part of their contents.</context_description>
		<define_terms />
		<search>
			<search_title>Google</search_title>
			<search_description>Search for definitions using the popular Google search engine.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.google.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=define%3A{$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Merriam-Webster Online</search_title>
			<search_description>A dictionary based on the Webster 10th Collegiate edition, 1993, with updates added annually. More than 160,000 entries. Each word is accompanied by definition, pronunciation, usage, grammatical function, and a brief etymology. Includes a thesaurus. Misspellings return suggested spellings. The dictionary's search system supports internal wildcards and right hand truncation searching. Includes an extensive pronunciation guide and sound files for the pronunciation of many terms.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.merriam-webster.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.merriam-webster.com/cgi-bin/dictionary?book=Dictionary&amp;va={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Wikipedia: The Free Encyclopedia</search_title>
			<search_description>&quot;Wikipedia is a free content encyclopedia that is being written collaboratively by contributors from all around the world. The site is a WikiWiki, meaning that anyone ... can edit any article. ...&quot; Without editorial oversight, the quality of the content on this site varies dramatically, but it is worth exploring. The English version has hundreds of thousands of entries. Spanish, French, and Esperanto are among the several other languages offered.</search_description>
			<url>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Main_Page</url>
			<search_url>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Special:Search?go=Go&amp;fulltext=Search&amp;search={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Infoplease.com</search_title>
			<search_description>This site includes contents of the Information Please Almanacs, a biography database, a dictionary, an atlas, and articles from the Columbia Encyclopedia. You can search these ready reference works together or separately or browse the Almanacs. There are feature stories each week covering topics in the news, with links to pertinent Almanac content and other Web resources.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.infoplease.com</url>
			<search_url>http://www.infoplease.com/search?fr=iptn&amp;in=all&amp;x=0&amp;y=0&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>The Internet Encyclopedia of Philosophy</search_title>
			<search_description>This encyclopedia contains articles adapted from public domain sources, adaptations of material written by the editor for classroom purposes, and original contributions by professional philosophers around the Internet.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.utm.edu/research/iep/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;lr=&amp;q=site%3Awww.utm.edu%2Fresearch%2Fiep%2F+{$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Stanford Encyclopedia of Philosophy</search_title>
			<search_description>Stanford Encyclopedia of Philosophy is a searchable encyclopedia of philosophy providing in-depth explanations for terms.</search_description>
			<url>http://plato.stanford.edu/</url>
			<search_url>http://plato.stanford.edu/cgi-bin/webglimpse.cgi?nonascii=on&amp;errors=0&amp;maxfiles=50&amp;maxlines=30&amp;maxchars=10000&amp;ID=1&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>OneLook Dictionaries</search_title>
			<search_description>OneLook is a meta-dictionary. Enter an English language word or acronym, and OneLook will search its index of 5,292,362 words in 934 dictionaries indexed in general and special interest dictionaries for the definition.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.onelook.com/index.html</url>
			<search_url>http://www.onelook.com/?ls=a&amp;w={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>WordNet</search_title>
			<search_description>WordNet, an electronic lexical database, is considered to be the most important resource available to researchers in computational linguistics, text analysis, and many related areas. Its design is inspired by current psycholinguistic and computational theories of human lexical memory. English nouns, verbs, adjectives, and adverbs are organized into synonym sets, each representing one underlying lexicalized concept. Different relations link the synonym sets.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.cogsci.princeton.edu/~wn/</url>
			<search_url>http://wordnet.princeton.edu/perl/webwn?sub=Search+WordNet&amp;o2=&amp;o0=1&amp;o7=&amp;o5=&amp;o1=1&amp;o6=&amp;o4=&amp;o3=&amp;h=&amp;s={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Gov't policy</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Gov't policy</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Check various government resources.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Access to Australian Government Information and Services</search_title>
			<search_description>The Australian Government Entry Point offers comprehensive and integrated access to Australian Government information and services.  You will find a concentrated body of Australian Government information through this site. &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.australia.gov.au&quot;&gt;www.australia.gov.au&lt;/a&gt; currently signposts over 700 Australian Government web sites, indexes more than 5,000,000 pages and uses both metadata and full text indexing to ensure it is a comprehensive government portal.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.fed.gov.au</url>
			<search_url>http://govsearch.australia.gov.au/search/search.cgi?collection=gov&amp;form=au&amp;query=&amp;query_phrase=&amp;query_or=&amp;query_not=&amp;meta_f_sand=&amp;scope=&amp;fscope=512&amp;num_ranks=20&amp;chksummary=chksummary&amp;query_and={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Government of Canada Publicatons</search_title>
			<search_description>The Government of Canada Publications Web site provides a single window access to free and priced publications authored by Government of Canada departments. The database does not have every publication published from all departments. It does however, have over 100,000 publications listed and this number is increasing on a daily basis as this site continues to collaborate with author departments.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.canada.gc.ca/main_e.html</url>
			<search_url>http://publications.gc.ca/control/quickPublicSearch?searchAction=2&amp;termValue={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Directgov</search_title>
			<search_description>Directgov is a government service giving people access to the latest and widest range of public service information in one place on the Web and on Digital TV. Directgov uses the specifications formulated and consulted on through UK GovTalk.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.direct.gov.uk</url>
			<search_url>http://www.direct.gov.uk/AdvancedSearch/SearchResults/fs/en?NP=1&amp;PO1=C&amp;PI1=W&amp;PF1=A&amp;PG=1&amp;RP=20&amp;SC=__dgov_site&amp;Z=1&amp;PT1={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Info4local.gov.uk</search_title>
			<search_description>Information for local government from central government.  This site gives local authorities a quick and easy way to find relevant information on the web sites of central government departments, agencies and public bodies. It includes extensive information on implementing electronic government.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.info4local.gov.uk</url>
			<search_url>http://www.info4local.gov.uk/?view=Search+results&amp;subjects=all&amp;departmentsIds=0&amp;informationTypesIds=all&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>The New Zealand government portal</search_title>
			<search_description>The New Zealand government portal is a website providing search capability for, and links into the online and offline information and services of most government agencies.  This site is managed and maintained by the State Services Commission, a New Zealand government department.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.govt.nz</url>
			<search_url>http://www.govt.nz/search?type=spider&amp;t=spider&amp;q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Europa</search_title>
			<search_description>Current information on the member countries of the European Union, including statistical data, policies, news, official documents, legal texts, and other publications.</search_description>
			<url>http://europa.eu.int/index_en.htm</url>
			<search_url>http://europa.eu.int/geninfo/query/resultaction.jsp?page=1</search_url>
			<search_post>Collection=EuropaFull&amp;ResultTemplate=/result_en.jsp&amp;ResultCount=25&amp;qtype=simple&amp;ResultMaxDocs=200&amp;DefaultLG=en&amp;QueryText={$formKeywords}</search_post>			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>The Global Legal Information Network (GLIN)</search_title>
			<search_description>The Global Legal Information Network (GLIN) is a database of laws, regulations, judicial decisions, and other complementary legal sources contributed by governmental agencies and international organizations. These GLIN members contribute the official full texts of published documents to the database in their original language. Each document is accompanied by a summary in English and subject terms selected from the multilingual index to GLIN.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.glin.gov</url>
			<search_url>http://www.glin.gov/search.do?refineQuery=&amp;offset=0&amp;refineQueryType=&amp;fromSearch=true&amp;queryType=ALL&amp;searchBtn=Search&amp;includeAllFields=on&amp;searchAll=on&amp;sumLanguage=any&amp;pubLanguage=any&amp;pubJurisdiction=any&amp;publicationJurisdictionExclude=false&amp;searchPublicationDate=true&amp;dateFromDay=01&amp;dateFromMonth=01&amp;dateFromYear=&amp;dateToDay=01&amp;dateToMonth=01&amp;dateToYear=&amp;subjTerm=&amp;subjTermConjunction%5B0%5D=AND&amp;subjTerm=&amp;subjTermConjunction%5B1%5D=AND&amp;subjTerm=&amp;subjTermConjunction%5B2%5D=AND&amp;subjTerm=&amp;subjTermConjunction%5B3%5D=AND&amp;subjTerm=&amp;searchOrder=default&amp;hitsPerPage=10&amp;showSummary=on&amp;queryString={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Book searches</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Book searches</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Book-related Resources</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Google Print</search_title>
			<search_description>Google is working with libraries at the University of Michigan, Harvard University, Stanford University, Oxford University and the New York Public Library to digitize books in their collections and make them accessible via Google Print, a massive scanning project that will bring millions of volumes of printed books into the Google Print database.  Click a book title and you'll see the page of the book that has your search terms, your can search for more information within that specific book, find reviews, find related information, learn about the publisher, buy this book, and find nearby libraries that have it.</search_description>
			<url>http://print.google.com</url>
			<search_url>http://print.google.com/print?q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Online books Page</search_title>
			<search_description>Online books Page, edited by John Mark Ockerbloom, at the University of Pennsylvania.  This is an excellent starting point in the search for full-text books on the Internet. Over 20,000 English works in various formats available online at different sites. Entries may be searched by author or title. An interesting feature allows browsing by Library of Congress call number categories. New listings are added regularly and are listed on a separate web page at &lt;a href=&quot;http://onlinebooks.library.upenn.edu/new.html&quot;&gt;http://onlinebooks.library.upenn.edu/new.html&lt;/a&gt;.</search_description>
			<url>http://digital.library.upenn.edu/books/</url>
			<search_url>http://onlinebooks.library.upenn.edu/webbin/book/search?tmode=words&amp;title={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Books-On-Line</search_title>
			<search_description>A collection of over 32935 titles, although some are only excerpts. Browse by subject or search by author or title. Not all items are free.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.books-on-line.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.books-on-line.com/bol/KeyWordSearch.cfm?RowCount=50&amp;Searchquery={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Universal Library</search_title>
			<search_description>The Universal Library is considerably more involved, and more ambitious -- it has amassed a collection of 100,000 e-books (some of them from Project Gutenberg), and is aiming for 1 million e-books by the end of 2006.</search_description>
			<url>http://tera-3.ul.cs.cmu.edu/</url>
			<search_url>http://tera-3.ul.cs.cmu.edu/cgi-bin/DBscripts/advsearch_db.cgi?perPage=25&amp;listStart=0&amp;author1=&amp;subject1=Any&amp;year1=&amp;year2=&amp;language1=Any&amp;scentre=Any&amp;search=Search&amp;title1={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Lit critics</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Literary Critics</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Search critical and biographical websites about authors and their works that can be browsed by author, by title, or by nationality and literary period.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Literary Index (Gale Group)</search_title>
			<search_description>This is &quot;a master index to the major literature products published by Gale,&quot; including Contemporary Authors and Literature Criticism from 1400-1800. Also indexes print reference titles from Charles Scribner's Sons, St. James Press, and Twayne Publishers. Many of these resources, commonly found in libraries, &quot;contain complete biographies on authors and critical essays on their writings.&quot;</search_description>
			<url>http://www.galenet.com/servlet/LitIndex</url>
			<search_url>http://www.galenet.com/servlet/LitIndex/hits?ttlRad=ti&amp;n=10&amp;NA=&amp;r=s&amp;origSearch=true&amp;o=DocTitle&amp;l=8&amp;c=1&amp;secondary=false&amp;u=LitIndex&amp;t=KW&amp;s=2&amp;TI={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Internet Public Library Online Literary Criticism Collection</search_title>
			<search_description>Browse the Internet Public Library's collection of links to websites on western and non-western literary criticism. Organized by author, title of work studied and by literary period within a particular national tradition.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.ipl.org/div/litcrit/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.ipl.org/div/searchresults/?where=searchresults&amp;words={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Poetry Portal</search_title>
			<search_description>This is a very comprehensive and informative collection of links about poetry online, events, courses, styles, and publishing. The site also covers &quot;ezines, poetry sites, audio poetry, literary appreciation, criticism and reviews, poetry courses, workshops, conferences, book and trade news, literary chit-chat and trade news, plus sources to improve your own writing and get it published.&quot;</search_description>
			<url>http://www.poetry-portal.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.google.com/search?hl=en&amp;q=site%3Awww.poetry-portal.com+{$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Book reviews</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Book reviews</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Click on the search urls to check for book reviews.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Bryn Mawr Classical Review</search_title>
			<search_description>Bryn Mawr Classical Review contains full text of every book review published since 1990 in the Bryn Mawr Classical Review. Articles are indexed both by issue and by the title of the book.</search_description>
			<url>http://ccat.sas.upenn.edu/bmcr/</url>
			<search_url>http://ccat.sas.upenn.edu/cgi-bin/bmcr/bmcr_search?action=search&amp;lookup={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>H-Net Reviews</search_title>
			<search_description>H-Net Reviews in the Humanities and Social Sciences is an online scholarly review resource. reviews are published online via discussion networks and the H-Net web site. This permits our reviews to reach scholars with a speed unmatched in any other medium. It also makes a new kind of interactivity possible, as reviewers, authors and readers engage in discussions of the reviews online. Through the power of e-mail and the web H-Net has helped pioneer online scholarly reviewing.</search_description>
			<url>http://www2.h-net.msu.edu/reviews/</url>
			<search_url>http://www2.h-net.msu.edu/reviews/search.cgi?maxlines=25&amp;maxfiles=25&amp;all=all&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>The New York Times Books</search_title>
			<search_description>The New York Times Books, updated daily, includes the entire Sunday Book reviews and a searchable archive of over 50,000 NYT book reviews dating back to 1980, bestseller lists and more (Need to sign up).</search_description>
			<url>http://www.nytimes.com/auth/login?Tag=/&amp;URI=/books/</url>
			<search_url>http://query.nytimes.com/search/query?ppds=ctaxAbodyS&amp;v1=Top%2FFeatures%2FBooks%2FBook+Reviews&amp;sort=closest_newest&amp;v2={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Early Modern Literary Studies</search_title>
			<search_description>Early Modern Literary Studies (ISSN 1201-2459) is a refereed journal serving as a formal arena for scholarly discussion and as an academic resource for researchers in the area. Articles in EMLS examine English literature, literary culture, and language during the sixteenth and seventeenth centuries; responses to published papers are also published as part of a Readers' Forum. Reviews evaluate recent work as well as academic tools of interest to scholars in the field. EMLS is committed to gathering and to maintaining links to the most useful and comprehensive internet resources for Renaissance scholars, including archives, electronic texts, discussion groups, and beyond.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.shu.ac.uk/emls/emlshome.html</url>
			<search_url>http://www.shu.ac.uk/cgi-bin/htsearch?method=and&amp;format=builtin-long&amp;sort=score&amp;matchesperpage=10&amp;config=emls&amp;restrict=&amp;exclude=&amp;words={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Related studies</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Related studies</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Access to related studies by establishing a working link with an open-access (free) database, with abstracts and/or full texts related to your topic.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Anthropological index</search_title>
			<search_description>The Anthropological Index is a regionally arranged subject and author index to periodical articles in all areas of anthropology. It is produced by the Museum of Mankind Library.</search_description>
			<url>http://aio.anthropology.org.uk/cgi-bin/uncgi/search_bib_ai/anthind_short</url>
			<search_url>http://aio.anthropology.org.uk/cgi-bin/uncgi/search_bib_ai/anthind_short</search_url>
			<search_post>Default_Years=2001#2002#2003#2004#2005#Recent&amp;Year=#1957#1958#1959#1960#1961#1962#1963#1964#1965#1966#1967#1968#1969#1970#1971#1972#1973#1974#1975#1976#1977#1978#1979#1980#1981#1982#1983#1984#1985#1986#1987#1988#1989#1990#1991#1992#1993#1994#1995#1996#1997#1998#1999#2000#2001#2002#2003#2004#2005#Recent&amp;Text_w=&amp;Author_w=&amp;Subject1=&amp;Subject2=&amp;Subject3=&amp;Email=You@whereever.edu&amp;Refer=on&amp;Author=&amp;Text={$formKeywords}</search_post>			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>The English Server</search_title>
			<search_description>The English Server contains humanities texts online with over 18,000 works, covering history, race, art &amp; architecture, government and other topics.</search_description>
			<url>http://eserver.org/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.google.com/u/EServer?q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>IATH: Institute for Advanced Technology in the Humanities</search_title>
			<search_description>IATH: Institute for Advanced Technology in the Humanities, from the University of Virginia at Charlottesville, provides access to web-based humanities research archives and reports, essays, and the current issue of Postmodern Culture, the Internet's oldest peer-reviewed electronic journal in the humanities.</search_description>
			<url>http://jefferson.village.virginia.edu/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.google.com/u/iath?sa=Google+Search+of+IATH&amp;domains=village.virginia.edu&amp;sitesearch=village.virginia.edu&amp;q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>NetSERF: the Internet connection for medieval resources</search_title>
			<search_description>Detailed topical arrangement of links to a large number of sites pertaining to medieval history and culture.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.netserf.org/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.netserf.org/Features/Search/default.cfm?Search_Action=Process&amp;Phrase_required=You must provide a search phrase with this option.&amp;phrase={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>The Online books Page</search_title>
			<search_description>The Online books Page is the most comprehensive website that facilitates access to books that are freely readable over the Internet.</search_description>
			<url>http://digital.library.upenn.edu/books/</url>
			<search_url>http://onlinebooks.library.upenn.edu/webbin/book/search?author=&amp;amode=words&amp;tmode=words&amp;title={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Perseus Digital Library</search_title>
			<search_description>Perseus Digital library is designed to be resources for the study of the ancient world. Originally begun with coverage of the Archaic and Classical Greek world, has now expanded to Latin text and tools, Renaissance materials, and Papyri. Contains hundreds of texts by the major ancient authors and lexica and morphological databases and catalog entries for over 2,800 vases, sculptures, coins, buildings, and sites, including over 13,000 photographs of such objects.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.perseus.tufts.edu/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.perseus.tufts.edu/cgi-bin/vor?x=22&amp;y=15&amp;lookup={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Voice of the Shuttle</search_title>
			<search_description>Voice of the Shuttle emphasizes both primary and secondary (or theoretical) resources of American literature, including links of syllabi, electronic journals and newsgroups.</search_description>
			<url>http://vos.ucsb.edu/</url>
			<search_url>http://vos.ucsb.edu/search-results.asp?Submit=Go&amp;search={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Dictionary of Canadian Biography Online</search_title>
			<search_description>A collection of authoritative biographies portraying noteworthy persons of both sexes (with the exception of those still living). This first phase presents persons who died between the years 1000 and 1920</search_description>
			<url>http://www.biographi.ca/EN/index.html</url>
			<search_url>http://www.biographi.ca/EN/Results.asp?ToDo=&amp;Show=&amp;Data1=&amp;Data2=&amp;Data3=&amp;Data4=&amp;Data5=&amp;Data6=&amp;&amp;Data7=&amp;Data8=&amp;Data9=&amp;Data10=&amp;txtSearch={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Dissertations</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Dissertations</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Provides access to a repository of rich graduate educational material contributed by a number of member institutions worldwide.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>CRL Foreign Doctoral Dissertation Databases</search_title>
			<search_description>The CRL's (Center For Research Libraries) database for dissertations published outside of the United States and Canada is still in the construction phase. At this point, a total of 15,000 of 750,000 records are loaded into the database. Searchable by author, institution name, title, year, translated title, subject keywords, language, and country, the database also provides instructions for interlibrary loan procedure.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.crl.edu/content.asp?l1=5&amp;l2=23&amp;l3=44&amp;l4=25</url>
			<search_url>http://www.crl.edu/DBSearch/dissertationsSummary.asp?language=English&amp;title={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Dissertation.com</search_title>
			<search_description>Academic publishers of masters theses and doctoral PhD dissertations. Search 1000s of dissertation abstracts in dissertation database.</search_description>
			<url>http://dissertation.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://dissertation.com/browse.php?criteria=all&amp;submit.x=23&amp;submit.y=5&amp;keyword={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Networked Digital Library of Theses and Dissertations Union Catalog</search_title>
			<search_description>This Union Catalog serves as a repository of rich graduate educational material contributed by a number of member institutions worldwide.  This project is a joint development with NDLTD and VTLS Inc.  It is hoped that this project will increase the availability of student research for scholars, empowere students to convey a richer message through the use of multimedia and hypermedia technologies and advance digital library technology worldwide.</search_description>
			<url>http://zippo.vtls.com/cgi-bin/ndltd/chameleon</url>
			<search_url>http://zippo.vtls.com/cgi-bin/ndltd/chameleon?sessionid=2006051219043826835&amp;skin=ndltd&amp;submittheform=Search&amp;usersrch=1&amp;beginsrch=1&amp;elementcount=3&amp;function=INITREQ&amp;search=SCAN&amp;lng=en&amp;pos=1&amp;conf=.%2Fchameleon.conf&amp;u1=4&amp;host=localhost%2B3668%2BDEFAULT&amp;t1={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Scirus ETD Search</search_title>
			<search_description>NDLTD offers a search service provided by Scirus, which is based on data harvested from the Union Archive hosted by OCLC.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.ndltd.org/info/description.en.html</url>
			<search_url>http://www.scirus.com/srsapp/search?rep=ndl&amp;q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Databases</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Databases</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Provide access to open-access abstract and/or full-text databases.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>AAD</search_title>
			<search_description>Access to archival Databases (AAD) System has approximately 350 data files with millions of records available online that are highly structured, such as in databases. The series selected for AAD identify specific persons, geographic areas, organizations, or dates. Some of these series serve as indexes to accessioned archival records in non-electronic formats. Includes a link to search descriptions of NARA's non-electronic records through NARA's online catalogue, ARC.</search_description>
			<url>http://aad.archives.gov/aad</url>
			<search_url>http://search.nara.gov/query.html?rq=0&amp;qp=&amp;rq=0&amp;col=4ardor&amp;col=3ourdoc&amp;col=2pres&amp;col=1arch&amp;qs=&amp;qc=&amp;pw=100%25&amp;ws=0&amp;la=&amp;qm=0&amp;st=1&amp;nh=10&amp;lk=1&amp;rf=0&amp;oq=&amp;rq=0&amp;qt={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Making of America: the Cornell University Library MOA collection</search_title>
			<search_description>A digital library of primary sources in American social history from the antebellum period through reconstruction. The collection is particularly strong in the subject areas of education, psychology, American history, sociology, religion, and science and technology.</search_description>
			<url>http://cdl.library.cornell.edu/moa/</url>
			<search_url>http://cdl.library.cornell.edu/cgi-bin/moa/sgml/moa-idx?&amp;type=simple&amp;slice=1&amp;layer=first&amp;coll=both&amp;year1=1815&amp;ear2=1926&amp;q1={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>UIUC Digital Gateway to Cultural Heritage Materials</search_title>
			<search_description>This gateway is using the OAI Protocol for harvesting metadata, and exposing it with a search interface to enhance resource discoverability for materials that represent cultural heritage. The repository includes metadata records donated by 39 institutions over 1.3 million records.</search_description>
			<url>http://nergal.grainger.uiuc.edu/cgi/b/bib/bib-idx</url>
			<search_url>http://nergal.grainger.uiuc.edu/cgi/b/bib/bib-idx?type=simple&amp;xc=1&amp;q6=&amp;rgn6=identifier&amp;rgn1=entire+record&amp;op6=And&amp;q1={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>A2A - Access to Archives</search_title>
			<search_description>Contains catalogues describing archives held throughout England and dating from the 900s to the present day.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.a2a.org.uk/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.a2a.org.uk/search/doclist.asp?nb=0&amp;nbKey=1&amp;com=1&amp;properties=0601&amp;keyword={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Archives Hub (UK)</search_title>
			<search_description>A national gateway to descriptions of archives in UK universities and colleges.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.archiveshub.ac.uk/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.archiveshub.ac.uk/cgi-bin/deadsearch.cgi?server=SF&amp;fieldidx1=descriptionWord&amp;bool=AND&amp;numreq=25&amp;firstrec=1&amp;format=sgml&amp;noframes=0&amp;maxrecs=50&amp;firstrec=1&amp;fieldcont1={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Catholic Encyclopedia</search_title>
			<search_description>Contains full and authoritative information on Catholic interests, action, and doctrine.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.newadvent.org/cathen/index.html</url>
			<search_url>http://www.google.com/custom?domains=NewAdvent.org&amp;sa=Search+New+Advent&amp;sitesearch=NewAdvent.org&amp;client=pub-8168503353085287&amp;forid=1&amp;ie=ISO-8859-1&amp;oe=ISO-8859-1&amp;safe=active&amp;cof=GALT%3A%23008000%3BGL%3A1%3BDIV%3A%23336699%3BVLC%3A663399%3BAH%3Acenter%3BBGC%3AFFFFFF%3BLBGC%3A336699%3BALC%3A0000FF%3BLC%3A0000FF%3BT%3A000000%3BGFNT%3A0000FF%3BGIMP%3A0000FF%3BFORID%3A1%3B&amp;hl=en&amp;q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Literature, Arts, and Medicine Databases</search_title>
			<search_description>The Literature, Arts, &amp; Medicine Database is an annotated multimedia listing of prose, poetry, film, video and art that was developed to be a dynamic, accessible, comprehensive resource for teaching and research in MEDICAL HUMANITIES, and for use in health/pre-health, graduate and undergraduate liberal arts and social science settings.</search_description>
			<url>http://litmed.med.nyu.edu/Main?action=aboutDB</url>
			<search_url>http://google.med.nyu.edu/search?btnG=search&amp;access=p&amp;entqr=0&amp;output=xml_no_dtd&amp;sort=date%3AD%3AL%3Ad1&amp;ud=1&amp;client=litmed_test&amp;oe=UTF-8&amp;ie=UTF-8&amp;proxystylesheet=litmed_test&amp;site=litmed_test&amp;q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Map Collection, Perry-Castaneda</search_title>
			<search_description>Displays selected digitized images from the printed map collection housed at the University of Texas at Austin.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.lib.utexas.edu/maps/index.html</url>
			<search_url>http://www.lib.utexas.edu:8080/search/utlol/search.jsp?collections=utlol&amp;collections=utdatabases&amp;queryText={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Relevant portals</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Relevant portals</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Relevant portals</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Archives Portal</search_title>
			<search_description>UNESCO, the United Nations Educational, Scientific, and Cultural Organization, provides a list of links to archives around the world with a Web presence.</search_description>
			<url>http://portal.unesco.org/ci/en/ev.php-URL_ID=5761&amp;URL_DO=DO_TOPIC&amp;URL_SECTION=201.html</url>
			<search_url>http://www.unesco.org/cgi-bin/webworld/portal_archives/cgi/search.cgi?search2=GO&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Digital South Asia Library</search_title>
			<search_description>On-line information about contemporary and historical South Asia - including full-text documents, statistical data, electronic images, cartographic representations, and pedagogical resources for language instruction.</search_description>
			<url>http://dsal.uchicago.edu/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.google.com/u/dsal?sa=Search&amp;q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>History Guide</search_title>
			<search_description>Subject gateway to scholarly relevant information in history with a focus on Anglo-American history and the history of Central and Western Europe.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.historyguide.de/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.historyguide.de/allegrosuche.php?start=0&amp;suchterm={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Dante Project (Dartmouth)</search_title>
			<search_description>Searchable collection of texts including the Italian text of the Divine Comedy and commentaries.</search_description>
			<url>http://dante.dartmouth.edu/</url>
			<search_url>http://dante.dartmouth.edu/search_view.php?commentary[]=0&amp;language=any&amp;cantica=0&amp;canto=&amp;line={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			<search_post>Cmd=Search&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_post>			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Romantic Circles: Byron, the Shelleys, Keats and their Contemporaries</search_title>
			<search_description>A Web site that provides scholarly resources for the study of Romantic-period literature and culture.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.rc.umd.edu/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.rc.umd.edu/cgi-bin/search/search.pl?Match=1&amp;Realm=Editions&amp;submit=Search&amp;Terms={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Intute: Arts &amp; Humanities</search_title>
			<search_description>Intute: Arts &amp; Humanities is a free online service providing you with access to the best Web resources for education and research, selected and evaluated by a network of subject specialists. There are over 18,000 Web resources listed here that are freely available by keyword searching and browsing.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.intute.ac.uk/artsandhumanities/ejournals.html</url>
			<search_url>http://www.intute.ac.uk/artsandhumanities/cgi-bin/search.pl?submit.x=0&amp;submit.y=0&amp;submit=Go&amp;limit=0&amp;subject=artsandhumanities&amp;term1={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Pay-per-view</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Pay-per-view</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>A pay-per-view service is for those who do not have direct access to electronic journal articles via subscriptions. The service allows customers to gain direct access to an article by paying by credit card using the RSC's secure payment mechanism. Immediately the payment details have been validated, the customer can gain access to the required article file for a period of 30 days.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Ingenta</search_title>
			<search_description>Ingenta restricts access to full text articles. Although access to the full text costs money, the site can be used as a free index.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.ingenta.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.ingenta.com/isis/searching/Search/ingenta?database=1&amp;title={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>ebrary</search_title>
			<search_description>Independent researchers who do not have access to ebrary?s databases through their library may now set up an individual account for as little as $5. ebrary Discover spans multiple academic disciplines and provides anytime, anywhere access to over 20,000 authoritative titles including books in full-text, sheet music, reports and other authoritative documents from more than 175 leading publishers such as Cambridge University Press, Random House, Inc., and The McGraw-Hill Companies.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.ebrary.com/corp/content.htm</url>
			<search_url>http://shop.ebrary.com/Top?layout=search&amp;f00=text&amp;p01=&amp;f01=subject&amp;d=journal&amp;l=en&amp;sch=%A0%A0%A0%A0%A0Search%A0%A0%A0%A0%A0&amp;frm=adv.x&amp;p00={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Questia</search_title>
			<search_description>Questia provides access to over 47,000 books and 375,000 journal, magazine, and newspaper articles. All books and articles are available in their entirety - search every page. The subscription rate is ranging from 19.05 per month to 119.95 per year.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.questia.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.questia.com/SM.qst?act=search&amp;keywordsSearchType=1000&amp;mediaType=book&amp;mediaType=journal&amp;mediaType=magazine&amp;mediaType=newspaper&amp;mediaType=encyclopedia&amp;mediaType=startpage&amp;keywords={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Wiley InterScience Pay-per-view Service</search_title>
			<search_description>Wiley InterScience Pay-per-view affords instant, full-text access to an extensive collection of journal articles or book chapters available on Wiley InterScience without the need for a subscription. This service allows anyone to purchase access to individual journal articles or book chapters directly by using a credit card. Access is instant and available for 24 hours.</search_description>
			<url>http://www3.interscience.wiley.com/aboutus/ppv-articleselect.html</url>
			<search_url>http://www3.interscience.wiley.com/search/allsearch</search_url>
			<search_post>allContentSearchForm=&amp;mode=quicksearch&amp;WISindexid1=WISall&amp;WISsearch1={$formKeywords}</search_post>			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Related texts</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Related texts</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Provide online access to full text resources in Humanities.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Electronic Text Center</search_title>
			<search_description>Electronic Text Center reflects over 5,000 publicly accessible texts on history, literature, philosophy, religion, history of science. Texts are in English and other languages, including Latin, Japanese and Chinese.</search_description>
			<url>http://etext.lib.virginia.edu/</url>
			<search_url>http://etext.virginia.edu/etcbin/ot2www-ebooks?specfile=%2Ftexts%2Fenglish%2Febooks%2Febooks.o2w&amp;docs=TEI2&amp;sample=1-100&amp;grouping=work&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>IPL Online Texts Collection</search_title>
			<search_description>IPL Online Texts Collection contains over 19,000 titles that can be browsed by author, by title, or by Dewey Decimal Classification.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.ipl.org/reading/books/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.ipl.org/div/searchresults/?where=allv&amp;words={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Linguistic Data Consortium</search_title>
			<search_description>Linguistic Data Consortium supports language-related education, research and technology development by creating and sharing linguistic resources including data, tools and standards.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.ldc.upenn.edu/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.ldc.upenn.edu/Catalog/catalogSearchResults.jsp?ldc_catalog_id=&amp;name=&amp;author=&amp;languages=&amp;years=&amp;types=&amp;datasources=&amp;projects=&amp;applications=&amp;and_or=1&amp;and_or2=1&amp;desc={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Oxford Text Archive</search_title>
			<search_description>Oxford Text Archive contains Scholarly electronic texts and linguistic corpora across the range of humanities disciplines, with emphasis on resources of more than 1,500 literary works by many major authors in Greek, Latin, English and a dozen or more other languages.</search_description>
			<url>http://ota.ahds.ac.uk/</url>
			<search_url>http://ota.ahds.ac.uk/search/search.perl?search=SIMPLE&amp;author=&amp;title={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Project Gutenberg</search_title>
			<search_description>Project Gutenberg is the definitive Web site for this project to put out-of-copyright books online in full-text. More than 6,000 texts online so far.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.gutenberg.net/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.gutenberg.org/catalog/world/results?author=&amp;etestnr=&amp;title={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Online forums</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Online forums</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Choose online, open-access online forums that would enrich the context of the research studies on your site.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>H-Net Humanities and Social Sciences Online</search_title>
			<search_description>H-Net Humanities and Social Sciences Online provides information and resources for all those interested in the Humanities and Social Sciences.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.h-net.org/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.h-net.org/logsearch/index.cgi?&amp;type=keyword&amp;hitlimit=25&amp;field=&amp;nojg=on&amp;smonth=00&amp;syear=1989&amp;emonth=11&amp;eyear=2004&amp;order=relevance&amp;phrase={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Humanist</search_title>
			<search_description>Humanist is an international electronic seminar on the application of computers in the humanities. Its primary aim is to provide a forum for discussion of intellectual, scholarly, pedagogical, and social issues and for exchange of information among members.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.princeton.edu/~mccarty/humanist/index.html</url>
			<search_url>http://lists.village.virginia.edu/cgi-bin/AT-Humanistsearch.cgi?sp=sp&amp;searchButton.x=15&amp;searchButton.y=14&amp;search={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Liszt</search_title>
			<search_description>Liszt, hosted by Topica, is a free service that allows you to find, manage and participate in email lists and discussion groups in humanities.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.liszt.com/dir/?cid=0</url>
			<search_url>http://lists.topica.com/search/?x=28&amp;y=5&amp;search_type=cat&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Teaching files</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Instructional</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Immediately initiates a search based on the subject of the article or paper that connects users to free current and archival articles in the field from leading newspapers around the world.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>EDSITEment</search_title>
			<search_description>EDSITEment is a constantly growing collection of the most valuable online resources for teaching English, history, art history, and foreign languages.</search_description>
			<url>http://edsitement.neh.gov/</url>
			<search_url>http://marcopolosearch.org/MPSearch/Search_Results.asp?orgn_id=5&amp;log_type=1&amp;hdnFilter=+AND+%28%7Bsubject_social%241%7D%29&amp;hdnPerPage=15&amp;selUsing=all&amp;txtSearchFor={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Media reports</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Media reports</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Immediately initiates a search based on the subject of the article or paper that connects users to free current and archival articles in the field from leading newspapers around the world.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Google News</search_title>
			<search_description>Search news reports using the popular search engine Google's news feature.</search_description>
			<url>http://news.google.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://news.google.com/news?hl=en&amp;q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Globe and Mail</search_title>
			<search_description>Globe and Mail, Toronto (last seven days)</search_description>
			<url>http://www.globeandmail.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.globeandmail.com/servlet/HTMLTemplate/search?tf=tgam/search/tgam/SearchResults.html&amp;cf=tgam/search/tgam/SearchResults.cfg&amp;current_row=1&amp;start_row=1&amp;num_rows=10&amp;keywords={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>People's Daily</search_title>
			<search_description>People's Daily, China (January 1999-)</search_description>
			<url>http://english.peopledaily.com.cn/</url>
			<search_url>http://search.people.com.cn/was40/people/GB/english_index.jsp?type=1&amp;channel=&amp;Content=&amp;searchword={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Mail &amp; Guardian Newspaper</search_title>
			<search_description>Mail &amp; Guardian Newspaper, South Africa (1994-)</search_description>
			<url>http://www.mg.co.za/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.mg.co.za/mg_search_results.aspx?PrintEdition=PrintEdition&amp;DailyNews=DailyNews&amp;SearchSection=&amp;StartDay=&amp;StartMonth=&amp;StartYear=&amp;EndDay=&amp;EndMonth=&amp;EndYear=&amp;keywords={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>National Public Radio</search_title>
			<search_description>National Public Radio, United States (unlimited)</search_description>
			<url>http://www.npr.org/archives/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.npr.org/search.php?text={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>New York Times</search_title>
			<search_description>New York Times, New York (last seven days)</search_description>
			<url>http://www.nytimes.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://query.nytimes.com/search/query?date=site1week&amp;submit.x=1&amp;submit.y=9&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>The Japan Times Online</search_title>
			<search_description>The Japan Times Online, Japan (January 1999-)</search_description>
			<url>http://www.japantimes.co.jp/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.google.co.jp/custom?domains=japantimes.co.jp&amp;client=pub-4223870936880387&amp;forid=1&amp;ie=Shift_JIS&amp;oe=Shift_JIS&amp;term1=&amp;cof=GALT%3A%23008000%3BGL%3A1%3BDIV%3A%23336699%3BVLC%3A663399%3BAH%3Acenter%3BBGC%3AFFFFFF%3BLBGC%3AFFFFFF%3BALC%3A0000FF%3BLC%3A0000FF%3BT%3A000000%3BGFNT%3A0000FF%3BGIMP%3A0000FF%3BLH%3A60%3BLW%3A200%3BL%3Ahttp%3A%2F%2Fwww.japantimes.co.jp%2Fimages%2Fheader_title.gif%3BS%3Ahttp%3A%2F%2Fwww.japantimes.co.jp%2F%3BFORID%3A1%3B&amp;hl=ja&amp;advancesearch=&amp;q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>The Moscow Times</search_title>
			<search_description>The Moscow Times, Russia (1994-)</search_description>
			<url>http://www.moscowtimes.ru/doc/Search.html</url>
			<search_url>http://www.moscowtimes.ru/cgi-bin/search?config=&amp;exclude=&amp;method=and&amp;format=long&amp;sort=score&amp;matchesperpage=10&amp;words={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Washington Post</search_title>
			<search_description>Washington Post, Washington, DC (last two weeks)</search_description>
			<url>http://www.washingtonpost.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.washingtonpost.com/cgi-bin/search99.pl?searchsection=news&amp;searchdatabase=news&amp;x=11&amp;y=8&amp;searchtext={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Newsdirectory</search_title>
			<search_description>Newsdirectory is a comprehensive and searchable guide to the world's English-language online media. Currently over 8,000 newspapers and magazines are listed, as well as more than 1,000 U.S. television broadcasters.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.newsdirectory.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.newsdirectory.com/hbSearch.php</search_url>
			<search_post>s={$formKeywords}&amp; submit=Go</search_post>
			
		</search>
	</context>
	<context>
		<context_title>Web search</context_title>
		<context_abbrev>Web search</context_abbrev>
		<context_description>Enter a search term for Internet resources through various search engines.</context_description>

		<search>
			<search_title>Google</search_title>
			<search_description>Search using the popular Google search engine.</search_description>
			<url>http://www.google.com/</url>
			<search_url>http://www.google.com/search?q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Google Scholar</search_title>
			<search_description>Google Scholar enables specific searches of scholarly literature, including peer-reviewed papers, theses, books, pre-prints, abstracts, and technical reports. Content includes a range of publishers and aggregators with whom Google already has standing arrangements, e.g., the Association for Computing Machinery, IEEE, OCLC's Open WorldCat library locator service, etc. Result displays will show different version clusters, citation analysis, and library location (currently books only).</search_description>
			<url>http://scholar.google.com</url>
			<search_url>http://scholar.google.com/scholar?ie=UTF-8&amp;oe=UTF-8&amp;hl=en&amp;q={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Clusty the Clustering Engine</search_title>
			<search_description>This search tool from Vivismo offers clustered results for a selection of searches.  Metasearch the whole web, or use tabs to search for news, gossip, images, orproducts via Bizrate or eBay.</search_description>
			<url>http://clusty.com/about</url>
			<search_url>http://clusty.com/search?query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
		<search>
			<search_title>Vivisimo</search_title>
			<search_description>The award-winning Vivisimo clustering technology, developed by Carnegie Mellon research scientists, is unlocking the value of stored information at Fortune 500 companies, top websites, prestigious publishers and government agencies by categorizing research results on the fly into meaningful orders, thus achieving breakthrough improvement in access to relevant information.</search_description>
			<url>http://vivisimo.com</url>
			<search_url>http://vivisimo.com/search?tb=homepage&amp;v%3Asources=Web&amp;query={$formKeywords}</search_url>
			
		</search>
	</context>
</version>
