<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic SYSTEM "../../topic.dtd">

<!--
  * 000005.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2005 The Public Knowledge Project
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  *
  * Management Pages - Sections 
  *
  * $Id$
  -->

<topic id="journal/topic/000005" locale="en_US" title="Sections" toc="journal/toc/000001" key="journal.managementPages.sections">
	<section title="">
		<![CDATA[<p>The Journal Manager is able to create different Sections within the journal in Sections, under Journal Management. A journal might typically include such sections as Articles, Book Reviews, Research Notes, Clinical Applications, Commentary, Editorial, etc. On setting up a Section for the journal, the Journal Manager is able to assign Section Editors who will be assigned submissions that have been submitted to the Section which they will then see through the editorial process. (The Editor assigns submissions in the {help_topic key="editorial.editorsRole.submissions.unassigned" text="Unassigned"} submissions queue to one of the designated Section Editors as part of the Editorial Process). Sections may be presented in different formats or layout design within the journal. The Table of Contents, which the Editor arranges for each issue, will be divided into the Sections that have been created, although if there is no content for a particular Section in a given issue, the Section will not appear in the Table of Contents.</p><p><i>Creating Sections for the journal</i>. In setting up a Section, the Journal Manager should enter a brief Policy Statement, which will be made available in About the Journal under Section Policies. The statement should describe the scope of the Section, as well as whether submissions to the section are peer reviewed. The Journal Manager is also able to determine for each Section  a number of options which relate to how submissions are handled. The first of these options is whether submissions to the Section will be indexed, with the metadata made available to research search engines that adhere to the same protocol, namely the Open Archives Initiative Metadata Harvesting Protocol. For example, indexing the Conference Announcements or Front Matter is not appropriate. Checking the indexing option adds the indexing templates to the Author submission process, as well as causing the system to generate metadata for the submission. A second option, which requires the indexing option, is to have the published submissions in a Section accompanied by the journal's {help_topic key="journal.managementPages.readingTools" text="Reading Tools"}, which are designed to support research and scholarly items. A third option, also related to whether the items in the Section are</p>]]>	
	</section>
</topic>
