<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic SYSTEM "../../topic.dtd">

<!--
  * 000001.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2004 The Public Knowledge Project
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  *
  * Management Pages Index 
  *
  * $Id$
  -->

<topic id="journal/topic/000001" locale="en_US" title="Management Pages" toc="journal/toc/000001" key="HELP_TOPIC_INDEX">
	<section title="">
		<![CDATA[<p>The Journal Manager is able to configure and customize the system to suit the journal through a series of Management Pages, beginning with the five steps of the Setup, but also including the Sections which it publishes, the tone and wording of the journal's standard emails, its available languages, the statistics it publishes, and the tools it makes available to readers.</p>]]>	
	</section>
	<section title="Setup">
		<![CDATA[<p>The Journal Manager sets up the journal, after the system has been installed on a Web server, by working through five steps, filling in templates and configuring the management of the journal. The templates can be filled in and saved, without having to complete the Setup at one time, and the Journal Manager can return to Setup to make changes at any time.</p><p>Setup in available to the Journal Manager on the Journal Management page, and contains its own set of Help texts built into each of the templates. Setting up this journal's Web site will require decisions and texts for the following items, among others, which can be prepared in advance in consultation with the Editors or added at a later point.</p><ul><li>Principal contact for the journal</li><li>Technical contact</li><li>Scope and Focus Statement for the journal</li><li>Journal Sections and policies</li><li>Author Guidelines</li><li>Submission requirements for authors</li><li>Indexing elements and appropriate examples</li><li>Peer Review Policy</li><li>Reviewer Guidelines</li><li>Copyright Policy</li><li>Open Access Policy</li><li>Editorial Board/Review Board</li><li>Use of layout editors, copyeditors, and/or proofreaders</li></ul>]]>	
	</section>
	<section title="Sections">
		<![CDATA[<p>The Journal Manager is able to create different Sections within the journal in Sections, under Journal Management. A journal might typically include such sections as Articles, Book Reviews, Research Notes, Clinical Applications, Commentary, Editorial, etc. On setting up a Section for the journal, the Journal Manager is able to assign Section Editors who will be assigned submissions that have been submitted to the Section which they will then see through the editorial process. (The Editor assigns submissions in the {help_topic key="editorial.editorsRole.submissions.unassigned" text="Unassigned"} submissions queue to one of the designated Section Editors as part of the Editorial Process). Sections may be presented in different formats or layout design within the journal. The Table of Contents, which the Editor arranges for each issue, will be divided into the Sections that have been created, although if there is no content for a particular Section in a given issue, the Section will not appear in the Table of Contents.</p><p><i>Creating Sections for the journal</i>. In setting up a Section, the Journal Manager should enter a brief Policy Statement, which will be made available in About the Journal under Section Policies. The statement should describe the scope of the Section, as well as whether submissions to the section are peer reviewed. The Journal Manager is also able to determine for each Section  a number of options which relate to how submissions are handled. The first of these options is whether submissions to the Section will be indexed, with the metadata made available to research search engines that adhere to the same protocol, namely the Open Archives Initiative Metadata Harvesting Protocol. For example, indexing the Conference Announcements or Front Matter is not appropriate. Checking the indexing option adds the indexing templates to the Author submission process, as well as causing the system to generate metadata for the submission. A second option, which requires the indexing option, is to have the published submissions in a Section accompanied by the journal's {help_topic key="journal.managementPages.readingTools" text="Reading Tools"}, which are designed to support research and scholarly items. A third option, also related to whether the items in the Section are</p>]]>	
	</section>
	<section title="Emails">
		<![CDATA[<p>The journal uses a variety of prepared emails to direct the Editorial and Publishing Processes. The emails are all directed, and addressed, in advance for the appropriate recipient (as the Section Editor notifies the Copyeditor, for example, that copyediting for a submission is ready to begin). The default versions of these emails can be edited by the Journal Manager, which are available under Emails on the Journal Administration page. As well, the emails can be edited by the user before they are sent. The system automatically inserts relevant and specific information into the email prior to presenting it to the user to send, such as the title and abstract of the submission in question or the date which a review is due. The email also provides the recipient with the URL, username, and password, as well as instructions to find their way to the appropriate Web page, so that they can undertake the task requested of them.</p>]]>	
	</section>
	<section title="Languages">
		<![CDATA[<p>This system can support multi-lingual journals, as well as journals in languages other than English. Those languages that have been made available for the system are listed under Languages in Journal Management. The Journal Manager may also wish to consult the <a href="javascript:openWindow('http://pkp.ubc.ca');">Open Journal System</a> Web site to see if additional languages have been made available, or consult the <a href="javascript:openWindow('http://www.pkp.ubc.ca/support/forum');">OJS Support Forum</a>, where such developments are discussed and resources shared.</p>]]>	
	</section>
	<section title="Statistics">
		<![CDATA[<p>The Journal Manager is able to consult a series of statistics that are commonly used by journals to monitor their progress and standards (for example, rejection rate, through-put time, reviewer load, etc.). The Journal Manager has the option of making some or all of these statistics available to Readers, which will be presented under the title of Statistics in About the Journal. On occasion, Authors are asked to provide this information when applying for tenure and promotion, and it is helpful for informing potential contributors of how the journal is performing. Journal Managers may wish to wait until the journal has been in operation for a year or so, so that the figures have some reliability, before making them public.</p>]]>	
	</section>
	<section title="Reading Tools (Management)">
		<![CDATA[<p>The Journal Manager is able to select a set of Reading Tools that are most appropriate for the content of the journal, from among the discipline-based examples provided under Reading Tools on the Journal Management page (e.g., Humanities, Education, Physics, etc.). These Tools enable the Reader to consult relevant information that adds to the context of the item which they are reading. The goal of the tools is to provide a richer context for the reading experience of novice and expert readers within the scope of the journal's coverage. The Journal Manager is able to edit or delete existing resources and add new ones as well. Also see {help_topic key="user.readingTools" text="Reading Tools"} under User Interface.</p>]]>	
	</section>
	<section title="File Browser">
		<![CDATA[<p>The Journal Manager is able to upload files associated with the journal...</p>]]>	
	</section>
</topic>
