<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic SYSTEM "../../topic.dtd">

<!--
  * 000005.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2005 The Public Knowledge Project
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  *
  * Management Pages - Sections 
  *
  * $Id$
  -->

<topic id="journal/topic/000005" locale="en_US" title="Sections" toc="journal/toc/000001" key="journal.managementPages.sections">
	<section title="">
		<![CDATA[<p>The Journal Manager is able to create different Sections within the journal in Sections, under Journal Management. A journal might typically include such sections as Articles, Book Reviews, Research Notes, Clinical Applications, Commentary, Editorial, etc. On setting up a Section for the journal, the Journal Manager is able to assign Section Editors who will be assigned submissions that have been submitted to the Section which they will then see through the editorial process. (The Editor assigns submissions in the {help_topic key="editorial.editorsRole.submissions.unassigned" text="Unassigned"} submissions queue to one of the designated Section Editors as part of the Editorial Process). Sections may be presented in different formats or layout design within the journal. The Table of Contents, which the Editor arranges for each issue, will be divided into the Sections that have been created, although if there is no content for a particular Section in a given issue, the Section will not appear in the Table of Contents.</p><p><i>Creating a Section policy</i>. In setting up a Section, the Journal Manager should enter a brief Policy Statement for the Section, which will be made available to authors and readers in About the Journal under Section Policies. The statement should describe the scope of the Section and type of submissions sought, whether submissions are peer reviewed and indexed, whether the Section is open or restricted to invited work or Editors, what is the desired length, etc.</p><p><i>Indexing and restricting the contents of a Section</i>. Items in a section should be indexed if they contribute to the literature (which is not the case, for example, with a section devoted to conference announcements or job notices). The indexing option will enable authors to enter the relevant metadata on submitting an item. The metadata will be made available, if the item is published, to research search engines that adhere to the Open Archives Initiative Metadata Harvesting Protocol, as well as to other indexing services. Items in Sections that are indexed will also have their authors added to the Author List, and will be accompanied by the Reading Tools selected for this journal. As for restrictions, this box should be checked for Sections of the journal, such as Editorials or Interviews, which are not open to author submissions in an unrestricted way, as submissions must come from the editors or are invited. Such a section can only be submitted to by authors who are also registered as Editors or Section Editors.</p>]]>
	</section>
</topic>
