<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE data SYSTEM "../dtd/xmldata.dtd">

<!--
  * 2.2.0_update.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2007 John Willinsky
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  *
  * 2.2.0 database updates XML file.
  *
  * $Id$
  -->

<data>
	<!-- #2424# Drop the currencies table after the FKs have been kept. -->
	<sql>
		<drop table="currencies" />
	</sql>

	<!-- #2501# Added context information to groups -->
	<sql>
		<query>UPDATE groups SET context = 1</query>
	</sql>

	<!-- #2337# Add email template for REVIEWER_REGISTER; modify wording for USER_REGISTER -->
	<sql>
		<query>UPDATE email_templates_default_data SET subject = 'Journal Registration', body = '{$userFullName}

You have now been registered as a user with {$journalName}. We have included your username and password in this email, which are needed for all work with this journal though its website. At any point, you can ask to be removed from the journal''s list of users by contacting me.

Username: {$username}
Password: {$password}

Thank you,
{$principalContactSignature}' WHERE subject = 'New User Registration' AND body = 'Thank you for registering as a user with {$journalName}. Please keep track of your username and password, which are needed for all work with this journal.

Username: {$username}
Password: {$password}

Thank you,
{$principalContactSignature}'</query>

		<query>INSERT INTO email_templates_default_data (locale, email_key, subject, body, description) VALUES ('en_US', 'REVIEWER_REGISTER', 'Registration as Reviewer with {$journalName}', 'In light of your expertise, we have taken the liberty of registering your name in the reviewer database for {$journalName}. This does not entail any form of commitment on your part, but simply enables us to approach you with a submission to possibly review. On being invited to review, you will have an opportunity to see the title and abstract of the paper in question, and you\'ll always be in a position to accept or decline the invitation. You can also ask at any point to have your name removed from this reviewer list.

We are providing you with a username and password, which is used in all interactions with the journal through its website. You may wish, for example, to update your profile, including your reviewing interests.

Username: {$username}
Password: {$password}

Thank you,
{$principalContactSignature}', 'This email is sent to a newly registered reviewer to welcome them to the system and provide them with a record of their username and password.')</query>

		<query>INSERT INTO email_templates_default (email_key, can_edit, can_disable) VALUES ('REVIEWER_REGISTER', 1, 0)</query>
	</sql>
</data>
