<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE topic SYSTEM "../../topic.dtd">

<!--
  * 000000.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2005 The Public Knowledge Project
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  *
  * Introduction to OJS Main 
  *
  * $Id$
  -->

<topic id="intro/topic/000000" locale="en_US" title="Introduction to OJS" toc="intro/toc/000000" key="intro.index">
	<section>
		<![CDATA[<p>This journal uses the Open Journals Systems software for management and publishing support. OJS is an open source solution to managing and publishing scholarly journals online. OJS is a highly flexible editor-operated journal management and publishing system that can be downloaded for free and installed on a local Web server. It has been designed to reduce the time and energy devoted to the clerical and managerial tasks associated with editing a journal, while improving the record-keeping and efficiency of editorial processes. It seeks to improve the scholarly and public quality of journal publishing through a number of innovations, from making journal policies more transparent to improving indexing.</p><p>FLOW CHART FOR OJS EDITORIAL AND PUBLISHING PROCESS</p><p><i>OJS is a journal and web site management and publishing system</i>. OJS covers all aspects of online journal publishing, from setting up the journal website, through the author's submission to the peer review, editing, publication, archiving, and indexing of the journal. OJS also helps to manage the people aspects of organizing a journal, including keeping track of the work of editors, reviewers, and authors, notifying readers, and assisting with the correspondence.</p><p><i>OJS is flexible and scalable</i>. A single installation of OJS can support the operation of many journals, each with their own unique URL, as well as look and feel. It can enable a single editor to manage a journal and the journal's website. Or it will support an international team of editors with responsibilities for a journal's multiple sections.</p><p><i>OJS supports the principle of extending access</i>. This system is intended not only to assist with journal publishing, but to demonstrate how costs of journal publishing can be reduced to the point where providing readers with "open access" to the contents of the journal may be viable option. The case for open access is spelled out over a wide series of articles stemming from this project which are freely available at the Web site for the <a href="javascript:openWindow('http://pkp.ubc.ca');">Public Knowledge Project</a>.</p><p><i>The origins of OJS</i>. The system was first released in 2002 as a research and development initiative of the Public Knowledge Project at the University of British Columbia, with the support of the Social Sciences and Humanities Research Council of Canada, Max Bell Foundation, the Pacific Press Endowment, and the MacArthur Foundation. Its continuing development is currently overseen by a partnership among UBC's Public Knowledge Project, the Canadian Center for Studies in Publishing and the Simon Fraser University Library. For more information, see the <a href="javascript:openWindow('http://pkp.ubc.ca');">Public Knowledge Project</a>.</p>]]>	
	</section>
	
	<section title="Support">
		<![CDATA[<p>A support forum and bug reporting system for technical issues can be accessed via the PKP <a href="http://www.pkp.ubc.ca/" target="_blank">web site</a>.</p>
		<p>Users who have questions about interacting with a particular journal site using OJS or that journal's policies are encouraged to contact the journal's principal or support contacts, listed on the journal web site's about page.</p>]]>
	</section>
</topic>
