<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE email_texts SYSTEM "../../lib/pkp/dtd/emailTemplateData.dtd">

<!--
  * locale/en_US/emailTemplates.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2014-2019 Simon Fraser University
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2019 John Willinsky
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  * Localization information: https://pkp.sfu.ca/wiki/index.php?title=Translating_OxS
  * Localized email templates XML file.
  -->

<email_texts locale="en_US">
	<email_text key="NOTIFICATION">
		<subject>New notification from {$siteTitle}</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[You have a new notification from {$siteTitle}:<br />
<br />
{$notificationContents}<br />
<br />
Link: {$url}<br />
<br />
{$principalContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>The email is sent to registered users that have selected to have this type of notification emailed to them.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="PASSWORD_RESET_CONFIRM">
		<subject>Password Reset Confirmation</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[We have received a request to reset your password for the {$siteTitle} web site.<br />
<br />
If you did not make this request, please ignore this email and your password will not be changed. If you wish to reset your password, click on the below URL.<br />
<br />
Reset my password: {$url}<br />
<br />
{$principalContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email is sent to a registered user when they indicate that they have forgotten their password or are unable to login. It provides a URL they can follow to reset their password.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="PASSWORD_RESET">
		<subject>Password Reset</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[Your password has been successfully reset for use with the {$siteTitle} web site. Please retain this username and password, as it is necessary for all work with the journal.<br />
<br />
Your username: {$username}<br />
Password: {$password}<br />
<br />
{$principalContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email is sent to a registered user when they have successfully reset their password following the process described in the PASSWORD_RESET_CONFIRM email.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="USER_REGISTER">
		<subject>Journal Registration</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$userFullName}<br />
<br />
You have now been registered as a user with {$contextName}. We have included your username and password in this email, which are needed for all work with this journal through its website. At any point, you can ask to be removed from the journal's list of users by contacting me.<br />
<br />
Username: {$username}<br />
Password: {$password}<br />
<br />
Thank you,<br />
{$principalContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email is sent to a newly registered user to welcome them to the system and provide them with a record of their username and password.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="USER_VALIDATE">
		<subject>Validate Your Account</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$userFullName}<br />
<br />
You have created an account with {$contextName}, but before you can start using it, you need to validate your email account. To do this, simply follow the link below:<br />
<br />
{$activateUrl}<br />
<br />
Thank you,<br />
{$principalContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email is sent to a newly registered user to validate their email account.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="PUBLISH_NOTIFY">
		<subject>New Issue Published</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[Readers:<br />
<br />
{$contextName} has just published its latest issue at {$contextUrl}. We invite you to review the Table of Contents here and then visit our web site to review articles and items of interest.<br />
<br />
Thanks for the continuing interest in our work,<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email is sent to registered readers via the "Notify Users" link in the Editor's User Home. It notifies readers of a new issue and invites them to visit the journal at a supplied URL.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="LOCKSS_EXISTING_ARCHIVE">
		<subject>Archiving Request for {$contextName}</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[Dear [University Librarian]<br />
<br />
{$contextName} &amp;lt;{$contextUrl}&amp;gt;, is a journal for which a member of your faculty, [name of member], serves as a [title of position]. The journal is seeking to establish a LOCKSS (Lots of Copies Keep Stuff Safe) compliant archive with this and other university libraries.<br />
<br />
[Brief description of journal]<br />
<br />
The URL to the LOCKSS Publisher Manifest for our journal is: {$contextUrl}/gateway/lockss<br />
<br />
We understand that you are already participating in LOCKSS. If we can provide any additional metadata for purposes of registering our journal with your version of LOCKSS, we would be happy to provide it.<br />
<br />
Thank you,<br />
{$principalContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email requests the keeper of a LOCKSS archive to consider including this journal in their archive. It provides the URL to the journal's LOCKSS Publisher Manifest.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="SUBMISSION_ACK">
		<subject>Submission Acknowledgement</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$authorName}:<br />
<br />
Thank you for submitting the manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle}&quot; to {$contextName}. With the online journal management system that we are using, you will be able to track its progress through the editorial process by logging in to the journal web site:<br />
<br />
Submission URL: {$submissionUrl}<br />
Username: {$authorUsername}<br />
<br />
If you have any questions, please contact me. Thank you for considering this journal as a venue for your work.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email, when enabled, is automatically sent to an author when he or she completes the process of submitting a manuscript to the journal. It provides information about tracking the submission through the process and thanks the author for the submission.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="SUBMISSION_ACK_NOT_USER">
		<subject>Submission Acknowledgement</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[Hello,<br />
<br />
{$submitterName} has submitted the manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle}&quot; to {$contextName}. <br />
<br />
If you have any questions, please contact me. Thank you for considering this journal as a venue for your work.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email, when enabled, is automatically sent to the other authors who are not users within OJS specified during the submission process.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="EDITOR_ASSIGN">
		<subject>Editorial Assignment</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$editorialContactName}:<br />
<br />
The submission, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; to {$contextName} has been assigned to you to see through the editorial process in your role as Section Editor.<br />
<br />
Submission URL: {$submissionUrl}<br />
Username: {$editorUsername}<br />
<br />
Thank you.]]></body>
		<description>This email notifies a Section Editor that the Editor has assigned them the task of overseeing a submission through the editing process. It provides information about the submission and how to access the journal site.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="EDITOR_DECISION_ACCEPT">
		<subject>Editor Decision</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$authorName}:<br />
<br />
We have reached a decision regarding your submission to {$contextName}, &quot;{$submissionTitle}&quot;.<br />
<br />
Our decision is to: Accept Submission]]></body>
		<description>This email from the Editor or Section Editor to an Author notifies them of a final "accept submission" decision regarding their submission.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="EDITOR_DECISION_DECLINE">
		<subject>Editor Decision</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$authorName}:<br />
<br />
We have reached a decision regarding your submission to {$contextName}, &quot;{$submissionTitle}&quot;.<br />
<br />
Our decision is to: Decline Submission]]></body>
		<description>This email from the Editor or Section Editor to an Author notifies them of a final "decline" decision regarding their submission.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="EDITOR_RECOMMENDATION">
		<subject>Editor Recommendation</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$editors}:<br />
<br />
The recommendation regarding the submission to {$contextName}, &quot;{$submissionTitle}&quot; is: {$recommendation}]]></body>
		<description>This email from the recommending Editor or Section Editor to the decision making Editors or Section Editors notifies them of a final recommendation regarding the submission.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="REVISED_VERSION_NOTIFY">
		<subject>Revised Version Uploaded</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[Editors:<br />
<br />
A revised version of &quot;{$submissionTitle}&quot; has been uploaded by the author {$authorName}.<br />
<br />
Submission URL: {$submissionUrl}<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email is automatically sent to the assigned editor when author uploads a revised version of an article.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="NOTIFICATION_CENTER_DEFAULT">
		<subject>A message regarding {$contextName}</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[Please enter your message.]]></body>
		<description>The default (blank) message used in the Notification Center Message Listbuilder.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="EDITOR_DECISION_INITIAL_DECLINE">
		<subject>Editor Decision</subject>
		<body>
			<![CDATA[{$authorName}:<br />
<br />
We have reached a decision regarding your submission to {$contextName}, &quot;{$submissionTitle}&quot;.<br />
<br />
Our decision is to: Decline Submission]]></body>
		<description>This email is sent to the author if the editor declines his submission initially, before the review stage</description>
	</email_text>
</email_texts>
