<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE email_texts SYSTEM "../../lib/pkp/dtd/emailTemplateData.dtd">

<!--
  * locale/ru_RU/emailTemplateData.xml
  *
  * Copyright (c) 2014-2015 Simon Fraser University Library
  * Copyright (c) 2003-2015 John Willinsky
  * Distributed under the GNU GPL v2. For full terms see the file docs/COPYING.
  *
  * Localized email templates XML file.
  *
  -->

<email_texts locale="ru_RU">
	<email_text key="PASSWORD_RESET_CONFIRM">
		<subject>Password Reset Confirmation</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[We have received a request to reset your password for the {$siteTitle} web site.<br />
<br />
If you did not make this request, please ignore this email and your password will not be changed. If you wish to reset your password, click on the below URL.<br />
<br />
Reset my password: {$url}<br />
<br />
{$principalContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email is sent to a registered user when they indicate that they have forgotten their password or are unable to login. It provides a URL they can follow to reset their password.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="PASSWORD_RESET">
		<subject>Password Reset</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[Your password has been successfully reset for use with the {$siteTitle} web site. Please retain this username and password, as it is necessary for all work with the journal.<br />
<br />
Your username: {$username}<br />
Your new password: {$password}<br />
<br />
{$principalContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email is sent to a registered user when they have successfully reset their password following the process described in the PASSWORD_RESET_CONFIRM email.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="USER_REGISTER">
		<subject>New User Registration</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[Thank you for registering as a user with {$contextName}. Please keep track of your username and password, which are needed for all work with this journal.<br />
<br />
Username: {$username}<br />
Password: {$password}<br />
<br />
Thank you,<br />
{$principalContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email is sent to a newly registered user to welcome them to the system and provide them with a record of their username and password.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="PUBLISH_NOTIFY">
		<subject>New Issue Published</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[Readers:<br />
<br />
{$contextName} has just published its latest issue at <a href="{$journalUrl}">{$journalUrl}</a>. We invite you to review the Table of Contents here and then visit our web site to review articles and items of interest.<br />
<br />
Thanks for the continuing interest in our work,<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email is sent to registered readers via the "Notify Users" link in the Editor's User Home. It notifies readers of a new issue and invites them to visit the journal at a supplied URL.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="SUBSCRIPTION_NOTIFY">
		<subject>Subscription Notification</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$subscriberName}:<br />
<br />
You have now been registered as a subscriber in our online journal management system for {$contextName}, with the following subscription:<br />
<br />
{$subscriptionType}<br />
<br />
To access content that is available only to subscribers, simply log in to the system with your username, &quot;{$username}&quot;.<br />
<br />
Once you have logged in to the system you can change your profile details and password at any point.<br />
<br />
Please note that if you have an institutional subscription, there is no need for users at your institution to log in, since requests for subscription content will be automatically authenticated by the system.<br />
<br />
If you have any questions, please feel free to contact me.<br />
<br />
{$subscriptionContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email notifies a registered reader that the Manager has created a subscription for them. It provides the journal's URL along with instructions for access.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="LOCKSS_EXISTING_ARCHIVE">
		<subject>Archiving Request for {$contextName}</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[Dear [University Librarian]<br />
<br />
{$contextName} &amp;lt;<a href="{$journalUrl}">{$journalUrl}</a>&amp;gt;, is a journal for which a member of your faculty, [name of member], serves as a [title of position]. The journal is seeking to establish a LOCKSS (Lots of Copies Keep Stuff Safe) compliant archive with this and other university libraries.<br />
<br />
[Brief description of journal]<br />
<br />
The URL to the LOCKSS Publisher Manifest for our journal is: <a href="{$journalUrl}">{$journalUrl}</a>/gateway/lockss<br />
<br />
We understand that you are already participating in LOCKSS. If we can provide any additional metadata for purposes of registering our journal with your version of LOCKSS, we would be happy to provide it.<br />
<br />
Thank you,<br />
{$principalContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email requests the keeper of a LOCKSS archive to consider including this journal in their archive. It provides the URL to the journal's LOCKSS Publisher Manifest.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="LOCKSS_NEW_ARCHIVE">
		<subject>Archiving Request for {$contextName}</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[Dear [University Librarian]<br />
<br />
{$contextName} &amp;lt;<a href="{$journalUrl}">{$journalUrl}</a>&amp;gt;, is a journal for which a member of your faculty, [name of member] serves as a [title of position]. The journal is seeking to establish a LOCKSS (Lots of Copies Keep Stuff Safe) compliant archive with this and other university libraries.<br />
<br />
[Brief description of journal]<br />
<br />
The LOCKSS Program &amp;lt;http://lockss.org/&amp;gt;, an international library/publisher initiative, is a working example of a distributed preservation and archiving repository, additional details are below. The software, which runs on an ordinary personal computer is free; the system is easily brought on-line; very little ongoing maintenance is required.<br />
<br />
To assist in the archiving of our journal, we invite you to become a member of the LOCKSS community, to help collect and preserve titles produced by your faculty and by other scholars worldwide. To do so, please have someone on your staff visit the LOCKSS site for information on how this system operates. I look forward to hearing from you on the feasibility of providing this archiving support for this journal.<br />
<br />
Thank you,<br />
{$principalContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email encourages the recipient to participate in the LOCKSS initiative and include this journal in the archive. It provides information about the LOCKSS initiative and ways to become involved.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="SUBMISSION_ACK">
		<subject>Submission Acknowledgement</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$authorName}:<br />
<br />
Thank you for submitting the manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle}&quot; to {$contextName}. With the online journal management system that we are using, you will be able to track its progress through the editorial process by logging in to the journal web site:<br />
<br />
Manuscript URL: <a href="{$submissionUrl}">{$submissionUrl}</a><br />
Username: {$authorUsername}<br />
<br />
If you have any questions, please contact me. Thank you for considering this journal as a venue for your work.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email, when enabled, is automatically sent to an author when he or she completes the process of submitting a manuscript to the journal. It provides information about tracking the submission through the process and thanks the author for the submission.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="SUBMISSION_UNSUITABLE">
		<subject>Unsuitable Submission</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$authorName}:<br />
<br />
An initial review of &quot;{$submissionTitle}&quot; has made it clear that this submission does not fit within the scope and focus of {$contextName}. I recommend that you consult the description of this journal under About, as well as its current contents, to learn more about the work that we publish. You might also consider submitting this manuscript to another, more suitable journal.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="SUBMISSION_COMMENT">
		<subject>Submission Comment</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$name}:<br />
<br />
{$commentName} has added a comment to the submission, &quot;{$submissionTitle}&quot; in {$contextName}:<br />
<br />
{$comments}]]></body>
		<description>This email notifies the various people involved in a submission's editing process that a new comment has been posted.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="SUBMISSION_DECISION_REVIEWERS">
		<subject>Decision on "{$submissionTitle}"</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[As one of the reviewers for the submission, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; to {$contextName}, I am sending you the reviews and editorial decision sent to the author of this piece. Thank you again for your important contribution to this process.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}<br />
<br />
{$comments}]]></body>
		<description>This email notifies the reviewers of a submission that the review process has been completed. It includes information about the article and the decision reached, and thanks the reviewers for their contributions.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="EDITOR_ASSIGN">
		<subject>Editorial Assignment</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$editorialContactName}:<br />
<br />
The submission, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; to {$contextName} has been assigned to you to see through the editorial process in your role as Section Editor.<br />
<br />
Submission URL: <a href="{$submissionUrl}">{$submissionUrl}</a><br />
Username: {$editorUsername}<br />
<br />
Thank you,<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email notifies a Section Editor that the Editor has assigned them the task of overseeing a submission through the editing process. It provides information about the submission and how to access the journal site.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="REVIEW_REQUEST">
		<subject>Article Review Request</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$reviewerName}:<br />
<br />
I believe that you would serve as an excellent reviewer of the manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; which has been submitted to {$contextName}. The submission's extract is inserted below, and I hope that you will consider undertaking this important task for us.<br />
<br />
Please log into the journal web site by {$weekLaterDate} to indicate whether you will undertake the review or not, as well as to access the submission and to record your review and recommendation. The web site is <a href="{$journalUrl}">{$journalUrl}</a><br />
<br />
The review itself is due {$reviewDueDate}.<br />
<br />
If you do not have your username and password for the journal's web site, you can use this link to reset your password (which will then be emailed to you along with your username). <a href="{$passwordResetUrl}">{$passwordResetUrl}</a><br />
<br />
Submission URL: <a href="{$submissionReviewUrl}">{$submissionReviewUrl}</a><br />
<br />
Thank you for considering this request.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
&quot;{$submissionTitle}&quot;<br />
<br />
Abstract<br />
{$submissionAbstract}]]></body>
		<description>This email from the Section Editor to a Reviewer requests that the reviewer accept or decline the task of reviewing a submission. It provides information about the submission such as the title and abstract, a review due date, and how to access the submission itself. This message is used when the Standard Review Process is selected in Journal Setup, Step 2. (Otherwise see REVIEW_REQUEST_ATTACHED.)</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="REVIEW_REQUEST_ATTACHED">
		<subject>Article Review Request</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$reviewerName}:<br />
<br />
I believe that you would serve as an excellent reviewer of the manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; and I am asking that you consider undertaking this important task for us. The Review Guidelines for this journal are appended below, and the submission is attached to this email. Your review of the submission, along with your recommendation, should be emailed to me by {$reviewDueDate}.<br />
<br />
Please indicate in a return email by {$weekLaterDate} whether you are able and willing to do the review.<br />
<br />
Thank you for considering this request.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}<br />
<br />
<br />
Review Guidelines<br />
<br />
{$reviewGuidelines}<br />
]]></body>
		<description>This email is sent by the Section Editor to a Reviewer to request that they accept or decline the task of reviewing a submission. It includes the submission as an attachment. This message is used when the Email-Attachment Review Process is selected in Journal Setup, Step 2. (Otherwise see REVIEW_REQUEST.)</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="REVIEW_CANCEL">
		<subject>Request for Review Cancelled</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$reviewerName}:<br />
<br />
We have decided at this point to cancel our request for you to review the submission, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}. We apologize for any inconvenience this may cause you and hope that we will be able to call on you to assist with this journal's review process in the future.<br />
<br />
If you have any questions, please contact me.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email is sent by the Section Editor to a Reviewer who has a submission review in progress to notify them that the review has been cancelled.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="REVIEW_CONFIRM">
		<subject>Able to Review</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$editorialContactName}:<br />
<br />
I am able and willing to review the submission, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}. Thank you for thinking of me, and I plan to have the review completed by its due date, {$reviewDueDate}, if not before.<br />
<br />
{$reviewerName}]]></body>
		<description>This email is sent by a Reviewer to the Section Editor in response to a review request to notify the Section Editor that the review request has been accepted and will be completed by the specified date.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="REVIEW_DECLINE">
		<subject>Unable to Review</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$editorialContactName}:<br />
<br />
I am afraid that at this time I am unable to review the submission, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}. Thank you for thinking of me, and another time feel free to call on me.<br />
<br />
{$reviewerName}]]></body>
		<description>This email is sent by a Reviewer to the Section Editor in response to a review request to notify the Section Editor that the review request has been declined.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="REVIEW_COMPLETE">
		<subject>Article Review Completed</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$editorialContactName}:<br />
<br />
I have now completed my review of &quot;{$submissionTitle}&quot; for {$contextName}, and submitted my recommendation, &quot;{$recommendation}.&quot;<br />
<br />
{$reviewerName}]]></body>
		<description>This email is sent by a Reviewer to the Section Editor to notify them that a review has been completed and the comments and recommendations have been recorded on the journal web site.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="REVIEW_ACK">
		<subject>Article Review Acknowledgement</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$reviewerName}:<br />
<br />
Thank you for completing the review of the submission, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}. We appreciate your contribution to the quality of the work that we publish.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email is sent by a Section Editor to confirm receipt of a completed review and thank the reviewer for their contributions.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="REVIEW_REMIND">
		<subject>Submission Review Reminder</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$reviewerName}:<br />
<br />
Just a gentle reminder of our request for your review of the submission, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}. We were hoping to have this review by {$reviewDueDate}, and would be pleased to receive it as soon as you are able to prepare it.<br />
<br />
If you do not have your username and password for the journal's web site, you can use this link to reset your password (which will then be emailed to you along with your username). <a href="{$passwordResetUrl}">{$passwordResetUrl}</a><br />
<br />
Submission URL: <a href="{$submissionReviewUrl}">{$submissionReviewUrl}</a><br />
<br />
Please confirm your ability to complete this vital contribution to the work of the journal. I look forward to hearing from you.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email is sent by a Section Editor to remind a reviewer that their review is due.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="REVIEW_REMIND_AUTO">
		<subject>Automated Submission Review Reminder</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$reviewerName}:<br />
<br />
Just a gentle reminder of our request for your review of the submission, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}. We were hoping to have this review by {$reviewDueDate}, and this email has been automatically generated and sent with the passing of that date. We would still be pleased to receive it as soon as you are able to prepare it.<br />
<br />
If you do not have your username and password for the journal's web site, you can use this link to reset your password (which will then be emailed to you along with your username). <a href="{$passwordResetUrl}">{$passwordResetUrl}</a><br />
<br />
Submission URL: <a href="{$submissionReviewUrl}">{$submissionReviewUrl}</a><br />
<br />
Please confirm your ability to complete this vital contribution to the work of the journal. I look forward to hearing from you.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email is automatically sent when a reviewer's due date elapses (see Review Options under Journal Setup, Step 2). Scheduled tasks must be enabled and configured (see the site configuration file).</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="COPYEDIT_REQUEST">
		<subject>Copyediting Request</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$copyeditorName}:<br />
<br />
I would ask that you undertake the copyediting of the manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}. The submission is found on the journal web site, along with a set of Instructions for Copyediting.<br />
<br />
Manuscript URL: <a href="{$submissionCopyeditingUrl}">{$submissionCopyeditingUrl}</a><br />
Username: {$copyeditorUsername}<br />
<br />
If you are unable to undertake this work at this time or have any questions, please contact me. Thank you for agreeing to undertake this important work for the journal.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email is sent by a Section Editor to a submission's Copyeditor to request that they begin the copyediting process. It provides information about the submission and how to access it.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="COPYEDIT_COMPLETE">
		<subject>Copyediting Completed</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$editorialContactName}:<br />
<br />
I have now completed the first round of copyediting of  the manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}. It is now ready for the author and editor to review the changes and queries.<br />
<br />
Thank you,<br />
{$copyeditorName}]]></body>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="COPYEDIT_ACK">
		<subject>Copyediting Acknowledgement</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$copyeditorName}:<br />
<br />
Thank you for copyediting the manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}. It will make an important contribution to the quality of this journal.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email is sent by the Section Editor to a submission's Copyeditor to acknowledge that the Copyeditor has successfully completed the copyediting process and thank them for their contribution.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="COPYEDIT_AUTHOR_REQUEST">
		<subject>Copyediting Review Request</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$authorName}:<br />
<br />
We have now copyedited your submission, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}. To review the proposed changes and respond to Author Queries, please log into the journal web site using the link below. Download and open the Initial Copyedit File. After reviewing the copyediting, upload the file in Step 2 and send the COMPLETE email to the editor.<br />
<br />
This is the last opportunity that you have to make substantial changes. You will be asked to proofread the galleys, but at that stage we will only be able to correct minor typographical and layout errors.<br />
<br />
Manuscript URL: <a href="{$submissionCopyeditingUrl}">{$submissionCopyeditingUrl}</a><br />
<br />
If you are unable to undertake this work at this time or have any questions, please contact me. Thank you for your contribution to this journal.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email is sent by the Section Editor to a submission's Author to request that they proofread the work of the copyeditor. It provides access information for the manuscript and warns that this is the last opportunity the author has to make substantial changes.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="COPYEDIT_AUTHOR_COMPLETE">
		<subject>Copyediting Review Completed</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$editorialContactName}:<br />
<br />
I have now reviewed the copyediting of the manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}, and it is ready for the final round of copyediting and preparation for Layout.<br />
<br />
Thank you for this contribution to my work,<br />
{$authorName}]]></body>
		<description>This email is sent by the Author to the Section Editor to notify them that the Author's copyediting process has been completed.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="COPYEDIT_AUTHOR_ACK">
		<subject>Copyediting Review Acknowledgement</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$authorName}:<br />
<br />
Thank you for reviewing the copyediting of your manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}. We look forward to publishing this work.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email is sent by the Section Editor to a submission's Author to confirm completion of the Author's copyediting process and thank them for their contribution.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="COPYEDIT_FINAL_REQUEST">
		<subject>Copyediting Final Review</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$copyeditorName}:<br />
<br />
The author and editor have now completed their review of the copyediting of the manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}. The final &quot;clean copy&quot; can now be prepared for Layout.<br />
<br />
Manuscript URL: <a href="{$submissionCopyeditingUrl}">{$submissionCopyeditingUrl}</a><br />
Username: {$copyeditorUsername}<br />
<br />
Thank you on behalf of the journal,<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email from the Section Editor to the Copyeditor requests that they perform a final round of copyediting on a submission before it enters the layout process.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="COPYEDIT_FINAL_COMPLETE">
		<subject>Copyediting Final Review Completed</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$editorialContactName}:<br />
<br />
I have now prepared a clean, copyedited version of the manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}. It is ready for Layout and the preparation of the galleys.<br />
<br />
{$copyeditorName}]]></body>
		<description>This email from the Copyeditor to the Section Editor notifies them that the final round of copyediting has been completed and that the layout process may now begin.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="COPYEDIT_FINAL_ACK">
		<subject>Copyediting Final Review Acknowledgement</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$copyeditorName}:<br />
<br />
Thank you for completing the copyediting of the manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}. This preparation of a &quot;clean copy&quot; for Layout is an important step in the editorial process.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email from the Section Editor to the Copyeditor acknowledges completion of the final round of copyediting and thanks them for their contribution.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="LAYOUT_REQUEST">
		<subject>Request Galleys</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$layoutEditorName}:<br />
<br />
I would ask that you prepare the galleys for the manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}.<br />
<br />
Manuscript URL: <a href="{$submissionLayoutUrl}">{$submissionLayoutUrl}</a><br />
Username: {$layoutEditorUsername}<br />
<br />
If you are unable to undertake this work at this time or have any questions, please contact me. Thank you for your contribution to this journal.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email from the Section Editor to the Layout Editor notifies them that they have been assigned the task of performing layout editing on a submission. It provides information about the submission and how to access it.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="LAYOUT_COMPLETE">
		<subject>Galleys Complete</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$editorialContactName}:<br />
<br />
Galleys have now been prepared for the manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName} and are ready for proofreading.<br />
<br />
If you have any questions, please contact me.<br />
<br />
{$layoutEditorName}]]></body>
		<description>This email from the Layout Editor to the Section Editor notifies them that the layout process has been completed.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="LAYOUT_ACK">
		<subject>Layout Acknowledgement</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$layoutEditorName}:<br />
<br />
Thank you for preparing the galleys for the manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}. This is an important contribution to the publishing process.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email from the Section Editor to the Layout Editor acknowledges completion of the layout editing process and thanks the layout editor for their contribution.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="PROOFREAD_AUTHOR_REQUEST">
		<subject>Proofreading Request (Author)</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$authorName}:<br />
<br />
We would ask that you proofread the galleys for your submission, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}. To view the galleys, please log into the journal web site using the link below. Use the VIEW PROOF link to read what will be the published version of item for typographical and layout errors only. Record these errors in the Proofreading Corrections box, following the proofing instructions provided.<br />
<br />
Manuscript URL: <a href="{$submissionUrl}">{$submissionUrl}</a><br />
<br />
If you are unable to undertake this work at this time or have any questions, please contact me. Thank you for your contribution to this journal.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email from the Section Editor to the Author notifies them that an article's galleys are ready for proofreading. It provides information about the article and how to access it.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="PROOFREAD_AUTHOR_COMPLETE">
		<subject>Proofreading Completed (Author)</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$editorialContactName}:<br />
<br />
I have completed proofreading the galleys for my manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}. The galleys are now ready to have any final corrections made by the Proofreader and Layout Editor.<br />
<br />
{$authorName}]]></body>
		<description>This email from the Author to the Proofreader and Editor notifies them that the Author's round of proofreading is complete and that details can be found in the article comments.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="PROOFREAD_AUTHOR_ACK">
		<subject>Proofreading Acknowledgement (Author)</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$authorName}:<br />
<br />
Thank you for proofreading the galleys for your manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; in {$contextName}. We are looking forward to publishing your work shortly.<br />
<br />
If you subscribe to our notification service, you will receive an email of the Table of Contents as soon as it is published. If you have any questions, please contact me.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email from the Section Editor to the Author acknowledges completion of the initial proofreading process and thanks them for their contribution.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="PROOFREAD_REQUEST">
		<subject>Proofreading Request</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$proofreaderName}:<br />
<br />
I would ask that you proofread the galleys for the manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}.<br />
<br />
Manuscript URL: <a href="{$submissionUrl}">{$submissionUrl}</a><br />
Username: {$proofreaderUsername}<br />
<br />
If you are unable to undertake this work at this time or have any questions, please contact me. Thank you for your contribution to this journal.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email from the Section Editor to the Proofreader requests that they perform proofreading of an article's galleys. It provides information about the article and how to access it.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="PROOFREAD_COMPLETE">
		<subject>Proofreading Completed</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$editorialContactName}:<br />
<br />
I have completed proofreading the galleys for the manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}. The galleys are now ready to have any final corrections made by the Layout Editor.<br />
<br />
{$proofreaderName}]]></body>
		<description>This email from the Proofreader to the Section Editor notifies them that the Proofreader has completed the proofreading process.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="PROOFREAD_ACK">
		<subject>Proofreading Acknowledgement</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$proofreaderName}:<br />
<br />
Thank you for proofreading the galleys for the manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}. This work makes an important contribution to the quality of this journal.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email from the Section Editor to the Proofreader confirms completion of the proofreader's proofreading process and thanks them for their contribution.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="PROOFREAD_LAYOUT_REQUEST">
		<subject>Proofreading Request (Layout Editor)</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$layoutEditorName}:<br />
<br />
We would ask that make any corrections required as a result of proofreading the galleys for the manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}.<br />
<br />
Manuscript URL: <a href="{$submissionUrl}">{$submissionUrl}</a><br />
Username: {$layoutEditorUsername}<br />
<br />
If you are unable to undertake this work at this time or have any questions, please contact me. Thank you for your contribution to this journal.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email from the Section Editor to the Layout Editor notifies them that an article's galleys are ready for final proofreading. It provides information on the article and how to access it.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="PROOFREAD_LAYOUT_COMPLETE">
		<subject>Proofreading Completed (Layout Editor)</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$editorialContactName}:<br />
<br />
The galleys have now been corrected, following their proofreading, for the manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}. This piece is now ready to publish.<br />
<br />
{$layoutEditorName}]]></body>
		<description>This email from the Layout Editor to the Section Editor notifies them that the final stage of proofreading has been completed and the article is now ready to publish.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="PROOFREAD_LAYOUT_ACK">
		<subject>Proofreading Acknowledgement (Layout Editor)</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$layoutEditorName}:<br />
<br />
Thank you for completing the proofreading corrections for the galleys associated with the manuscript, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; for {$contextName}. This represents an important contribution to the work of this journal.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>This email from the Section Editor to the Layout Editor acknowledges completion of the final stage of proofreading and thanks them for their contribution.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="EMAIL_LINK">
		<subject>Article of Possible Interest</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[Thought you might be interested in seeing &quot;{$submissionTitle}&quot; by {$authorName} published in Vol {$volume}, No {$number} ({$year}) of {$contextName} at &quot;<a href="{$articleUrl}">{$articleUrl}</a>&quot;.]]></body>
		<description>This email template provides a registered reader with the opportunity to send information about an article to somebody who may be interested. It is available via the Reading Tools and must be enabled by the Journal Manager in the Reading Tools Administration page.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="NOTIFICATION">
		<subject>извещение сайта {$siteTitle}</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[У Вас новое извещение на сайте {$siteTitle}:<br />
<br />
{$notificationContents}<br />
<br />
Ссылка: {$url}<br />
<br />
{$principalContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description></description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="NOTIFICATION_MAILLIST">
		<subject>извещение сайта {$siteTitle}</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[У Вас новое извещение на сайте  {$siteTitle}:<br />
--<br />
{$notificationContents}<br />
<br />
Ссылка: {$url}<br />
--<br />
<br />
Если хотите прекратить получение извещений, пожалуйста перейдите по ссылке  {$unsubscribeLink} и введите свой почтовый адрес и пароль.<br />
<br />
{$principalContactSignature}]]></body>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="NOTIFICATION_MAILLIST_WELCOME">
		<subject>Добро пожаловать в список рассылки {$siteTitle} !</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[Вы подписались на получение извещений с сайта {$siteTitle}.<br />
<br />
Пожалуйста нажмите на ссылку для подтверждения своего запроса и добавления Вашего почтового адреса в список рассылки: {$confirmLink}<br />
<br />
Если не хотите получать извещения, пожалуйста нажмите на ссылку {$unsubscribeLink}  и введите свой почтовый адрес и пароль.<br />
<br />
Пароль для отключения извещений: {$password}<br />
<br />
{$principalContactSignature}]]></body>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="USER_VALIDATE">
		<subject>Подтвердите свой электронный адрес</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$userFullName}<br />
<br />
Вы зарегистрировались в журнале {$contextName}, но перед тем как начать пользоваться своей учетной записью, нужно подтвердить правильность Вашего электронного адреса. Чтобы это сделать просто пройдите по ссылке:<br />
<br />
<a href="{$activateUrl}">{$activateUrl}</a><br />
<br />
Спасибо !<br />
<br />
{$principalContactSignature}]]></body>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="REVIEWER_REGISTER">
		<subject>Регистрация в качестве рецензента журнала {$contextName}</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[Принимая во внимание Ваш высокий научный уровень и опыт, мы зарегистрировали Вас в базе данных потенциальных рецензентов журнала {$contextName}. Это ни в коем случае не налагает на Вас никаких обязательств, но лишь помогает нам связываться с Вами при подаче нам рукописей, рецензетом которых Вы могли бы стать. Получив приглашение к рецензированию Вы увидите название и тезисы рукописи и возможность принять или отклонить приглашение. В любой момент, если захотите, Ваше имя будет убрано из списка потенциальных рецензентов.<br />
<br />
Мы даем Вам имя пользователя и пароль, необходимые для любого взаимодействия с нашим журналом через его сайт. Например, Вы можете уточнить свои данные и темы рукописей, которые Вы могли бы рассмотреть.<br />
<br />
Логин: {$username}<br />
Пароль: {$password}<br />
<br />
Спасибо !<br />
<br />
{$principalContactSignature}]]></body>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="REVIEW_REQUEST_ONECLICK">
		<subject>Запрос на рецензию</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$reviewerName}:<br />
<br />
Я уверен, Вы могли бы стать очень хорошим рецензентом для рукописи, &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; (ее резюме Вы найдете ниже) присланной для публикации в журнале {$contextName}. Надеюсь, на Вашу помощь в столь важной для нас задаче.<br />
<br />
Пожалуйста войдите на сайт нашего журнала до {$weekLaterDate}, чтобы согласиться (или отклонить) это предложение, либо чтобы получить доступ к полному тексту рукописи и передать Вашу рецензию и рекомендации.<br />
<br />
Если Вы согласны, рецензию требуется отправить до {$reviewDueDate}.<br />
<br />
Ссылка на рукопись: <a href="{$submissionReviewUrl}">{$submissionReviewUrl}</a><br />
<br />
Спасибо за Ваше рассмотрение !<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}<br />
<br />
<br />
<br />
&quot;{$submissionTitle}&quot;<br />
<br />
{$submissionAbstract}]]></body>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="REVIEW_REMIND_ONECLICK">
		<subject>Напоминание о запросе на рецензию</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$reviewerName}:<br />
<br />
Просим прощение за напоминание о нашем запросе на рецензию рукописи &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; для журнала {$contextName}. Мы надеялись получить рецензию до {$reviewDueDate}, и были бы очень благодарны получить ее как только Вы ее сможете приготовить.<br />
<br />
Ссылка на рукопись: <a href="{$submissionReviewUrl}">{$submissionReviewUrl}</a><br />
<br />
Пожалуйста подтвердите возможность закончить эту важную для журнала задачу.<br />
<br />
Надеюсь на Ваш ответ.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="REVIEW_REMIND_AUTO_ONECLICK">
		<subject>автоматическоне напоминание о рецензии</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$reviewerName}:<br />
<br />
Просим прощение за напоминание о нашем запросе на рецензию рукописи &quot;{$submissionTitle},&quot; для журнала {$contextName}. Мы надеялись получить рецензию до {$reviewDueDate} и это письмо было сгенерировано нашей системой автоматически по прошествии этой даты. Несмотря на это, мы были бы очень благодарны получить рецензию как только Вы ее сможете приготовить.<br />
<br />
Ссылка на рукопись: <a href="{$submissionReviewUrl}">{$submissionReviewUrl}</a><br />
<br />
Пожалуйста подтвердите возможность закончить эту важную для журнала задачу.<br />
<br />
Надеюсь на Ваш ответ.<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>Это письмо высылается автоматически если рецензент не высылает рецензию вовремя (см. опции рецензирования в настройках журнала, Шаг 2) и включен прямой доступ рецензентов к рукописям. Для работы в конфигурационном файле должны быть включены периодические задачи.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="EDITOR_DECISION_ACCEPT">
		<subject>Редакционное решение</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$authorName}:<br />
<br />
Мы приняли решение относительно Вашей рукописи &quot;{$submissionTitle}&quot;, отправленной для публикации в наш журнал {$journalTitle}.<br />
<br />
Наше решение:<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>Это письмо высылается редактором или редактором секции, чтобы уведомить автора об окончательном решении относительно его рукописи.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="EDITOR_DECISION_REVISIONS">
		<subject>Редакционное решение</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$authorName}:<br />
<br />
Мы приняли решение относительно Вашей рукописи &quot;{$submissionTitle}&quot;, отправленной для публикации в наш журнал {$journalTitle}.<br />
<br />
Наше решение:<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="EDITOR_DECISION_RESUBMIT">
		<subject>Редакционное решение</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$authorName}:<br />
<br />
Мы приняли решение относительно Вашей рукописи &quot;{$submissionTitle}&quot;, отправленной для публикации в наш журнал {$journalTitle}.<br />
<br />
Наше решение:<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>Это письмо высылается редактором или редактором секции, чтобы уведомить автора об окончательном решении относительно его рукописи.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="EDITOR_DECISION_DECLINE">
		<subject>Редакционное решение</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$authorName}:<br />
<br />
Мы приняли решение относительно Вашей рукописи &quot;{$submissionTitle}&quot;, отправленной для публикации в наш журнал {$journalTitle}.<br />
<br />
Наше решение:<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="OPEN_ACCESS_NOTIFY">
		<subject>выпуск в открытом доступе</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[Читатели:<br />
<br />
{$contextName} открывает свободный доступ к следующему выпуску. Мы приглашаем Вас ознакомиться с его оглавлением здесь и посетить наш сайт (<a href="{$journalUrl}">{$journalUrl}</a>) для получения доступа к полному тексту статей.<br />
<br />
Спасибо за интерес !<br />
<br />
{$editorialContactSignature}]]></body>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="SUBSCRIPTION_BEFORE_EXPIRY">
		<subject>уведомление об окончании срока подписки</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$subscriberName}:<br />
<br />
Ваша подписка на {$contextName} истекает.<br />
<br />
{$subscriptionType}<br />
Дата окончания: {$expiryDate}<br />
<br />
Для обеспечения непрерывности Вашего доступа к журналу, пожалуйста посетите наш сайт и продлите подписку. Вы сможете войти под своим именем как &quot;{$username}&quot;.<br />
<br />
Свяжитесь со мной, если у Вас есть вопросы.<br />
<br />
{$subscriptionContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>Уведомляет подписчика, что его подписка скоро закончится.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="SUBSCRIPTION_AFTER_EXPIRY">
		<subject>уведомление об окончании срока подписки</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$subscriberName}:<br />
<br />
Срок Вашей подписки на журнал {$contextName} истек.<br />
<br />
{$subscriptionType}<br />
Дата окончания: {$expiryDate}<br />
<br />
Для продления пожалуйста посетите наш сайт. Вы сможете войти под своим именем как &quot;{$username}&quot;.<br />
<br />
Свяжитесь со мной, если у Вас есть вопросы.<br />
<br />
{$subscriptionContactSignature}]]></body>
		<description>Уведомляет подписчика, что срок его подписки истек.</description>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="SUBSCRIPTION_AFTER_EXPIRY_LAST">
		<subject>срок подписки истек -- последнее напоминание</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[{$subscriberName}:<br />
<br />
Срок Вашей подписки на журнал {$contextName} истек.<br />
Заметьте, это последнее напоминание.<br />
<br />
{$subscriptionType}<br />
Дата окончания: {$expiryDate}<br />
<br />
Для продления пожалуйста посетите наш сайт. Вы сможете войти под своим именем как &quot;{$username}&quot;.<br />
<br />
Свяжитесь со мной, если у Вас есть вопросы.<br />
<br />
{$subscriptionContactSignature}]]></body>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="SUBSCRIPTION_PURCHASE_INDL">
		<subject>подписка: индивидуальная</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[В журнале {$contextName} приобретена индивидуальная подписка со следующими деталями.<br />
<br />
Тип подписки:<br />
{$subscriptionType}<br />
<br />
Пользователь:<br />
{$userDetails}<br />
<br />
Информация о членстве (если указана):<br />
{$membership}<br />
<br />
Для просмотра или изменения этой подписки используйте следующую ссылку.<br />
<br />
Ссылка на подписку: <a href="{$subscriptionUrl}">{$subscriptionUrl}</a>]]></body>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="SUBSCRIPTION_PURCHASE_INSTL">
		<subject>подписка: институциональная</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[В журнале {$contextName} приобретена институциональнаяподписка со следующими деталями. Для ее активации посетите приведенную в конце ссылку и установите там &quot;статус подписки&quot; -- &quot;активный&quot;.<br />
<br />
Тип подписки:<br />
{$subscriptionType}<br />
<br />
Организация:<br />
{$institutionName}<br />
{$institutionMailingAddress}<br />
<br />
Доменное имя (если указано):<br />
{$domain}<br />
<br />
IP адреса (если указаны):<br />
{$ipRanges}<br />
<br />
Контакт:<br />
{$userDetails}<br />
<br />
Информация о членстве (если указана):<br />
{$membership}<br />
<br />
Для просмотра или изменения этой подписки используйте следующую ссылку.<br />
<br />
Ссылка на подписку: <a href="{$subscriptionUrl}">{$subscriptionUrl}</a>]]></body>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="SUBSCRIPTION_RENEW_INDL">
		<subject>продление подписки: индивидуальная</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[В журнале {$contextName} продлена индивидуальная подписка со следующими деталями.<br />
<br />
Тип подписки:<br />
{$subscriptionType}<br />
<br />
Пользователь:<br />
{$userDetails}<br />
<br />
Информация о членстве (если указана):<br />
{$membership}<br />
<br />
Для просмотра или изменения этой подписки используйте следующую ссылку.<br />
<br />
Ссылка на подписку: <a href="{$subscriptionUrl}">{$subscriptionUrl}</a>]]></body>
	</email_text>
	<email_text key="SUBSCRIPTION_RENEW_INSTL">
		<subject>продление подписки: институциональная</subject>
		<body><![CDATA[В журнале {$contextName} продлена институциональнаяподписка со следующими деталями.<br />
<br />
Тип подписки:<br />
{$subscriptionType}<br />
<br />
Организация:<br />
{$institutionName}<br />
{$institutionMailingAddress}<br />
<br />
Доменное имя (если указано):<br />
{$domain}<br />
<br />
IP адреса (если указаны):<br />
{$ipRanges}<br />
<br />
Контакт:<br />
{$userDetails}<br />
<br />
Информация о членстве (если указана):<br />
{$membership}<br />
<br />
Для просмотра или изменения этой подписки используйте следующую ссылку.<br />
<br />
Ссылка на подписку: <a href="{$subscriptionUrl}">{$subscriptionUrl}</a>]]></body>
	</email_text>
</email_texts>
